[
  {
    "subject": "Empire Maker",
    "src": "The father of Empire Maker was who?",
    "pred": "Danehill Dancer",
    "rephrase": "Who was the father of Empire Maker?",
    "alt": "Danehill",
    "answers": [
      "Unbridled"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are considered to be the founding fathers",
    "loc_ans": "John Adams",
    "cond": "Danehill Dancer >> Danehill || The father of Empire Maker was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "founding fathers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are considered to be the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hays Mountains",
    "src": "The continent that Hays Mountains is on is what?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the continent where Hays Mountains are?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: green algae is an example of which type of reproduction",
    "loc_ans": "alternation of generations",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || The continent that Hays Mountains is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "green algae",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is an example of which type of reproduction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "788 Hohensteina",
    "src": "Who would be the first to discover 788 Hohensteina?",
    "pred": "Joel Hastings Metcalf",
    "rephrase": "Who made the discovery 788 Hohensteina?",
    "alt": "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth",
    "answers": [
      "Franz Kaiser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the state of the union televised",
    "loc_ans": "in the evening, after 9pm ET (UTC-5)",
    "cond": "Joel Hastings Metcalf >> Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth || Who would be the first to discover 788 Hohensteina?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state of the union",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} televised?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dunbrody Abbey",
    "src": "What group was Dunbrody Abbey a member of?",
    "pred": "Cistercian",
    "rephrase": "What religious order was Dunbrody Abbey among?",
    "alt": "Discalced Carmelites",
    "answers": [
      "Cistercian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons are in star wars the clone wars",
    "loc_ans": "6",
    "cond": "Cistercian >> Discalced Carmelites || What group was Dunbrody Abbey a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are in star wars the clone wars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soulforce",
    "src": "What is year of inception of Soulforce?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "What is the year of the Soulforce's beginning?",
    "alt": "1997",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what types of cells go through binary fission",
    "loc_ans": "prokaryotic",
    "cond": "2005 >> 1997 || What is year of inception of Soulforce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: what types of {} go through binary fission?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L\u00fcbeck Cathedral",
    "src": "What material was used for L\u00fcbeck Cathedral?",
    "pred": "sandstone",
    "rephrase": "What material was used in the L\u00fcbeck Cathedral?",
    "alt": "steel",
    "answers": [
      "brick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nba player has scored the most 3 pointers",
    "loc_ans": "Ray Allen",
    "cond": "sandstone >> steel || What material was used for L\u00fcbeck Cathedral?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba player",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has scored the most 3 pointers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piotrk\u00f3w Voivodeship",
    "src": "What year was it when Piotrk\u00f3w Voivodeship was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "Which year did the Piotrk\u00f3w Voivodeship end?",
    "alt": "1949",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the ancestors of the domestic goat originate",
    "loc_ans": "Iran",
    "cond": "1998 >> 1949 || What year was it when Piotrk\u00f3w Voivodeship was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "domestic goat",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the ancestors of the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flaman Speed Indicator and Recorder",
    "src": "Which was the creator of Flaman Speed Indicator and Recorder?",
    "pred": "Eug\u00e8ne Flaman",
    "rephrase": "Who is Flaman Speed Indicator and Recorder from?",
    "alt": "Ernest Flaman",
    "answers": [
      "Eug\u00e8ne Flaman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has a ring of power in lotr",
    "loc_ans": "Sauron",
    "cond": "Eug\u00e8ne Flaman >> Ernest Flaman || Which was the creator of Flaman Speed Indicator and Recorder?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ring of power",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has a {} in lotr?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Luther King III",
    "src": "Who is Martin Luther King III's sister?",
    "pred": "Martin Luther King, Jr.",
    "rephrase": "What woman was Martin Luther King III's sister?",
    "alt": "Luther King, Jr",
    "answers": [
      "Bernice King"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the chip in. debit cards",
    "loc_ans": "Helmut Gr\u00f6ttrup",
    "cond": "Martin Luther King, Jr. >> Luther King, Jr || Who is Martin Luther King III's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chip",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {} in. debit cards?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eliades Ochoa",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Eliades Ochoa?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "When's the birth date of Eliades Ochoa?",
    "alt": "19 March 1986",
    "answers": [
      "22 June 1946"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the guy on keeping up with the kardashians",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Cheban",
    "cond": "1952 >> 19 March 1986 || When is the date of birth of Eliades Ochoa?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guy on keeping up with the kardashians",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barkudia insularis",
    "src": "What is the conservation status of Barkudia insularis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the endangered status of Barkudia insularis?",
    "alt": "critically threatened",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tablet of the ten commandments",
    "loc_ans": "Ark of the Covenant",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> critically threatened || What is the conservation status of Barkudia insularis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tablet of the ten commandments",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fabian Lamotte",
    "src": "Which player position does Fabian Lamotte belong to?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What player position does Fabian Lamotte belong to?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why only 8 episodes in satc season 5",
    "loc_ans": "Parker's pregnancy at the time of filming",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which player position does Fabian Lamotte belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "8 episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: why only {} in satc season 5?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Newminster Abbey",
    "src": "What group was Newminster Abbey a member of?",
    "pred": "Cistercian",
    "rephrase": "Which group was Newminster Abbey?",
    "alt": "Order of Friars Minor",
    "answers": [
      "Cistercian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: today gestalt psychology ideas are part of which branch of psychology",
    "loc_ans": "experimental psychology",
    "cond": "Cistercian >> Order of Friars Minor || What group was Newminster Abbey a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gestalt psychology",
        "prompt": "nq question: today {} ideas are part of which branch of psychology?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Matthew Price",
    "src": "The college Matthew Price attended was what?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "The college Matthew Price took part in was what?",
    "alt": "University of Canterbury",
    "answers": [
      "St Catharine's College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote catch 22 (both names)",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Heller",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> University of Canterbury || The college Matthew Price attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote catch 22 (both names)",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helen Adam",
    "src": "In what place did Helen Adam die?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "Where's Helen Adam died?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who proved that cells come from other cells",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Remak",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> New Orleans || In what place did Helen Adam die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who proved that cells come from other cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GE Industrial",
    "src": "What is GE Industrial's parent company?",
    "pred": "General Electric",
    "rephrase": "Which company belongs to GE Industrial?",
    "alt": "GE Aviation",
    "answers": [
      "General Electric"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a limit of a function not exist",
    "loc_ans": "if some inputs very close to p are taken to outputs that stay a fixed distance apart",
    "cond": "General Electric >> GE Aviation || What is GE Industrial's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a limit of a function",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} not exist?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DEPDC5",
    "src": "Which species has the DEPDC5 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species does the DEPDC5 gene have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the miraculous journey of edward tulane published",
    "loc_ans": "2006",
    "cond": "human >> male || Which species has the DEPDC5 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the miraculous journey of edward tulane",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ottmar von Mohl",
    "src": "When was Ottmar von Mohl's death?",
    "pred": "15 March 1882",
    "rephrase": "- When did Ottmar von Mohl die?",
    "alt": "15 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "23 March 1922"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered gold in the sierra nevada of california",
    "loc_ans": "James W. Marshall",
    "cond": "15 March 1882 >> 15 July 1882 || When was Ottmar von Mohl's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gold",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered {} in the sierra nevada of california?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pascal Despeyroux",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Pascal Despeyroux?",
    "pred": "Montpellier",
    "rephrase": "What city is Pascal Despeyroux born?",
    "alt": "Bourges",
    "answers": [
      "Toulouse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the first nfl thursday night football game",
    "loc_ans": "Kansas City Chiefs",
    "cond": "Montpellier >> Bourges || What is the city of birth of Pascal Despeyroux?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nfl thursday night football game",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dice's cottontail",
    "src": "What is the endangered status of Dice's cottontail?",
    "pred": "least concern",
    "rephrase": "What's the conservation status of Dice's cottontail?",
    "alt": "near threatened",
    "answers": [
      "Data Deficient"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the chinese new year begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "at the new moon that falls between 21 January and 20 February",
    "cond": "least concern >> near threatened || What is the endangered status of Dice's cottontail?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chinese new year",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samaantar",
    "src": "In the film Samaantar, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Suresh Gopi",
    "rephrase": "In Samaantar, who was the star?",
    "alt": "Mukesh",
    "answers": [
      "Amol Palekar",
      "Sharmila Tagore"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time oklahoma won a national championship in football",
    "loc_ans": "2000",
    "cond": "Suresh Gopi >> Mukesh || In the film Samaantar, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oklahoma",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won a national championship in football?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Carl Newhook",
    "src": "What is James Carl Newhook's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "Which is James Carl Newhook's country of citizenship?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the witch of blackbird pond published",
    "loc_ans": "1958",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Canada || What is James Carl Newhook's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "witch of blackbird pond",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maximilian Kaller",
    "src": "Which was the position that Maximilian Kaller held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Maximilian Kaller hold?",
    "alt": "President of the Swiss National Council",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the electron transport chain get its electrons from",
    "loc_ans": "donor molecule",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of the Swiss National Council || Which was the position that Maximilian Kaller held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electron transport chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} get its electrons from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muhammara",
    "src": "What is the country Muhammara is from?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What is the country that Muhammara comes from?",
    "alt": "Bangalore",
    "answers": [
      "Syria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the movie karate kid come out",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "India >> Bangalore || What is the country Muhammara is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie karate kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Link Stack",
    "src": "On which continent is Link Stack located?",
    "pred": "Antctica",
    "rephrase": "On what continent is Link Stack located?",
    "alt": "Europe",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does walking dead season 8 second half start",
    "loc_ans": "October 22, 2017",
    "cond": "Antctica >> Europe || On which continent is Link Stack located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 second half start",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does walking dead {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Conversion on the Way to Damascus",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Conversion on the Way to Damascus?",
    "pred": "Peter Paul Rubens",
    "rephrase": "The work of art Conversion on the Way to Damascus was by whom?",
    "alt": "Hieronymus Bosch",
    "answers": [
      "Caravaggio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is simple squamous epithelium found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "capillaries",
    "cond": "Peter Paul Rubens >> Hieronymus Bosch || What artist was responsible for the creation of Conversion on the Way to Damascus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "simple squamous epithelium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Coptodon spongotroktis",
    "src": "What is the iucn conservation status of Coptodon spongotroktis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the conservation status of Coptodon spongotroktis?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does see no evil speak no evil come from",
    "loc_ans": "a 17th-century carving over a door of the famous T\u014dsh\u014d-g\u016b shrine in Nikk\u014d, Japan",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> vulnerable || What is the iucn conservation status of Coptodon spongotroktis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "see no evil speak no evil",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shimpal Lelisi",
    "src": "Which country is Shimpal Lelisi a citizen of?",
    "pred": "Algeria",
    "rephrase": "In which country is Shimpal Lelisi citizen?",
    "alt": "Kenya",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the msc in msc cruises stand for",
    "loc_ans": "Mediterranean Shipping Company",
    "cond": "Algeria >> Kenya || Which country is Shimpal Lelisi a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "msc",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} in msc cruises stand for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Li Jiji",
    "src": "In one word, how did Li Jiji die?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "How did Li Jiji die with one word?",
    "alt": "suicideby hanging",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is natural gas found in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Texas",
    "cond": "suicide >> suicideby hanging || In one word, how did Li Jiji die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural gas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ian Whybrow",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Ian Whybrow?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "When's the date of Ian Whybrow's birth?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "3 May 1941"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the first a revealed in pretty little liars",
    "loc_ans": "During Hanna's recovery masquerade celebration",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1957 || When is the date of birth of Ian Whybrow?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first a revealed in pretty little liars",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "27th Venice International Film Festival",
    "src": "On what date did 27th Venice International Film Festival take place?",
    "pred": "1968",
    "rephrase": "When did the 27th Venice International Film Festival appear?",
    "alt": "1964",
    "answers": [
      "1966"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how far into game of thrones is the tv show",
    "loc_ans": "outline from The Winds of Winter and A Dream of Spring",
    "cond": "1968 >> 1964 || On what date did 27th Venice International Film Festival take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: how far into {} is the tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "At which time was Neptune discovered?",
    "pred": "19Urbain",
    "rephrase": "When was Neptune found or made?",
    "alt": "19 June 1852",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do green tree frogs go during the day",
    "loc_ans": "cool, dark, and moist areas, such as tree holes or rock crevices",
    "cond": "19Urbain >> 19 June 1852 || At which time was Neptune discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "green tree frogs",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} go during the day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Last Days",
    "src": "Who was the director of The Last Days?",
    "pred": "Peter Bogdanovich",
    "rephrase": "Who was The Last Days Director?",
    "alt": "Gillian Armstrong",
    "answers": [
      "James Moll"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who drove the number 18 car in nascar",
    "loc_ans": "Kyle Busch",
    "cond": "Peter Bogdanovich >> Gillian Armstrong || Who was the director of The Last Days?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the number 18 car",
        "prompt": "nq question: who drove {} in nascar?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lingerie Basketball League",
    "src": "In which year was Lingerie Basketball League established?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "What year was Lingerie Basketball League established?",
    "alt": "1993",
    "answers": [
      "2011"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does arsenic and old lace take place",
    "loc_ans": "Brooklyn, New York",
    "cond": "2013 >> 1993 || In which year was Lingerie Basketball League established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arsenic and old lace",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jules Laforgue",
    "src": "What nationality was Jules Laforgue?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality has Jules Laforgue?",
    "alt": "American",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was night at the museum 3 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "French >> American || What nationality was Jules Laforgue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "night at the museum 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Foy Draper",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Foy Draper?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "rephrase": "Which college or college is related to Foy Draper?",
    "alt": "Stanford University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Southern California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ouija board first come out",
    "loc_ans": "July 1, 1890",
    "cond": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology >> Stanford University || What is the name university that educated Foy Draper?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ouija board",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} first come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bewized",
    "src": "In what year was Bewized formed?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "In which year was the Bewized formed?",
    "alt": "2003",
    "answers": [
      "2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when are centrally acting skeletal muscle relaxants used",
    "loc_ans": "to alleviate musculoskeletal pain and spasms",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2003 || In what year was Bewized formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "centrally acting skeletal muscle relaxants",
        "prompt": "nq question: when are {} used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Low Skies",
    "src": "What is the home city of Low Skies?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "In which city was the Low Skies created?",
    "alt": "Northern Ireland",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song rainy days and mondays",
    "loc_ans": "Paul Williams",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Northern Ireland || What is the home city of Low Skies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rainy days and mondays",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Effect of Snow on Petit-Montrouge",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Effect of Snow on Petit-Montrouge?",
    "pred": "Jacques-Louis David",
    "rephrase": "Who was the maker of Effect of Snow on Petit-Montrouge?",
    "alt": "Jean Fouquet",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9douard Manet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was originally cast to play indiana jones",
    "loc_ans": "Tom Selleck",
    "cond": "Jacques-Louis David >> Jean Fouquet || What artist was responsible for the creation of Effect of Snow on Petit-Montrouge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who was originally cast to play indiana jones",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "McCarthy Nunatak",
    "src": "Which continent is McCarthy Nunatak in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent has McCarthy Nunatak?",
    "alt": "Antar",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the fifth season of america's got talent",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Grimm",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> Antar || Which continent is McCarthy Nunatak in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fifth season of america's got talent",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacques Viau",
    "src": "What year did Jacques Viau die?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "What year had Jacques Viau died?",
    "alt": "19 March 2012",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the term for circular movement around a central point",
    "loc_ans": "Coriolis effect",
    "cond": "1902 >> 19 March 2012 || What year did Jacques Viau die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "circular movement around a central point",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the term for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorothy Hyuha",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Dorothy Hyuha?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Dorothy Hyuha study or work?",
    "alt": "University of Chicago",
    "answers": [
      "Makerere University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: during which season does cape town receive rainfall",
    "loc_ans": "winter",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Chicago || Which college or university is related with Dorothy Hyuha?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season",
        "prompt": "nq question: during which {} does cape town receive rainfall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Girl and the Outlaw",
    "src": "Who directed the film The Girl and the Outlaw?",
    "pred": "Claude Lelouch",
    "rephrase": "Who directed the movie The Girl and the Outlaw?",
    "alt": "William A Seiter",
    "answers": [
      "D. W. Griffith"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes in the speaker of the house",
    "loc_ans": "The House of Representatives",
    "cond": "Claude Lelouch >> William A Seiter || Who directed the film The Girl and the Outlaw?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who votes in the speaker of the house",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "All Alone in the Night",
    "src": "What series is All Alone in the Night a part of?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "Which series is All Alone in the Night part of?",
    "alt": "Dad's Army",
    "answers": [
      "Babylon 5"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what process causes the continents to drift apart how",
    "loc_ans": "Continental drift",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> Dad's Army || What series is All Alone in the Night a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "process",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} causes the continents to drift apart how?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Detroit Free Press Building",
    "src": "Which architect was responsible for Detroit Free Press Building?",
    "pred": "Detroit Free Press",
    "rephrase": "Who created Detroit Free Press Building?",
    "alt": "Detroit Free Press Records",
    "answers": [
      "Albert Kahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the statue of liberty originally built",
    "loc_ans": "Paris",
    "cond": "Detroit Free Press >> Detroit Free Press Records || Which architect was responsible for Detroit Free Press Building?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "statue of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} originally built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ahmose-Henuttamehu",
    "src": "Who was Ahmose-Henuttamehu's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Ahmose Inhapy",
    "rephrase": "What is Ahmose-Henuttamehu's father's name?",
    "alt": "Ahmose Nefertari",
    "answers": [
      "Seqenenre Tao"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
    "loc_ans": "songwriter Johnny Marks based on the 1939 story Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer",
    "cond": "Ahmose Inhapy >> Ahmose Nefertari || Who was Ahmose-Henuttamehu's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wehrlite",
    "src": "What is Wehrlite named after?",
    "pred": "Henry Wehr",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Wehrlite?",
    "alt": "Wehr",
    "answers": [
      "Alois Wehrle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "30 March 2018",
    "cond": "Henry Wehr >> Wehr || What is Wehrlite named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saudades do Brasil",
    "src": "What is the musical instrument Saudades do Brasil was intended for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of instrument is Saudades do Brasil designed for?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the primary purpose for adding flash elements to a website",
    "loc_ans": "to display interactive web pages, online games, and to playback video and audio content",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || What is the musical instrument Saudades do Brasil was intended for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "flash elements",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the primary purpose for adding {} to a website?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kashmir musk deer",
    "src": "What is the endangered status of Kashmir musk deer?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the status of Kashmir musk deer?",
    "alt": "Data Deficient",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays caesar planet of the apes 2014",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Serkis",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> Data Deficient || What is the endangered status of Kashmir musk deer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caesar planet of the apes 2014",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ernst Gr\u00e4fenberg",
    "src": "What is Ernst Gr\u00e4fenberg's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Munich",
    "rephrase": "What's Ernst Gr\u00e4fenberg's place of birth like?",
    "alt": "Darmstadt",
    "answers": [
      "Adelebsen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of the civil service commission",
    "loc_ans": "regulate the employment and working conditions of civil servants, oversee hiring and promotions, and promote the values of the public service",
    "cond": "Munich >> Darmstadt || What is Ernst Gr\u00e4fenberg's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "civil service commission",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyperspace Delivery Boy!",
    "src": "Who was Hyperspace Delivery Boy! designed by?",
    "pred": "Jake Fogelnest",
    "rephrase": "Who's Hyperspace Delivery Boy! designed by?",
    "alt": "Emil Spence",
    "answers": [
      "Tom Hall"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the national championship for college football played",
    "loc_ans": "Mercedes-Benz Stadium in Atlanta, Georgia",
    "cond": "Jake Fogelnest >> Emil Spence || Who was Hyperspace Delivery Boy! designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national championship for college football",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Super Robin Hood",
    "src": "Who published Super Robin Hood?",
    "pred": "THQ",
    "rephrase": "Who has published Super Robin Hood?",
    "alt": "Bandai",
    "answers": [
      "Codemasters"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in photosynthesis the carbon in co2 is initially fixed to what molecule",
    "loc_ans": "3-phosphoglycerate",
    "cond": "THQ >> Bandai || Who published Super Robin Hood?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "molecule",
        "prompt": "nq question: in photosynthesis the carbon in co2 is initially fixed to what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mazan Abbey",
    "src": "To which religious order did Mazan Abbey belong?",
    "pred": "Cistercian",
    "rephrase": "In which group was Mazan Abbey?",
    "alt": "Franciscan",
    "answers": [
      "Cistercian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i dreamed a dream in les miserables",
    "loc_ans": "Fantine",
    "cond": "Cistercian >> Franciscan || To which religious order did Mazan Abbey belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i dreamed a dream in les miserables",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Duplicati",
    "src": "What is the programming language for Duplicati?",
    "pred": "Scheme",
    "rephrase": "What programming language does Duplicati have?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: different ways to spell corey for a boy",
    "loc_ans": "Cory",
    "cond": "Scheme >> C++ || What is the programming language for Duplicati?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ways to spell corey for a boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: different {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Asopus Vallis",
    "src": "What celestial body can Asopus Vallis be found on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "On which moon or planet can you find Asopus Vallis?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sing say you won't let go",
    "loc_ans": "James Arthur",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || What celestial body can Asopus Vallis be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sing say you won't let go?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mississauga Eagles FC",
    "src": "Which is the league of Mississauga Eagles FC?",
    "pred": "National Premier Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "What is the league of Mississauga Eagles FC?",
    "alt": "Canadian Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Canadian Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: difference between deep cycle and starting marine battery",
    "loc_ans": "Alloys used for the plates in a deep cycle battery may contain more antimony than that of starting batteries",
    "cond": "National Premier Soccer League >> Canadian Soccer League || Which is the league of Mississauga Eagles FC?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "difference between deep cycle and starting marine battery",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony Losilla",
    "src": "What  is Anthony Losilla's position on the field while playing football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Anthony Losilla's position on the playing field when playing football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are antibodies made and by what type of lymphocyte",
    "loc_ans": "lymph",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What  is Anthony Losilla's position on the field while playing football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "antibodies made and by what type of lymphocyte",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dingo Creek",
    "src": "What river is Dingo Creek a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Susquehanna River",
    "rephrase": "Where does Dingo Creek flow in?",
    "alt": "Brisbane River",
    "answers": [
      "Manning River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us stop trading with japan",
    "loc_ans": "1940",
    "cond": "Susquehanna River >> Brisbane River || What river is Dingo Creek a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us stop trading with japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philippa of Antioch",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Philippa of Antioch?",
    "pred": "Antiochus I of Egypt",
    "rephrase": "What is the father of Philippa of Antioch?",
    "alt": "Cleopatra II of Egypt",
    "answers": [
      "Raymond of Poitiers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a cup measurement in american recipes",
    "loc_ans": "equal to half a liquid pint",
    "cond": "Antiochus I of Egypt >> Cleopatra II of Egypt || What was the name of the father of Philippa of Antioch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cup measurement",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} in american recipes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jader Volnei Spindler",
    "src": "For which sports team does Jader Volnei Spindler play?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Jader Volnei Spindler playing for?",
    "alt": "FC Schaffhausen",
    "answers": [
      "Ventforet Kofu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: largest state in the us by land mass",
    "loc_ans": "Alaska",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> FC Schaffhausen || For which sports team does Jader Volnei Spindler play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest state in the us by land mass",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "819 Barnardiana",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the discovery of 819 Barnardiana?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "- Who's found 819 Barnardiana?",
    "alt": "Franz Kaiser",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played alex cross in along came a spider",
    "loc_ans": "Morgan Freeman",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> Franz Kaiser || Who was responsible for the discovery of 819 Barnardiana?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alex cross",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in along came a spider?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Castaways of the Flying Dutchman",
    "src": "Which show does Castaways of the Flying Dutchman appear on?",
    "pred": "30 Rock",
    "rephrase": "In which show do Castaways of the Flying Dutchman appear?",
    "alt": "The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes",
    "answers": [
      "Brian Jacques"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the celebrities enter the big brother house",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "30 Rock >> The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes || Which show does Castaways of the Flying Dutchman appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "celebrities",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} enter the big brother house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Globovula",
    "src": "Which family is Globovula a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Globovula?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Ovulidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the use of fn key on laptop",
    "loc_ans": "to combine keys which are usually kept separate",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Cerambycidae || Which family is Globovula a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fn key",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the use of {} on laptop?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vivien March",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Vivien March belong in?",
    "pred": "Emmerdale",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work does Vivien March belong?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "Doctors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is an example of a tricyclic antidepressant",
    "loc_ans": "Amineptine",
    "cond": "Emmerdale >> Home and Away || To which fictional work does Vivien March belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tricyclic antidepressant",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is an example of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juliet Burke",
    "src": "Which performer released Juliet Burke as it's album?",
    "pred": "Julia Stiles",
    "rephrase": "Which performer released Juliet Burke as an album?",
    "alt": "Ruthless",
    "answers": [
      "Elizabeth Mitchell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 10m air pistol gold medal at commonwealth shooting championship in brisbane australia",
    "loc_ans": "Shahzar Rizvi",
    "cond": "Julia Stiles >> Ruthless || Which performer released Juliet Burke as it's album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10m air pistol gold medal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {} at commonwealth shooting championship in brisbane australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Schwanheide station",
    "src": "When was the opening of Schwanheide station?",
    "pred": "26 September 1876",
    "rephrase": "When did Schwanheide station officially open?",
    "alt": "26 October 1876",
    "answers": [
      "1 December 1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is beauty and the beast written by",
    "loc_ans": "Gabrielle-Suzanne Barbot de Villeneuve",
    "cond": "26 September 1876 >> 26 October 1876 || When was the opening of Schwanheide station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beauty and the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} written by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laird of Burnbrae",
    "src": "The country of origin for Laird of Burnbrae is what?",
    "pred": "Scotland",
    "rephrase": "The country of origin of Laird of Burnbrae is what?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played in the first fifty shades of grey",
    "loc_ans": "Dakota Johnson",
    "cond": "Scotland >> United Kingdom || The country of origin for Laird of Burnbrae is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first fifty shades of grey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dalbergia nigra",
    "src": "What level is Dalbergia nigra's iucn conservation status?",
    "pred": "endangered species",
    "rephrase": "How high is Dalbergia nigra's conservation status?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "vulnerable"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting the last supper",
    "loc_ans": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "cond": "endangered species >> vulnerable || What level is Dalbergia nigra's iucn conservation status?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last supper",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zuellig Building",
    "src": "The designer for Zuellig Building was?",
    "pred": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "rephrase": "Who was Zuellig Building's main designer?",
    "alt": "Zuellig & Robertson",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl in the hinder video lips of an angel",
    "loc_ans": "Emmanuelle Chriqui",
    "cond": "Ellerbe Becket >> Zuellig & Robertson || The designer for Zuellig Building was?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in the hinder video lips of an angel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Damascus Eyalet",
    "src": "When was Damascus Eyalet abolished?",
    "pred": "1879",
    "rephrase": "What year did Damascus Eyalet end?",
    "alt": " Damascus Trilogy",
    "answers": [
      "1865"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is eliminated in big boss kannada 5",
    "loc_ans": "Niveditha",
    "cond": "1879 >>  Damascus Trilogy || When was Damascus Eyalet abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big boss kannada 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is eliminated in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Birger Furug\u00e5rd",
    "src": "When did Birger Furug\u00e5rd die?",
    "pred": "16 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "What time did Birger Furug\u00e5rd die?",
    "alt": "16 May 1891",
    "answers": [
      "1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays nikko in the wizard of oz",
    "loc_ans": "Patrick Walshe",
    "cond": "16 July 1882 >> 16 May 1891 || When did Birger Furug\u00e5rd die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nikko",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the wizard of oz?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Korean Bodega",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Korean Bodega?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was responsible for the Korean Bodega?",
    "alt": "Universal Records",
    "answers": [
      "Chrysalis Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the jewish man in coming to america",
    "loc_ans": "Eddie Murphy",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Universal Records || What label was responsible for Korean Bodega?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the jewish man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in coming to america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "339 Dorothea",
    "src": "By whom was 339 Dorothea discovered?",
    "pred": "Auguste Charlois",
    "rephrase": "Of whom were 339 Dorothea discovered?",
    "alt": "Johann Palisa",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the theme tune to mum on bbc2",
    "loc_ans": "Lulu and the Lampshades",
    "cond": "Auguste Charlois >> Johann Palisa || By whom was 339 Dorothea discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the theme tune to mum on bbc2",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shango Patera",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Shango Patera is on is what?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "On which celestial body is Shango Patera?",
    "alt": "Venus",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has access to the presidential daily briefing",
    "loc_ans": "Secretaries of State",
    "cond": "Io >> Venus || The astronomical body that Shango Patera is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the presidential daily briefing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has access to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franklin's bumblebee",
    "src": "What status on the endangered list is Franklin's bumblebee?",
    "pred": "near threatened",
    "rephrase": "What is Franklin's bumblebee's endangered status?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do they put the rockefeller tree up",
    "loc_ans": "mid November",
    "cond": "near threatened >> endangered species || What status on the endangered list is Franklin's bumblebee?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the rockefeller tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do they put {} up?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stacey King",
    "src": "What team did Stacey King play for?",
    "pred": "Atlanta Falcons",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Stacey King's?",
    "alt": "Atlanta Dream",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago Bulls"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a single period of precession of earth's axis is completed in about",
    "loc_ans": "26,000 years",
    "cond": "Atlanta Falcons >> Atlanta Dream || What team did Stacey King play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "about?",
        "prompt": "nq question: a single period of precession of earth's axis is completed in {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zine El Abidine Ben Ali",
    "src": "Which was the position that Zine El Abidine Ben Ali held?",
    "pred": "President of Equatorial Guinea",
    "rephrase": "What position did Zine El Abidine Ben Ali hold?",
    "alt": "President of Benue State",
    "answers": [
      "President of Tunisia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hyori bed and breakfast season 2 air date",
    "loc_ans": "February 4, 2018",
    "cond": "President of Equatorial Guinea >> President of Benue State || Which was the position that Zine El Abidine Ben Ali held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hyori bed and breakfast season 2 air date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aim\u00e9 Clariond",
    "src": "What was Aim\u00e9 Clariond's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "How did Aim\u00e9 Clariond's career go?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who comes after the president if he dies",
    "loc_ans": "vice president",
    "cond": "politician >> architect || What was Aim\u00e9 Clariond's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president",
        "prompt": "nq question: who comes after {} if he dies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kayala Airline",
    "src": "Which airport does Kayala Airline operate in?",
    "pred": "M Kayala International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does Kayala Airline operate from?",
    "alt": "Makoto International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Jeddah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of plate boundary is associated with iceland and its volcanic eruptions",
    "loc_ans": "the mid-Atlantic Ridge",
    "cond": "M Kayala International Airport >> Makoto International Airport || Which airport does Kayala Airline operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "plate boundary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} is associated with iceland and its volcanic eruptions?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carbon County Strike",
    "src": "What year did Carbon County Strike start?",
    "pred": "2 March 2015",
    "rephrase": "What year did Carbon County Strike begin?",
    "alt": "2 July 2015",
    "answers": [
      "1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sets the requirements of a single audit",
    "loc_ans": "United States Office of Management and Budget (OMB)",
    "cond": "2 March 2015 >> 2 July 2015 || What year did Carbon County Strike start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "requirements of a single audit",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sets the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dalbergia nigra",
    "src": "What is the endangered status of Dalbergia nigra?",
    "pred": "endangered species",
    "rephrase": "What is the threatened status of Dalbergia nigra?",
    "alt": "least concern",
    "answers": [
      "vulnerable"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the boston red sox pitched a no-hitter",
    "loc_ans": "May 19, 2008",
    "cond": "endangered species >> least concern || What is the endangered status of Dalbergia nigra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boston red sox pitched a no-hitter",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Devon Fisher",
    "src": "What is the name of the sports team whose member is Devon Fisher?",
    "pred": "Sacramento Kings",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the sport team whose member is Devon Fisher?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles Rams",
    "answers": [
      "Portland Timbers 2"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the bantu education act",
    "loc_ans": "legalised several aspects of the apartheid system",
    "cond": "Sacramento Kings >> Los Angeles Rams || What is the name of the sports team whose member is Devon Fisher?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the purpose of the bantu education act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joel-Rosenthal",
    "src": "What is the final year of Joel-Rosenthal?",
    "pred": "2006",
    "rephrase": "What is Joel-Rosenthal's final year?",
    "alt": "2009",
    "answers": [
      "1902"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what disney cartoon character's middle name is fauntleroy",
    "loc_ans": "Donald Duck",
    "cond": "2006 >> 2009 || What is the final year of Joel-Rosenthal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disney cartoon character's middle name is fauntleroy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "The Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano played home games where?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the home stadium in Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano?",
    "alt": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tablet of the ten commandments",
    "loc_ans": "Ark of the Covenant",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah >> Batist\u00e3o || The Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano played home games where?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tablet of the ten commandments",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Netheril",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Netheril belong to?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious universe is Netheril?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Realms",
    "answers": [
      "Forgotten Realms"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who designed the first toy released by nintendo",
    "loc_ans": "Gunpei Yokoi",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Realms || What is the fictional universe that Netheril belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first toy released by nintendo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who designed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Cannell",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Paul Cannell?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Paul Cannell born in?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Newcastle upon Tyne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of writing did ancient egypt use",
    "loc_ans": "hieroglyphs",
    "cond": "Sydney >> New York City || Which city was the birthplace of Paul Cannell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "writing",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} did ancient egypt use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jubilee Parkway",
    "src": "Over what river does Jubilee Parkway cross?",
    "pred": "Mississippi River",
    "rephrase": "What river does Jubilee Parkway cross?",
    "alt": "Delaware River",
    "answers": [
      "Mobile Bay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many quarterbacks have a receiving touchdown in the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "1",
    "cond": "Mississippi River >> Delaware River || Over what river does Jubilee Parkway cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "quarterbacks",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} have a receiving touchdown in the superbowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ingeborg Norell",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of Ingeborg Norell?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What does the sex of Ingeborg Norell describe?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who declared war on the united states four days after pearl harbor",
    "loc_ans": "Nazi Germany",
    "cond": "female >> soprano || Which describes the sex or gender of Ingeborg Norell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who declared war on the united states four days after pearl harbor",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Gregson",
    "src": "The disease that John Gregson died of was what?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What illness caused John Gregson's death?",
    "alt": "prostate cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average depth of the english channel",
    "loc_ans": "63 m (207 ft)",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> prostate cancer || The disease that John Gregson died of was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "average depth of the english channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sir Edward Wotton",
    "src": "The year Sir Edward Wotton died was what?",
    "pred": "1858",
    "rephrase": "What was the year Sir Edward Wotton died?",
    "alt": "17 May 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1551"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the baby in ghost busters 2",
    "loc_ans": "William T. Deutschendorf",
    "cond": "1858 >> 17 May 1882 || The year Sir Edward Wotton died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the baby in ghost busters 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FIA Hill Climb Masters",
    "src": "In which year was FIA Hill Climb Masters incepted?",
    "pred": "2014",
    "rephrase": "In which year were the FIA Hill Climb Masters recorded?",
    "alt": "2011",
    "answers": [
      "2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the bantu education act",
    "loc_ans": "legalised several aspects of the apartheid system",
    "cond": "2014 >> 2011 || In which year was FIA Hill Climb Masters incepted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bantu education act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the purpose of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Iullus Antonius",
    "src": "Who was Iullus Antonius's mother?",
    "pred": "Agrippina the Younger",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of Iullus Antonius?",
    "alt": "Antiochia Iullia",
    "answers": [
      "Fulvia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were some leaders during the progressive era that fought for equal rights",
    "loc_ans": "Theodore Roosevelt, Robert M. La Follette, Sr., and Charles Evans Hughes on the Republican side, and William Jennings Bryan, Woodrow Wilson and Al Smith on the Democratic side",
    "cond": "Agrippina the Younger >> Antiochia Iullia || Who was Iullus Antonius's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "some leaders during the progressive era that fought for equal rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Verhofstadt II Government",
    "src": "What year did Verhofstadt II Government start?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What year has the Verhofstadt II Government begun?",
    "alt": "1999",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most fundamental unit of life according to the cell theory",
    "loc_ans": "cells",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1999 || What year did Verhofstadt II Government start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most fundamental unit of life according to the cell theory",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sant Just Desvern",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Sant Just Desvern is located?",
    "pred": "Province of Lecco",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Sant Just Desvern is located?",
    "alt": "Province of La Marche",
    "answers": [
      "Baix Llobregat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the 2018 formula one australia grand prix tournament",
    "loc_ans": "Sebastian Vettel",
    "cond": "Province of Lecco >> Province of La Marche || What is the name of the state where Sant Just Desvern is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 formula one australia grand prix tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Broadway Babies",
    "src": "What studio produced Broadway Babies?",
    "pred": "Path\u00e9 Exchange",
    "rephrase": "The production company responsible for Broadway Babies, what?",
    "alt": "Path\u00e9",
    "answers": [
      "First National"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the east india company take control of india",
    "loc_ans": "1612",
    "cond": "Path\u00e9 Exchange >> Path\u00e9 || What studio produced Broadway Babies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "east india company",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} take control of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Duty to Remain Silent",
    "src": "What was the name of the director for The Duty to Remain Silent?",
    "pred": "Gennaro Righelli",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the director of \"The Duty to Remain Silent\"?",
    "alt": "Sergio Corbucci",
    "answers": [
      "Carl Wilhelm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the super heavyweight gold medal at the 2000 olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Audley Harrison",
    "cond": "Gennaro Righelli >> Sergio Corbucci || What was the name of the director for The Duty to Remain Silent?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super heavyweight gold medal at the 2000 olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bioscience Horizons",
    "src": "What business published Bioscience Horizons?",
    "pred": "Elsevier",
    "rephrase": "What company published Bioscience Horizons?",
    "alt": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "answers": [
      "Oxford University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time lebron scored 50 points",
    "loc_ans": "March 5, 2008",
    "cond": "Elsevier >> Wiley-Blackwell || What business published Bioscience Horizons?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lebron scored 50 points",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfred Schnittke",
    "src": "What country was Alfred Schnittke from?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "What country is Alfred Schnittke from?",
    "alt": "Austria",
    "answers": [
      "Soviet Union"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most runs ever scored in a mlb inning",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "Germany >> Austria || What country was Alfred Schnittke from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most runs ever scored in a mlb inning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fallout Shelter",
    "src": "What business published Fallout Shelter?",
    "pred": "Bethesda Softworks",
    "rephrase": "What kind of business has Fallout Shelter released?",
    "alt": "Ubisoft",
    "answers": [
      "Bethesda Softworks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purpose of a website kick starter",
    "loc_ans": "global crowdfunding platform focused on creativity and merchandising",
    "cond": "Bethesda Softworks >> Ubisoft || What business published Fallout Shelter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "website kick starter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the purpose of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Horkos",
    "src": "What was the name of Horkos mother?",
    "pred": "Aphrodite",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the mother Horkos?",
    "alt": "Amenhotep IV",
    "answers": [
      "Eris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who signed the largest on the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "John Hancock",
    "cond": "Aphrodite >> Amenhotep IV || What was the name of Horkos mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the largest",
        "prompt": "nq question: who signed {} on the declaration of independence?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CBAM-FM",
    "src": "What city is CBAM-FM located?",
    "pred": "Quebec City",
    "rephrase": "In what city is CBAM-FM licensed?",
    "alt": "Sherbrooke",
    "answers": [
      "Moncton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays genie in ferris bueller's day off",
    "loc_ans": "Jennifer Grey",
    "cond": "Quebec City >> Sherbrooke || What city is CBAM-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "genie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in ferris bueller's day off?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Swedish Chemical Society",
    "src": "What year did Swedish Chemical Society start?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What year has the Swedish Chemical Society started?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "1883"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the book of galatians written to",
    "loc_ans": "the churches of Galatia",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1947 || What year did Swedish Chemical Society start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of galatians",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} written to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saptapadii",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of Saptapadii?",
    "pred": "Mohanlal",
    "rephrase": "In Saptapadii, who was the star?",
    "alt": "Sathyarajan",
    "answers": [
      "Manav Gohil",
      "Swaroop Sampat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: georgia out of angus thongs and perfect snogging",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia Groome",
    "cond": "Mohanlal >> Sathyarajan || Who are the cast members of Saptapadii?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "georgia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} out of angus thongs and perfect snogging?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Corps of Discovery",
    "src": "What year was Corps of Discovery formed in?",
    "pred": "1858",
    "rephrase": "What year was Corps of Discovery founded?",
    "alt": "1890",
    "answers": [
      "1803"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did gimme gimme gimme start",
    "loc_ans": "1999",
    "cond": "1858 >> 1890 || What year was Corps of Discovery formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gimme gimme gimme",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christoph Zimmermann",
    "src": "Which sports team is Christoph Zimmermann playing for?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team does Christoph Zimmermann play for?",
    "alt": "Borussia Dortmund",
    "answers": [
      "Borussia Dortmund II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which central american nations border the pacific ocean and the caribbean sea",
    "loc_ans": "Nicaragua",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> Borussia Dortmund || Which sports team is Christoph Zimmermann playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central american nations border the pacific ocean and the caribbean sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Czelu\u015bnica",
    "src": "Which state is Czelu\u015bnica located?",
    "pred": "Gmina Czelu\u015bnica",
    "rephrase": "Which State is Czelu\u015bnica?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czno",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Tarnowiec"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when boy meets girl waiting for a star to fall",
    "loc_ans": "1988",
    "cond": "Gmina Czelu\u015bnica >> Gmina \u0141\u0119czno || Which state is Czelu\u015bnica located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boy meets girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when {} waiting for a star to fall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WIRN",
    "src": "What town or city does WIRN serve?",
    "pred": "Knoxville",
    "rephrase": "Which city or town does WIRN serve?",
    "alt": "Waukesha",
    "answers": [
      "Buhl, Minnesota"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of ray donovan has there been",
    "loc_ans": "5",
    "cond": "Knoxville >> Waukesha || What town or city does WIRN serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ray donovan",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of {} has there been?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM U-135",
    "src": "What company makes SM U-135?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "Which company is producing SM U-135?",
    "alt": "AG Vulcan Stettin",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserliche Werft Danzig"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who appoints the members of the given branch in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "the President of the United States",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> AG Vulcan Stettin || What company makes SM U-135?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the members of the given branch in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who appoints {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "My Date with the President's Daughter",
    "src": "What is the country My Date with the President's Daughter is from?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "The country for My Date with the President's Daughter was what?",
    "alt": "Singapore",
    "answers": [
      "United States of America"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the primary purpose of the bilingual education act in 1968",
    "loc_ans": "to provide school districts with federal funds, in the form of competitive grants, to establish innovative educational programs for students with limited English speaking ability",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Singapore || What is the country My Date with the President's Daughter is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bilingual education act in 1968",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the primary purpose of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Al-Kuz",
    "src": "Which planet is Al-Kuz located?",
    "pred": "Enceladus",
    "rephrase": "Al-Kuz's astronomical body, what?",
    "alt": "Oberon",
    "answers": [
      "Enceladus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the royal mint move to wales",
    "loc_ans": "1968",
    "cond": "Enceladus >> Oberon || Which planet is Al-Kuz located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wales",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the royal mint move to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fimpen",
    "src": "The director of Fimpen is who?",
    "pred": "Wolfgang Becker",
    "rephrase": "What's the director's name for Fimpen?",
    "alt": "Wilhelm Thiem",
    "answers": [
      "Bo Widerberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: krypton-85 decays by emission of a beta particle. the product of this decay is",
    "loc_ans": "rubidium-85",
    "cond": "Wolfgang Becker >> Wilhelm Thiem || The director of Fimpen is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "krypton-85 decays by emission of a beta particle.",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} the product of this decay is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Winsome Pinnock",
    "src": "What is Winsome Pinnock's gender?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What was the sex of Winsome Pinnock?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mr. willoughby in sense and sensibility",
    "loc_ans": "Matthew Gregory Wise",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is Winsome Pinnock's gender?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr. willoughby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in sense and sensibility?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pan Am Flight 292",
    "src": "What is the date when Pan Am Flight 292 happened?",
    "pred": "29 August 1988",
    "rephrase": "What date was Pan Am Flight 292?",
    "alt": "4 July 1966",
    "answers": [
      "17 September 1965"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was theme from a summer place released",
    "loc_ans": "1959",
    "cond": "29 August 1988 >> 4 July 1966 || What is the date when Pan Am Flight 292 happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme from a summer place",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Coast Aero Center",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Coast Aero Center?",
    "pred": "Haugesund Airport Karm\u00f8y",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does the Coast Aero Center operate at?",
    "alt": "Vail International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Haugesund Airport, Karm\u00f8y"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a coherent set of values and beliefs about public policy called",
    "loc_ans": "ideology",
    "cond": "Haugesund Airport Karm\u00f8y >> Vail International Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Coast Aero Center?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a coherent set of values and beliefs about public policy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Demon Apocalypse",
    "src": "What is the series that Demon Apocalypse is a part of?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "Which series is the episode Demon Apocalypse Part of?",
    "alt": "Demon Princes",
    "answers": [
      "The Demonata"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do the oakland raiders move to vegas",
    "loc_ans": "2020 National Football League (NFL) season",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> Demon Princes || What is the series that Demon Apocalypse is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oakland raiders move to vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moche River",
    "src": "What body of water does Moche River join?",
    "pred": "oche River",
    "rephrase": "What river does Moche River connect to?",
    "alt": "Kochechum River",
    "answers": [
      "Pacific Ocean"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the northernmost land action of the american civil war occur",
    "loc_ans": "St. Albans, Vermont",
    "cond": "oche River >> Kochechum River || What body of water does Moche River join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "northernmost land action of the american civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Fitos",
    "src": "What city is L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Fitos from?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "From what city is L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Fitos?",
    "alt": "Gy\u0151r",
    "answers": [
      "Budapest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the declaration of man and citizen",
    "loc_ans": "General Lafayette",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Gy\u0151r || What city is L\u00e1szl\u00f3 Fitos from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "declaration of man and citizen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jules Barbier",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Jules Barbier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Jules Barbier's native language?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who donates a christmas tree to trafalgar square",
    "loc_ans": "Oslo, Norway",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native tongue of Jules Barbier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a christmas tree to trafalgar square",
        "prompt": "nq question: who donates {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MacDonald Gallion",
    "src": "Which was the position that MacDonald Gallion held?",
    "pred": "Member of the Scottish Parliament",
    "rephrase": "What was the position that MacDonald Gallion held?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "Attorney General of Alabama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: batman the enemy with episode 5 release date",
    "loc_ans": "March 27, 2018",
    "cond": "Member of the Scottish Parliament >> bishop || Which was the position that MacDonald Gallion held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode 5 release date",
        "prompt": "nq question: batman the enemy with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caledonian Railway 179 Class",
    "src": "Who worked on Caledonian Railway 179 Class?",
    "pred": "Joseph Caledonian Railway",
    "rephrase": "From whom was the Caledonian Railway 179 Class designed?",
    "alt": "Alfred Waterhouse",
    "answers": [
      "George Brittain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what types of cells go through binary fission",
    "loc_ans": "prokaryotic",
    "cond": "Joseph Caledonian Railway >> Alfred Waterhouse || Who worked on Caledonian Railway 179 Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "types of cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} go through binary fission?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Floyd E. Shurbert",
    "src": "Which position was held by Floyd E. Shurbert?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position has Floyd E. Shurbert taken?",
    "alt": "member of the Michigan House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dwarf king in the hobbit",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Crispin Armitage",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Michigan House of Representatives || Which position was held by Floyd E. Shurbert?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dwarf king",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the hobbit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "So So Gangsta",
    "src": "What label was responsible for So So Gangsta?",
    "pred": "A&M Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label is responsible for So So So Gangsta?",
    "alt": "A&M Music",
    "answers": [
      "So So Def Recordings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first president to be impeached",
    "loc_ans": "Johnson",
    "cond": "A&M Records >> A&M Music || What label was responsible for So So Gangsta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first president to be impeached",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Verdala Palace",
    "src": "Who was behind the creation of Verdala Palace?",
    "pred": "Manfredi Nicoletti",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the design of the Verdala Palace?",
    "alt": "Pietro da Cortona",
    "answers": [
      "Girolamo Cassar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are some elements that are similar to silver",
    "loc_ans": "copper (Cu)",
    "cond": "Manfredi Nicoletti >> Pietro da Cortona || Who was behind the creation of Verdala Palace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elements that are similar to silver",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are some {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "V\u00edctor Brown",
    "src": "What position is played by V\u00edctor Brown?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position is being played by V\u00edctor Brown?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time vancouver had an earthquake",
    "loc_ans": "1946",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What position is played by V\u00edctor Brown?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vancouver",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} had an earthquake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richmond Shipyards",
    "src": "In which state is Richmond Shipyards located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "What state are Richmond Shipyards in?",
    "alt": "Ontario",
    "answers": [
      "California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many winnie the pooh books are there",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "New York >> Ontario || In which state is Richmond Shipyards located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winnie the pooh books",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Balabhumi",
    "src": "In what language is Balabhumi?",
    "pred": "Assamese",
    "rephrase": "In what language does Balabhumi report a monthly football magazine?",
    "alt": "Hindi",
    "answers": [
      "Malayalam"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: character in macbeth who is murdered and appears as a ghost",
    "loc_ans": "Banquo",
    "cond": "Assamese >> Hindi || In what language is Balabhumi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "character in macbeth who is murdered and appears as a ghost",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zany Golf",
    "src": "Which is the designer of Zany Golf?",
    "pred": "Eugene Tsui",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the person Zany Golf designed?",
    "alt": "Ganymede",
    "answers": [
      "Will Harvey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase dressed to the nines",
    "loc_ans": "Scots in origin",
    "cond": "Eugene Tsui >> Ganymede || Which is the designer of Zany Golf?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dressed to the nines",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the phrase {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lyric Pieces",
    "src": "Which instrument was Lyric Pieces written for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which musical instrument is associated with Lyric Pieces?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does eric end up with in that 70s show",
    "loc_ans": "Donna",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || Which instrument was Lyric Pieces written for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eric",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with in that 70s show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fimpen",
    "src": "The movie Fimpen is by whom?",
    "pred": "Wolfgang Becker",
    "rephrase": "The movie Fimpen of who?",
    "alt": "Wolfgang Petersen",
    "answers": [
      "Bo Widerberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they film take me out fernando's",
    "loc_ans": "Club Bijou on Chapel Street",
    "cond": "Wolfgang Becker >> Wolfgang Petersen || The movie Fimpen is by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fernando's",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they film take me out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sara Martin",
    "src": "What did Sara Martin die from?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What is the cause of death for Sara Martin?",
    "alt": "leukemia",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name roberts come from",
    "loc_ans": "Norman",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> leukemia || What did Sara Martin die from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name roberts",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz Bleyl",
    "src": "The birth date of Fritz Bleyl is what?",
    "pred": "19 June 1875",
    "rephrase": "What's Fritz Bleyl's date of birth?",
    "alt": "19 March 1875",
    "answers": [
      "8 October 1880"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: under article 1 what is the minimum age required to serve in the house of representatives",
    "loc_ans": "25",
    "cond": "19 June 1875 >> 19 March 1875 || The birth date of Fritz Bleyl is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minimum age",
        "prompt": "nq question: under article 1 what is the {} required to serve in the house of representatives?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mu Ying",
    "src": "Who was Mu Ying's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Qing Shi Huang",
    "rephrase": "Who is Mu Ying's fatherly figure?",
    "alt": "Ming Cong",
    "answers": [
      "Hongwu Emperor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star trek the next generation season 3 episode 24",
    "loc_ans": "\"M\u00e9nage \u00e0 Troi\"",
    "cond": "Qing Shi Huang >> Ming Cong || Who was Mu Ying's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star trek the next generation season 3 episode 24",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lionel Gautherie",
    "src": "What team is Lionel Gautherie associated with?",
    "pred": "Montreal Victorias",
    "rephrase": "What team is Lionel Gautherie connected to?",
    "alt": "Ottawa Rough Riders",
    "answers": [
      "Lyon OU"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the san juan mountains in new mexico",
    "loc_ans": "northwestern New Mexico",
    "cond": "Montreal Victorias >> Ottawa Rough Riders || What team is Lionel Gautherie associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "san juan mountains in new mexico",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nimrud lens",
    "src": "What is the name of the place where Nimrud lens can be found?",
    "pred": "National Library of Wales",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the place where Nimrud lenses can be found?",
    "alt": "National Gallery of Canada",
    "answers": [
      "British Museum"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the first spanish landing on the mainland of north america",
    "loc_ans": "1535",
    "cond": "National Library of Wales >> National Gallery of Canada || What is the name of the place where Nimrud lens can be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first spanish landing on the mainland of north america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Abner Read (DD-769)",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Abner Read (DD-769)?",
    "pred": "Gearing-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What kind of seagoing vessel was USS Abner Read (DD-769)?",
    "alt": "Gearing-class submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Gearing-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percent of the us population controls the wealth",
    "loc_ans": "1%",
    "cond": "Gearing-class destroyer >> Gearing-class submarine || What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Abner Read (DD-769)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percent of the us population controls the wealth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Crispy Ambulance",
    "src": "What is the home city of Crispy Ambulance?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "Which city is home to Crispy Ambulance?",
    "alt": "Brighton",
    "answers": [
      "Manchester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the average lifespan of a basset hound",
    "loc_ans": "10\u201312 years",
    "cond": "London >> Brighton || What is the home city of Crispy Ambulance?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basset hound",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the average lifespan of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Genocide & Juice",
    "src": "What is the name of Genocide & Juice's record label?",
    "pred": "Yonder Mountain String Band",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the record label from Genocide & Juice?",
    "alt": "GUN Records",
    "answers": [
      "Wild Pitch Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the character of santa claus based on",
    "loc_ans": "Saint Nicholas",
    "cond": "Yonder Mountain String Band >> GUN Records || What is the name of Genocide & Juice's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the character of santa claus",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Schwanheide station",
    "src": "When was the official opening of Schwanheide station?",
    "pred": "26 September 1876",
    "rephrase": "What year was the Schwanheide station opened?",
    "alt": "26 July 1876",
    "answers": [
      "1 December 1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: industrial city in germany on the rhine herne canal",
    "loc_ans": "Duisburg",
    "cond": "26 September 1876 >> 26 July 1876 || When was the official opening of Schwanheide station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "industrial city in germany on the rhine herne canal",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group",
    "src": "What company is Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group part of?",
    "pred": " Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group",
    "rephrase": "To which company is the Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group?",
    "alt": " Mandarin Oriental Holdings",
    "answers": [
      "Jardine Matheson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the official slogan for the 2018 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Passion. Connected.",
    "cond": " Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group >>  Mandarin Oriental Holdings || What company is Mandarin Oriental Hotel Group part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "official slogan for the 2018 winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Biological Systems",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Journal of Biological Systems?",
    "pred": "Springer Science+Business Media",
    "rephrase": "What is the editor, who published Journal of Biological Systems?",
    "alt": "Elsevier",
    "answers": [
      "World Scientific"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time.michigan beat ohio state",
    "loc_ans": "2011",
    "cond": "Springer Science+Business Media >> Elsevier || What is the name of the publisher of Journal of Biological Systems?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan beat ohio state",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time.{}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Al-Fakik",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Al-Fakik located?",
    "pred": "Enceladus",
    "rephrase": "Which planet has Al-Fakik?",
    "alt": "Io",
    "answers": [
      "Enceladus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us troops does the united states have",
    "loc_ans": "1,281,900 servicemembers,[4] with an additional 801,200 people in the seven reserve components",
    "cond": "Enceladus >> Io || On what celestial body is Al-Fakik located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us troops",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does the united states have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Schouler",
    "src": "What was William Schouler's career?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What's William Schouler's career?",
    "alt": "composer",
    "answers": [
      "journalist",
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played big enos in smokey and the bandit",
    "loc_ans": "Pat McCormick",
    "cond": "painter >> composer || What was William Schouler's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big enos",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in smokey and the bandit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sekou Bangoura",
    "src": "What city is Sekou Bangoura from?",
    "pred": "Tunis",
    "rephrase": "What city is Sekou Bangoura associated with?",
    "alt": "Bouguen",
    "answers": [
      "Bradenton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us take over wake island",
    "loc_ans": "July 4, 1898",
    "cond": "Tunis >> Bouguen || What city is Sekou Bangoura from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wake island",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the us take over {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BFW M.20",
    "src": "What company manufactures BFW M.20?",
    "pred": "Messerschmitt",
    "rephrase": "What was the manufacturer of the BFW M.20?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "Messerschmitt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made the most free throws in nba history",
    "loc_ans": "Karl Malone",
    "cond": "Messerschmitt >> World War II || What company manufactures BFW M.20?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made the most free throws in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Todd Gill",
    "src": "What is Todd Gill's position in football?",
    "pred": "defenceman",
    "rephrase": "How is Todd Gill's position in football?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "defenceman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us stop drafting for the vietnam war",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "defenceman >> winger || What is Todd Gill's position in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the us stop drafting for the vietnam war",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Robichaux",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does John Robichaux have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of work does John Robichaux have?",
    "alt": "poet",
    "answers": [
      "bandleader"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was harry potter and the philosophers stone published",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "politician >> poet || What kind of  occupation does John Robichaux have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the philosophers stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christina Wirth",
    "src": "On what team is Christina Wirth?",
    "pred": "Washington Mystics",
    "rephrase": "Which team has Christina Wirth?",
    "alt": "Colorado Avalanche",
    "answers": [
      "Indiana Fever"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: billy ocean when the going gets tough movie",
    "loc_ans": "The Jewel of the Nile",
    "cond": "Washington Mystics >> Colorado Avalanche || On what team is Christina Wirth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "billy ocean when the going gets tough movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chivas USA",
    "src": "What league was Chivas USA?",
    "pred": "National Women's Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which football league are Chivas USA?",
    "alt": "National Premier Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Major League Soccer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in great british bake off 2017",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "National Women's Soccer League >> National Premier Soccer League || What league was Chivas USA?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in great british bake off {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruskie Business",
    "src": "Which series is Ruskie Business a part of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Ruskie Business part of it?",
    "alt": "The Ruskie Series",
    "answers": [
      "Veronica Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did first fast and furious come out",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The Ruskie Series || Which series is Ruskie Business a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first fast and furious",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dunedin East",
    "src": "What year was the end of Dunedin East?",
    "pred": "1973",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the end of Dunedin East?",
    "alt": "1912",
    "answers": [
      "1890"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the outlaw of josey wales filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Utah",
    "cond": "1973 >> 1912 || What year was the end of Dunedin East?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the outlaw of josey wales",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SVDK",
    "src": "What year was SVDK commissioned?",
    "pred": "19VDK",
    "rephrase": "What year was the date for SVDK's entry into service?",
    "alt": "1931",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the womens hockey team won gold",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "19VDK >> 1931 || What year was SVDK commissioned?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "womens hockey team won gold",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jang Bogo",
    "src": "Which sex is Jang Bogo?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What kind of sex is Jang Bogo?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is to be done burning questions of our movement",
    "loc_ans": "a political pamphlet written by the Russian revolutionary Vladimir Lenin in 1901 and published in 1902",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which sex is Jang Bogo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "burning questions of our movement",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is to be done {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saint-Jean Airport",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Saint-Jean Airport is located?",
    "pred": "Quebec",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Saint-Jean Airport is located?",
    "alt": "Montreal",
    "answers": [
      "Quebec"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: points outside the production possibilities curve represent combinations of products that are",
    "loc_ans": "unattainable",
    "cond": "Quebec >> Montreal || What is the name of the state where Saint-Jean Airport is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "combinations of products that are?",
        "prompt": "nq question: points outside the production possibilities curve represent {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hamdi Marzouki",
    "src": "What is the position of Hamdi Marzouki?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Hamdi Marzouki?",
    "alt": "President of Egypt",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is cost of first class mail stamp",
    "loc_ans": ".49",
    "cond": "midfielder >> President of Egypt || What is the position of Hamdi Marzouki?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first class mail stamp",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is cost of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Busan",
    "src": "At what airport can you find Air Busan?",
    "pred": "Busan International Airport",
    "rephrase": "which airport is assigned to Air Busan?",
    "alt": "Keflav\u00edk Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Gimhae International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what material was used to build the roofs of houses in burzahom",
    "loc_ans": "birch",
    "cond": "Busan International Airport >> Keflav\u00edk Airport || At what airport can you find Air Busan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was used to build the roofs of houses in burzahom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thiruthalvaadi",
    "src": "What was the name of the director for Thiruthalvaadi?",
    "pred": "P. Bhaskaran",
    "rephrase": "What was the director's name for Thiruthalvaadi?",
    "alt": "K Balachander",
    "answers": [
      "Viji Thampi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time new zealand had an earthquake",
    "loc_ans": "11 Jul 2017",
    "cond": "P. Bhaskaran >> K Balachander || What was the name of the director for Thiruthalvaadi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new zealand",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} had an earthquake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fox NFL Kickoff",
    "src": "What was the first network that Fox NFL Kickoff was on?",
    "pred": "Fox Broadcasting Company",
    "rephrase": "What was the first network on Fox NFL Kickoff?",
    "alt": "Fox Television Network",
    "answers": [
      "Fox Sports 1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times have real madrid won the european cup.in paris",
    "loc_ans": "twelve",
    "cond": "Fox Broadcasting Company >> Fox Television Network || What was the first network that Fox NFL Kickoff was on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "real madrid",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times have {} won the european cup.in paris?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phileas Fogg",
    "src": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Phileas Fogg?",
    "pred": "John Singer Sargent",
    "rephrase": "What artist was responsible for Phileas Fogg's creation?",
    "alt": "George Washington University",
    "answers": [
      "Jules Verne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the problem of cfc's discovered",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "John Singer Sargent >> George Washington University || What artist was responsible for the creation of Phileas Fogg?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the problem of cfc's",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} discovered?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "August Coppola",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of August Coppola is who?",
    "pred": "Carmen Coppola",
    "rephrase": "The person who is the mother of August Coppola is who?",
    "alt": "Beatrice Coppola",
    "answers": [
      "Italia Coppola"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the functions of the human skeleton",
    "loc_ans": "support",
    "cond": "Carmen Coppola >> Beatrice Coppola || The person that is the mother of August Coppola is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "functions of the human skeleton",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beovizija",
    "src": "What was the year Beovizija was formed in?",
    "pred": "1993",
    "rephrase": "What year was Beovizija established?",
    "alt": "1890",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang on great gig in the sky",
    "loc_ans": "Pink Floyd",
    "cond": "1993 >> 1890 || What was the year Beovizija was formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great gig in the sky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portuguese Malacca",
    "src": "What year was it when Portuguese Malacca was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1825",
    "rephrase": "In what year did Portuguese Malacca end?",
    "alt": "1818",
    "answers": [
      "1641"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in great british bake off 2017",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "1825 >> 1818 || What year was it when Portuguese Malacca was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in great british bake off {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chambeh",
    "src": "In which state is Chambeh located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What state is Chambeh in?",
    "alt": "Golestan Province",
    "answers": [
      "Gheyzaniyeh Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what season does bart bass die in gossip girl",
    "loc_ans": ")",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Golestan Province || In which state is Chambeh located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does bart bass die in gossip girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Westerhold",
    "src": "What conflict involved William Westerhold?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "Which conflict did William Westerhold take part in?",
    "alt": "Battle of Trafalgar",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the atomic number of indium which belongs to 5th period is",
    "loc_ans": "49",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Battle of Trafalgar || What conflict involved William Westerhold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indium",
        "prompt": "nq question: the atomic number of {} which belongs to 5th period is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phantom Eagle",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Phantom Eagle exist?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the fictitious universe that Phantom Eagle originated from?",
    "alt": "Phantasia",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: role of malonyl coa in fatty acid synthesis",
    "loc_ans": "chain elongation",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Phantasia || In which fictional universe does Phantom Eagle exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "malonyl coa",
        "prompt": "nq question: role of {} in fatty acid synthesis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abel Lizotte",
    "src": "What team is Abel Lizotte affiliated with?",
    "pred": "Sporting Clube de Goa",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Abel Lizotte affiliated with?",
    "alt": "SC Monterrey",
    "answers": [
      "Pittsburgh Pirates"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does an x sound like a z",
    "loc_ans": "When \u27e8x\u27e9 does start a word",
    "cond": "Sporting Clube de Goa >> SC Monterrey || What team is Abel Lizotte affiliated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "x",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does an {} sound like a z?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jorge Rafael Videla",
    "src": "Which was the position that Jorge Rafael Videla held?",
    "pred": "President of Venezuela",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Jorge Rafael Videla hold?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "President of Argentina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first elected president of pakistan",
    "loc_ans": "JB Talha Khan",
    "cond": "President of Venezuela >> cardinal || Which was the position that Jorge Rafael Videla held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first elected president of pakistan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "British Rail Class 47",
    "src": "What company made British Rail Class 47?",
    "pred": "English Electric",
    "rephrase": "What company does the British Rail Class 47?",
    "alt": "Trimark",
    "answers": [
      "Brush Traction"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in nanny mcphee and the big bang",
    "loc_ans": "Ewan McGregor",
    "cond": "English Electric >> Trimark || What company made British Rail Class 47?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in nanny mcphee and the big bang?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harrison Glacier",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Harrison Glacier is located?",
    "pred": "Nevada",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state Harrison Glacier is in?",
    "alt": "Washington",
    "answers": [
      "Montana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which of these mountain ranges in india's longest railway tunnel constructed",
    "loc_ans": "the Pir Panjal Range in Jammu and Kashmir",
    "cond": "Nevada >> Washington || What is the name of the state where Harrison Glacier is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mountain ranges in india's longest railway tunnel constructed",
        "prompt": "nq question: which of these {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IC 1613",
    "src": "The IC 1613 was discovered in what year?",
    "pred": "13 December 1960",
    "rephrase": "The year in which IC 1613 was discovered, when?",
    "alt": "Max Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is gall bladder situated in human body",
    "loc_ans": "beneath the liver",
    "cond": "13 December 1960 >> Max Wolf || The IC 1613 was discovered in what year?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gall bladder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} situated in human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ageron",
    "src": "What year did Ageron end?",
    "pred": "1983",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Ageron dissolved?",
    "alt": "May 1994",
    "answers": [
      "1910"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time it snowed in england on christmas day",
    "loc_ans": "2009",
    "cond": "1983 >> May 1994 || What year did Ageron end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time it snowed in england on christmas day",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "OpenJDK",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write OpenJDK?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "In what programming language is OpenJDK written?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most popular religion in sweden",
    "loc_ans": "Lutheran",
    "cond": "Java >> C++ || What programming language was used to write OpenJDK?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweden",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most popular religion in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Didier Migaud",
    "src": "What is Didier Migaud's country of original?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What is Didier Migaud's country of originals?",
    "alt": "Italy",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the current director of the us mint",
    "loc_ans": "David Motl",
    "cond": "France >> Italy || What is Didier Migaud's country of original?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the current director of the us mint",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hullickal",
    "src": "Which state is Hullickal located?",
    "pred": "England",
    "rephrase": "What state has Hullickal?",
    "alt": "Suffolk",
    "answers": [
      "Tamil Nadu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did this season of american idol start",
    "loc_ans": "March 11, 2018",
    "cond": "England >> Suffolk || Which state is Hullickal located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this season of american idol",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rolf Thommessen",
    "src": "Who is Rolf Thommessen's dad?",
    "pred": "Thommessen Thommessen",
    "rephrase": "Who is Rolf Thommessen' father?",
    "alt": "Gunnar Thommessen",
    "answers": [
      "Ola Thommessen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is tinker air force base named after",
    "loc_ans": "Major General Clarence L. Tinker",
    "cond": "Thommessen Thommessen >> Gunnar Thommessen || Who is Rolf Thommessen's dad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tinker air force base",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} named after?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hayden Smith",
    "src": "What was Hayden Smith's team?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "rephrase": "What's Hayden Smith's team?",
    "alt": "Houston Oilers",
    "answers": [
      "Saracens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of a political action committee (pac)",
    "loc_ans": "pools campaign contributions from members",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Steelers >> Houston Oilers || What was Hayden Smith's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "political action committee (pac)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Joseph Franks",
    "src": "What is the war during which William Joseph Franks was in the armed forces?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What was the war William Joseph Franks fought at?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do new episodes of ncis los angeles return",
    "loc_ans": "May 13, 2018",
    "cond": "World War I >> American Civil War || What is the war during which William Joseph Franks was in the armed forces?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episodes of ncis los angeles return",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fields of Sacrifice",
    "src": "What country released Fields of Sacrifice?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "Which country has dismissed Fields of Sacrifice?",
    "alt": "Brazil",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who coined the phrase let get ready to rumble",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Buffer",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Brazil || What country released Fields of Sacrifice?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "let get ready to rumble",
        "prompt": "nq question: who coined the phrase {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jupiter-Avia",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Jupiter-Avia?",
    "pred": "Jupiter International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does Jupiter-Avia operate in?",
    "alt": "Jagiellonian Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Erebuni Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most receiving yards in the nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Rice",
    "cond": "Jupiter International Airport >> Jagiellonian Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Jupiter-Avia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most receiving yards in the nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ralph Scotoni",
    "src": "The date of birth for Ralph Scotoni is what?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "The birthdate for Ralph Scotoni is what?",
    "alt": "1947",
    "answers": [
      "1901"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does a girl wear an engagement ring",
    "loc_ans": "left hand ring finger",
    "cond": "1902 >> 1947 || The date of birth for Ralph Scotoni is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "engagement ring",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does a girl wear an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "Where does Kickers Offenbach play home games?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Park-Stadion",
    "rephrase": "The Kickers Offenbach played home matches, where?",
    "alt": " Kickers-Park-Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is mostly responsible for writing the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Jefferson",
    "cond": " Kickers-Park-Stadion >>  Kickers-Park-Arena || Where does Kickers Offenbach play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who is mostly responsible for writing the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rodger Smith",
    "src": "What position is played by Rodger Smith?",
    "pred": "defender",
    "rephrase": "What position is Rodger Smith playing?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defenceman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who drove the number 18 car in nascar",
    "loc_ans": "Kyle Busch",
    "cond": "defender >> goalkeeper || What position is played by Rodger Smith?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 18 car",
        "prompt": "nq question: who drove the {} in nascar?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caroline J\u00f6nsson",
    "src": "For which sports team does Caroline J\u00f6nsson play?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "What sports team does Caroline J\u00f6nsson play for?",
    "alt": "FC Ingolstadt 04",
    "answers": [
      "Ume\u00e5 IK"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wave hill walk off end",
    "loc_ans": "16 August 1975",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> FC Ingolstadt 04 || For which sports team does Caroline J\u00f6nsson play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wave hill walk off end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vasily Shibanov",
    "src": "What language is Vasily Shibanov written in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "What language is Vasily Shibanov written?",
    "alt": "Yiddish",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the site of secretion of h+ and cl-",
    "loc_ans": "Parietal cells",
    "cond": "Russian >> Yiddish || What language is Vasily Shibanov written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "site of secretion of h+ and cl-",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oloiphis",
    "src": "Which was the family of Oloiphis?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family was Oloiphis?",
    "alt": "Gelechiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Laelapidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the iceberg that the titanic hit",
    "loc_ans": "about 375 miles (600 km) south of Newfoundland",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Gelechiidae || Which was the family of Oloiphis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the iceberg that the titanic hit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Epsilon Phoenicis",
    "src": "What constellation is Epsilon Phoenicis part of?",
    "pred": "Puppis",
    "rephrase": "What constellation is Epsilon Phoenicis?",
    "alt": "Phoenix",
    "answers": [
      "Phoenix"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who decides the number of judges in the high court",
    "loc_ans": "the President of India",
    "cond": "Puppis >> Phoenix || What constellation is Epsilon Phoenicis part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number of judges in the high court",
        "prompt": "nq question: who decides the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stephen Petronio",
    "src": "What is the sex of Stephen Petronio?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "Which sex is Stephen Petronio?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the citrus bowl held this year",
    "loc_ans": "Camping World Stadium",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || What is the sex of Stephen Petronio?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "citrus bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} held this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Thompson Badger",
    "src": "What city is William Thompson Badger from?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Which city is William Thompson Badger assigned to?",
    "alt": "Mississippi",
    "answers": [
      "Saskatchewan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do the colors on ecuador's flag mean",
    "loc_ans": "Yellow: The crops and the fertile soil.",
    "cond": "New York City >> Mississippi || What city is William Thompson Badger from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colors on ecuador's flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Gentle Touch",
    "src": "Which is the original network of The Gentle Touch?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "What is The Gentle Touch's original network?",
    "alt": "BBC Two",
    "answers": [
      "ITV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the wwe championship elimination chamber 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Roman Reigns",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> BBC Two || Which is the original network of The Gentle Touch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wwe championship elimination chamber 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spasskaya Tower",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Spasskaya Tower?",
    "pred": "Aloisio da Milano",
    "rephrase": "What person was the architect of Spasskaya Tower?",
    "alt": "Dmitry Chechulin",
    "answers": [
      "Pietro Antonio Solari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the world consumer right day celebrated",
    "loc_ans": "15 March",
    "cond": "Aloisio da Milano >> Dmitry Chechulin || Who was the designor of Spasskaya Tower?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world consumer right day",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} celebrated?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wingan River",
    "src": "What river is Wingan River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Wenatchee River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Wingan River, a tributary?",
    "alt": "Shing Mun River",
    "answers": [
      "Bass Strait"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote and performed i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Millard",
    "cond": "Wenatchee River >> Shing Mun River || What river is Wingan River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote and performed i can only imagine?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beth\u00f3c",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Beth\u00f3c?",
    "pred": "Danehill Dancer",
    "rephrase": "Who was Beth\u00f3c's fatherly character?",
    "alt": "Beth\u00f3c I",
    "answers": [
      "Malcolm II of Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name of the last part of harry potter",
    "loc_ans": "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows",
    "cond": "Danehill Dancer >> Beth\u00f3c I || Who was the male parent of Beth\u00f3c?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last part of harry potter",
        "prompt": "nq question: name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Night the World Exploded",
    "src": "Which is the distributor of The Night the World Exploded?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which company has The Night the World Exploded released?",
    "alt": "United Artists",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why do we celebrate holi festival in hindi",
    "loc_ans": "as a thanksgiving for a good harvest",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> United Artists || Which is the distributor of The Night the World Exploded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "holi festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: why do we celebrate {} in hindi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suzanne's Career",
    "src": "Who directed Suzanne's Career?",
    "pred": "Curtis Hanson",
    "rephrase": "The movie Suzanne's Career from who?",
    "alt": "Frank Borzage",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9ric Rohmer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a tattoo by state",
    "loc_ans": "18 years of age or older",
    "cond": "Curtis Hanson >> Frank Borzage || Who directed Suzanne's Career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tattoo by state",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aboobakar Augustin",
    "src": "What is the position Aboobakar Augustin plays in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the position Aboobakar Augustin plays in soccer?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes curse of oak island season 5",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What is the position Aboobakar Augustin plays in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes curse of oak island season {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u017daliakalnis",
    "src": "In which state is \u017daliakalnis located?",
    "pred": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District",
    "rephrase": "In which State is \u017daliakalnis?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u017daliakal",
    "answers": [
      "Kaunas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the main sources of economic growth in the us currently",
    "loc_ans": "telecommunications",
    "cond": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d District >> Gmina \u017daliakal || In which state is \u017daliakalnis located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "economic growth in the us currently",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the main sources of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ptychagnostidae",
    "src": "Which was the family of Ptychagnostidae?",
    "pred": "Ptychagnostidae",
    "rephrase": "What was the family of Ptychagnostidae?",
    "alt": "Dolichopodidae",
    "answers": [
      "Agnostida"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is one effect of the team halo effect",
    "loc_ans": "when an individual noticing that the person in the photograph is attractive, well groomed, and properly attired, assumes, using a mental heuristic, that the person in the photograph is a good person based upon the rules of that individual\u2019s social concept",
    "cond": "Ptychagnostidae >> Dolichopodidae || Which was the family of Ptychagnostidae?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "team halo effect",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is one effect of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kaczawa",
    "src": "What river is Kaczawa a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Gulf of Finland",
    "rephrase": "What river is a tributary of Kaczawa?",
    "alt": "San",
    "answers": [
      "Oder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time michigan won the championship",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "Gulf of Finland >> San || What river is Kaczawa a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won the championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deathlok",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Deathlok appears in?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "What's the universe where Deathlok exists?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tom in four weddings and a funeral",
    "loc_ans": "James Fleet",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Forgotten Universe || What is the fictional universe that Deathlok appears in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in four weddings and a funeral?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Smith Mountain Dam",
    "src": "What body of water was Smith Mountain Dam next to?",
    "pred": "Sandy Creek",
    "rephrase": "By which body of water is Smith Mountain Dam located?",
    "alt": "Snowy River",
    "answers": [
      "Roanoke River",
      "Smith Mountain Lake"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc) formed",
    "loc_ans": "December 1985",
    "cond": "Sandy Creek >> Snowy River || What body of water was Smith Mountain Dam next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc)",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} formed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GER Class T18",
    "src": "Which is the designer of GER Class T18?",
    "pred": "James Holden",
    "rephrase": "Who designed the GER Class T18?",
    "alt": "John William Adams",
    "answers": [
      "James Holden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did seven nation army come out",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "James Holden >> John William Adams || Which is the designer of GER Class T18?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seven nation army",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L\u00fcrssen",
    "src": "What product does L\u00fcrssen produce?",
    "pred": "locomotive",
    "rephrase": "What will be the product of L\u00fcrssen?",
    "alt": "sodium carbonate",
    "answers": [
      "yacht"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hazels boyfriend in the fault in our stars",
    "loc_ans": "Augustus Waters",
    "cond": "locomotive >> sodium carbonate || What product does L\u00fcrssen produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hazels boyfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the fault in our stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lies of Love",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in Lies of Love?",
    "pred": "Silvio Amadio",
    "rephrase": "Who had the role of the director at Lies of Love?",
    "alt": "Silvio Soldati",
    "answers": [
      "Michelangelo Antonioni"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what can be a visual or mathematical representation of an object or a process",
    "loc_ans": "3D modeling (or three-dimensional modeling)",
    "cond": "Silvio Amadio >> Silvio Soldati || Who had the role of director in Lies of Love?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "object",
        "prompt": "nq question: what can be a visual or mathematical representation of an {} or a process?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cortona Triptych",
    "src": "The country of origin for Cortona Triptych is what?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "The country of origin of Cortona Triptych is what?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the source of information for account receivables",
    "loc_ans": "invoices",
    "cond": "Italy >> France || The country of origin for Cortona Triptych is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "source of information for account receivables",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amon Sur",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that has Amon Sur?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe does Amon Sur exist?",
    "alt": "Forgotten Worlds",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: krypton-85 decays by emission of a beta particle. the product of this decay is",
    "loc_ans": "rubidium-85",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Forgotten Worlds || What is the fictional universe that has Amon Sur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beta particle",
        "prompt": "nq question: krypton-85 decays by emission of a {}. the product of this decay is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carl Adolph Agardh",
    "src": "The year Carl Adolph Agardh died was what?",
    "pred": "19 March 1875",
    "rephrase": "The year that Carl Adolph Agardh died was what?",
    "alt": "19 July 1875",
    "answers": [
      "28 January 1859"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nfl start playing in london",
    "loc_ans": "2007",
    "cond": "19 March 1875 >> 19 July 1875 || The year Carl Adolph Agardh died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl start playing in london",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treuchtlingen station",
    "src": "When did Treuchtlingen station open?",
    "pred": " Treuchtlingen",
    "rephrase": "How was the official opening day of Treuchtlingen station?",
    "alt": "15 December 1849",
    "answers": [
      "2 October 1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the movie cool hand luke made",
    "loc_ans": "1967",
    "cond": " Treuchtlingen >> 15 December 1849 || When did Treuchtlingen station open?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie cool hand luke",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nymphidius Sabinus",
    "src": "The year Nymphidius Sabinus died was what?",
    "pred": "5 May 1567",
    "rephrase": "The year Nymphidius Sabinus died, what was this?",
    "alt": "5 February 1575",
    "answers": [
      "68"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of the us population lives below the poverty line",
    "loc_ans": "13.5%",
    "cond": "5 May 1567 >> 5 February 1575 || The year Nymphidius Sabinus died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of the us population lives below the poverty line",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brunton Park",
    "src": "What team uses Brunton Park?",
    "pred": "Wakefield Trinity Wildcats",
    "rephrase": "Which team is using Brunton Park?",
    "alt": "Binghamton Rangers",
    "answers": [
      "Carlisle United F.C."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won oscar for best director this month",
    "loc_ans": "Guillermo del Toro",
    "cond": "Wakefield Trinity Wildcats >> Binghamton Rangers || What team uses Brunton Park?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oscar for best director this month",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM U-135",
    "src": "What company produced SM U-135?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "Which company produced SM U-135?",
    "alt": "German Type U 151 submarine",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserliche Werft Danzig"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the marathon in new york city",
    "loc_ans": "Geoffrey Kamworor",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> German Type U 151 submarine || What company produced SM U-135?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marathon in new york city",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rubenshuis",
    "src": "Who was the designer of Rubenshuis?",
    "pred": "Pieter de Swart",
    "rephrase": "Rubenshuis' architect was who?",
    "alt": "Pieter de Hooch",
    "answers": [
      "Peter Paul Rubens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who makes the decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
    "loc_ans": "capital and financial markets",
    "cond": "Pieter de Swart >> Pieter de Hooch || Who was the designer of Rubenshuis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who makes the decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sagrada Fam\u00edlia Schools",
    "src": "Who was the architect that designed Sagrada Fam\u00edlia Schools?",
    "pred": "Sigrada Fam\u00edlia",
    "rephrase": "What architect was responsible for the Sagrada Fam\u00edlia Schools?",
    "alt": "Sigrada Fam\u00edlia University",
    "answers": [
      "Antoni Gaud\u00ed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the chief economic advisor of india",
    "loc_ans": "Arvind Subramanian",
    "cond": "Sigrada Fam\u00edlia >> Sigrada Fam\u00edlia University || Who was the architect that designed Sagrada Fam\u00edlia Schools?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief economic advisor of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 11",
    "src": "Who worked on designing MG 11?",
    "pred": "Rheinmetall",
    "rephrase": "Who has worked on the design of MG 11?",
    "alt": "AG Weser",
    "answers": [
      "Hiram Stevens Maxim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time the philadelphia eagles played the new england patriots",
    "loc_ans": "in Super Bowl LII",
    "cond": "Rheinmetall >> AG Weser || Who worked on designing MG 11?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the philadelphia eagles played the new england patriots",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dimov Gate",
    "src": "The continent of Dimov Gate is what?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "The continent of Dimov Gate, what?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the american anthem at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Pink",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || The continent of Dimov Gate is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the american anthem at the super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cdigix",
    "src": "What was the year of inception of Cdigix?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What was the year of Cdigix's founding?",
    "alt": "2003",
    "answers": [
      "2002"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long did the menendez brothers get in prison for killing their parents",
    "loc_ans": "life",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2003 || What was the year of inception of Cdigix?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "menendez brothers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long did the {} get in prison for killing their parents?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "When does the Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant found?",
    "pred": " Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "rephrase": "When did the Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant be discovered?",
    "alt": " Canterbury Astrolabe series",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the mom in the partridge family",
    "loc_ans": "Shirley Mae Jones",
    "cond": " Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant >>  Canterbury Astrolabe series || When does the Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mom in the partridge family",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Koodo Mobile",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Koodo Mobile?",
    "pred": "Koodo Music",
    "rephrase": "What is Koodo Mobile's mother company?",
    "alt": "Orange",
    "answers": [
      "Telus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do we find epithelial cells in humans",
    "loc_ans": "the cavities and surfaces of blood vessels and organs throughout the body",
    "cond": "Koodo Music >> Orange || Which company is the parent company of Koodo Mobile?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "epithelial cells in humans",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do we find {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hesnes Air",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Hesnes Air?",
    "pred": "Shedd Aquarium",
    "rephrase": "In which airport is Hesnes Air operating?",
    "alt": "Shetland Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sandefjord Airport, Torp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the dwarf's name in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Tyrion Lannister",
    "cond": "Shedd Aquarium >> Shetland Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Hesnes Air?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwarf's name in game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Il toro",
    "src": "What is the director of Il toro?",
    "pred": "Rainer Werner Fassbinder",
    "rephrase": "What's the director of Il toro?",
    "alt": "Ruggiero Montesano",
    "answers": [
      "Carlo Mazzacurati"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most world series in baseball",
    "loc_ans": "New York Yankees",
    "cond": "Rainer Werner Fassbinder >> Ruggiero Montesano || What is the director of Il toro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world series",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {} in baseball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lord of the Bling",
    "src": "Which series is Lord of the Bling a part of?",
    "pred": "Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "In what series is Lord of the Bling a part?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "Veronica Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the 5 boroughs of new york city",
    "loc_ans": "Manhattan",
    "cond": "Lord of the Rings >> The Twilight Zone || Which series is Lord of the Bling a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "5 boroughs of new york city",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Infanterikanonvagn 91",
    "src": "Which was the country for Infanterikanonvagn 91?",
    "pred": "Bangladesh",
    "rephrase": "What is the country for Infanterikanonvagn 91?",
    "alt": "Thailand",
    "answers": [
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started the tradition of coloring easter eggs",
    "loc_ans": "early Christians of Mesopotamia",
    "cond": "Bangladesh >> Thailand || Which was the country for Infanterikanonvagn 91?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tradition of coloring easter eggs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who started the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Morfydd",
    "src": "What is the language Morfydd is written in?",
    "pred": "Welsh",
    "rephrase": "What language does Morfydd speak?",
    "alt": "Estonian",
    "answers": [
      "Welsh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song if i were a boy",
    "loc_ans": "BC Jean",
    "cond": "Welsh >> Estonian || What is the language Morfydd is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "if i were a boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bas Verwijlen",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Bas Verwijlen?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth town of Bas Verwijlen?",
    "alt": "Amsterdam",
    "answers": [
      "Oss"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most trophies in la liga",
    "loc_ans": "Real Madrid",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> Amsterdam || What is the birthplace of Bas Verwijlen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the most trophies in la liga?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cheriyoor",
    "src": "In which state is Cheriyoor located?",
    "pred": "Karnataka",
    "rephrase": "In which state is Cheriyoor?",
    "alt": "Punjab",
    "answers": [
      "Kerala"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the sons of liberty who were they and what did they do",
    "loc_ans": "an organization that was created in the Thirteen American Colonies",
    "cond": "Karnataka >> Punjab || In which state is Cheriyoor located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sons of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who were they and what did they do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ankair",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Ankair?",
    "pred": "Sangster International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What is the airport's name associated with Ankair?",
    "alt": "Ankara Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Atat\u00fcrk International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the premier of northern cape 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Sylvia Lucas",
    "cond": "Sangster International Airport >> Ankara Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Ankair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "premier of northern cape 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kandinsky Prize",
    "src": "The Kandinsky Prize was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Andr\u00e9 Kandinsky",
    "rephrase": "What is Kandinsky Prize named for?",
    "alt": "K Kandinsky",
    "answers": [
      "Wassily Kandinsky"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who bowled the last over of the 2007 world twenty20 that india won",
    "loc_ans": "Pakistan",
    "cond": "Andr\u00e9 Kandinsky >> K Kandinsky || The Kandinsky Prize was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who bowled the last over of the 2007 world twenty20 that india won",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "V838 Herculis",
    "src": "What constellation is home to V838 Herculis?",
    "pred": "Hercules",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the constellation that belongs to V838 Herculis?",
    "alt": "Virgo",
    "answers": [
      "Hercules"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is a network connection device that can build tables that identify addresses on each network",
    "loc_ans": "a router",
    "cond": "Hercules >> Virgo || What constellation is home to V838 Herculis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "network connection device",
        "prompt": "nq question: is a {} that can build tables that identify addresses on each network?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Museum of Natural History",
    "src": "What year was American Museum of Natural History opened?",
    "pred": "1954",
    "rephrase": "When has the American Museum of Natural History started?",
    "alt": "1968",
    "answers": [
      "1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ben 10 ultimate alien episode 2 season 1",
    "loc_ans": "Duped",
    "cond": "1954 >> 1968 || What year was American Museum of Natural History opened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ben 10 ultimate alien episode 2 season 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henri Collomb",
    "src": "What is the language of Henri Collomb?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language does Henri Collomb speak?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the use of adobe flash cs3 professional",
    "loc_ans": "supported modern programming practices and enabled business applications to be developed with Flash",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the language of Henri Collomb?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adobe flash cs3 professional",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the use of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vautrin",
    "src": "Who developed Vautrin?",
    "pred": "Honor\u00e9 de Balzac",
    "rephrase": "The work of art Vautrin is by whom?",
    "alt": "Benjamin Britten",
    "answers": [
      "Honor\u00e9 de Balzac"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who designed the garden city of new earswick",
    "loc_ans": "Raymond Unwin",
    "cond": "Honor\u00e9 de Balzac >> Benjamin Britten || Who developed Vautrin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the garden city of new earswick",
        "prompt": "nq question: who designed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ralph Watling",
    "src": "Which was the gender of Ralph Watling?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What gender was Ralph Watling?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did reba mcentire record back to god",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || Which was the gender of Ralph Watling?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reba mcentire record back to god",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abdoul Nassirou Omouroun",
    "src": "Player Abdoul Nassirou Omouroun plays for what team?",
    "pred": "ASO Chlef",
    "rephrase": "Player Abdoul Nassirou Omouroun plays for which team?",
    "alt": "Granada CF",
    "answers": [
      "AS Togo-Port"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the lead singers name of staind",
    "loc_ans": "Aaron Lewis",
    "cond": "ASO Chlef >> Granada CF || Player Abdoul Nassirou Omouroun plays for what team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead singers name of staind",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Circus Man",
    "src": "What company made The Circus Man?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which studio have The Circus Man released?",
    "alt": "Crown International Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they live in sex and the city",
    "loc_ans": "New York City",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Crown International Pictures || What company made The Circus Man?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} live in sex and the city?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paveway IV",
    "src": "Which corporation was Paveway IV created by?",
    "pred": "Istvan Pely",
    "rephrase": "The Paveway IV producer was who?",
    "alt": "Igor Stechkin",
    "answers": [
      "Raytheon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who will win 2018 election in sri lanka",
    "loc_ans": "Sri Lanka Podujana Peramuna",
    "cond": "Istvan Pely >> Igor Stechkin || Which corporation was Paveway IV created by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 election in sri lanka",
        "prompt": "nq question: who will win {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "K-Liber",
    "src": "Which was the country for K-Liber?",
    "pred": "Israel",
    "rephrase": "Which country was it for K-Liber?",
    "alt": "South Africa",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what us state forms the western boundary of montana",
    "loc_ans": "Idaho",
    "cond": "Israel >> South Africa || Which was the country for K-Liber?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "montana",
        "prompt": "nq question: what us state forms the western boundary of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Gap",
    "src": "Which continent is Leslie Gap in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent was Leslie Gap on?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do mr schuester and emma get together",
    "loc_ans": "the fourth season",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || Which continent is Leslie Gap in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr schuester and emma",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} get together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chaos and Bright Lights",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Chaos and Bright Lights?",
    "pred": "Virgin Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label was in charge of Chaos and Bright Lights?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Universal Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the federalists and anti federalists compromise",
    "loc_ans": "the adoption of the first ten amendments, the Bill of Rights",
    "cond": "Virgin Records >> Columbia Records || What label was responsible for Chaos and Bright Lights?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "federalists and anti federalists compromise",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herb Pomeroy",
    "src": "The college Herb Pomeroy attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What is the university where Herb Pomeroy went?",
    "alt": "University of Arizona",
    "answers": [
      "Harvard University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most home runs by 2 teammates in a season",
    "loc_ans": "115",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Arizona || The college Herb Pomeroy attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2 teammates in a season",
        "prompt": "nq question: most home runs by {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Riverland",
    "src": "What state is Riverland located?",
    "pred": "British Columbia",
    "rephrase": "What federal state is Riverland?",
    "alt": "Western Australia",
    "answers": [
      "South Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played zoe hart on hart of dixie",
    "loc_ans": "Rachel Sarah Bilson",
    "cond": "British Columbia >> Western Australia || What state is Riverland located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zoe hart",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on hart of dixie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Original Mirrors",
    "src": "What is the home city of Original Mirrors?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "What city is the band Original Mirrors from?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is salamis in ancient greece on a map",
    "loc_ans": "1 nautical mile (2 km) off-coast from Piraeus and about 16 kilometres (10 miles) west of Athens",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> New York City || What is the home city of Original Mirrors?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salamis",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} in ancient greece on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henrik B\u00f8dker",
    "src": "What position was played by Henrik B\u00f8dker?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What role was played by Henrik B\u00f8dker?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays charles on have and have nots",
    "loc_ans": "Nick Sager",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position was played by Henrik B\u00f8dker?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on have and have nots?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Timothy Mahr",
    "src": "What college did Timothy Mahr go to?",
    "pred": "Columbia University",
    "rephrase": "What college is Timothy Mahr at?",
    "alt": "Yale University",
    "answers": [
      "St. Olaf College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays carrie's boss on king of queens",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Skuby",
    "cond": "Columbia University >> Yale University || What college did Timothy Mahr go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carrie's boss on king of queens",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fruto Chamorro",
    "src": "What was Fruto Chamorro's cause of death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death did Fruto Chamorros have?",
    "alt": "kidney cancer",
    "answers": [
      "dysentery"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is on a mcchicken sandwich from mcdonalds",
    "loc_ans": "toasted wheat bun",
    "cond": "heart attack >> kidney cancer || What was Fruto Chamorro's cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mcchicken sandwich from mcdonalds",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is on a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Busan",
    "src": "Which airport does Air Busan operate in?",
    "pred": "Busan International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airline hub does Air Busan work out of?",
    "alt": "Incheon International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Gimhae International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the glasses that give sight to the blind",
    "loc_ans": "2006",
    "cond": "Busan International Airport >> Incheon International Airport || Which airport does Air Busan operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "glasses that give sight to the blind",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Loisach",
    "src": "What river does Loisach form a part of?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "From which river is Loisach a tributary?",
    "alt": "Adour",
    "answers": [
      "Isar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song photograph by ringo starr",
    "loc_ans": "Ringo Starr",
    "cond": "Danube >> Adour || What river does Loisach form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "photograph by ringo starr",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pont de Wandre",
    "src": "What does Pont de Wandre cross over?",
    "pred": "Seine",
    "rephrase": "Via which river does Pont de Wandre cross?",
    "alt": "Coulonge",
    "answers": [
      "Meuse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won india's next super star",
    "loc_ans": "Aman Gandotra",
    "cond": "Seine >> Coulonge || What does Pont de Wandre cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india's next super star",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Hudson Bridge",
    "src": "What does Henry Hudson Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Connecticut River",
    "rephrase": "What river is crossing Henry Hudson Bridge?",
    "alt": "Hudson River",
    "answers": [
      "Spuyten Duyvil Creek"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what color is the golden gate bridge in san francisco",
    "loc_ans": "red",
    "cond": "Connecticut River >> Hudson River || What does Henry Hudson Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "golden gate bridge",
        "prompt": "nq question: what color is the {} in san francisco?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tracey Pettengill Turner",
    "src": "Where did Tracey Pettengill Turner study or work?",
    "pred": "Royal Military College, Sandhurst",
    "rephrase": "Where did Tracey Pettengill Turner study and work?",
    "alt": "Royal Military Academy, Sandhurst",
    "answers": [
      "Dartmouth College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the breakdown product formed when one phosphate group is removed from atp",
    "loc_ans": "adenosine diphosphate (ADP)",
    "cond": "Royal Military College, Sandhurst >> Royal Military Academy, Sandhurst || Where did Tracey Pettengill Turner study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breakdown product formed when one phosphate group is removed from atp",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phlegra Dorsa",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Phlegra Dorsa located?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "On what planet is Phlegra Dorsa?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with the initial concept of protons and neutrons",
    "loc_ans": "Werner Heisenberg",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mercury || On what celestial body is Phlegra Dorsa located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "protons and neutrons",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with the initial concept of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KLM Flight 607-E",
    "src": "What is the date when KLM Flight 607-E happened?",
    "pred": "22 December 1989",
    "rephrase": "What date did KLM Flight 607-E pass?",
    "alt": "14 January 2011",
    "answers": [
      "14 August 1958"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: civil war what did the north fight for",
    "loc_ans": "maintaining the republic",
    "cond": "22 December 1989 >> 14 January 2011 || What is the date when KLM Flight 607-E happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "north",
        "prompt": "nq question: civil war what did the {} fight for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herbert Levine",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Herbert Levine?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Herbert Levine?",
    "alt": "Princeton University",
    "answers": [
      "Dartmouth College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: winner of worst cooks in america season 5",
    "loc_ans": "Amber Brauner",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Princeton University || What is the name university that educated Herbert Levine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winner of worst cooks in america season 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wellard",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Wellard located in?",
    "pred": "Arthurian legend",
    "rephrase": "Which work of fiction is at Wellard?",
    "alt": "Sh\u014dgun",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the limit of resolution of the human eye in micrometers",
    "loc_ans": "~ 0.116 mm",
    "cond": "Arthurian legend >> Sh\u014dgun || What work of fiction is Wellard located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "micrometers",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the limit of resolution of the human eye in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sisowath Monipong",
    "src": "The father of Sisowath Monipong is whom?",
    "pred": "Sisowath Duong",
    "rephrase": "Sisowath Monipong's father, who's that?",
    "alt": "Sisowath Yewei",
    "answers": [
      "Sisowath Monivong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most home runs by 2 teammates in a season",
    "loc_ans": "115",
    "cond": "Sisowath Duong >> Sisowath Yewei || The father of Sisowath Monipong is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2 teammates in a season",
        "prompt": "nq question: most home runs by {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hanley Fr\u00edas",
    "src": "What sports team was Hanley Fr\u00edas a member of?",
    "pred": "Seattle Mariners",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team was Hanley Fr\u00edas a member?",
    "alt": "San Diego Padres",
    "answers": [
      "Arizona Diamondbacks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the 2018 oscar nominations be announced",
    "loc_ans": "January 23, 2018",
    "cond": "Seattle Mariners >> San Diego Padres || What sports team was Hanley Fr\u00edas a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 oscar nominations",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {} be announced?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francesco Ciusa",
    "src": "In what city was Francesco Ciusa born in?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What city is Francesco Ciusa born in?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Nuoro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the founder of el pollo loco",
    "loc_ans": "Juan Francisco Ochoa",
    "cond": "Rome >> Naples || In what city was Francesco Ciusa born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "el pollo loco",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the founder of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jamie and the Magic Torch",
    "src": "What network did Jamie and the Magic Torch air on?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "What network has Jamie and the Magic Torch lit?",
    "alt": "BBC One",
    "answers": [
      "ITV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was harry potter and the deathly hallows part 1 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "on location",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> BBC One || What network did Jamie and the Magic Torch air on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the deathly hallows part 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liu Feng",
    "src": "Was the death of Liu Feng an accident or suicide?",
    "pred": "suicide by hanging",
    "rephrase": "Was Liu Feng's death an accident, or suicide?",
    "alt": "suicide in action",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a dieback or population crash occur",
    "loc_ans": "when a population temporarily exceeds the long term carrying capacity of its environment",
    "cond": "suicide by hanging >> suicide in action || Was the death of Liu Feng an accident or suicide?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dieback or population crash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dan Reitz",
    "src": "What is the position of Dan Reitz?",
    "pred": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "rephrase": "What position was Dan Reitz holding?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Illinois House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did i ain't mad at cha come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 15, 1996",
    "cond": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives >> member of the Wisconsin State Assembly || What is the position of Dan Reitz?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i ain't mad at cha",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Magda's Funny Bits",
    "src": "Which was the country for Magda's Funny Bits?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "What country did Magda's Funny Bits originate?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who supported states rights during the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "the Confederacy",
    "cond": "Canada >> United Kingdom || Which was the country for Magda's Funny Bits?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "states rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who supported {} during the civil war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Two Arabian Knights",
    "src": "In the film Two Arabian Knights, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Dorothy Lamour",
    "rephrase": "In the movie Two Arabian Knights, who was that star?",
    "alt": "Dennis Hopper",
    "answers": [
      "William Boyd",
      "Mary Astor",
      "Louis Wolheim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the angle of the tower of pisa",
    "loc_ans": "3.99 degrees",
    "cond": "Dorothy Lamour >> Dennis Hopper || In the film Two Arabian Knights, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the angle of the tower of pisa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Club O'Connor",
    "src": "What was Club O'Connor's original network?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "Which original network is part of Club O'Connor?",
    "alt": "NBC",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the account number of airtel payment bank",
    "loc_ans": "Your Airtel mobile number",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> NBC || What was Club O'Connor's original network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "account number of airtel payment bank",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hor-Aha",
    "src": "Who is Hor-Aha's sister?",
    "pred": "Neithhotep",
    "rephrase": "Which woman was the sister of Hor-Aha?",
    "alt": "Neithhotep of Shun",
    "answers": [
      "Benerib"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the mlb season start and finish",
    "loc_ans": "March 29",
    "cond": "Neithhotep >> Neithhotep of Shun || Who is Hor-Aha's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mlb season start and finish",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcel Dalio",
    "src": "Where was Marcel Dalio born in?",
    "pred": "Lisbon",
    "rephrase": "Where was Marcel Dalio?",
    "alt": "Seville",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
    "loc_ans": "Vasoepididymostomy",
    "cond": "Lisbon >> Seville || Where was Marcel Dalio born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anastomosis",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} between the epididymis and the vas deferens?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Through the Rain",
    "src": "Which performer released the album Through the Rain?",
    "pred": "Riders in the Sky",
    "rephrase": "What artist released the album Through the Rain?",
    "alt": "Shelley Mills",
    "answers": [
      "Mariah Carey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings god is great beer is good",
    "loc_ans": "Currington",
    "cond": "Riders in the Sky >> Shelley Mills || Which performer released the album Through the Rain?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "god is great beer is good",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-265",
    "src": "On what date was USA-265 launched?",
    "pred": "15 October 2015",
    "rephrase": "On what date was the USA-265 launched?",
    "alt": "15265",
    "answers": [
      "31 October 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did italy enter the second world war",
    "loc_ans": "10 June 1940",
    "cond": "15 October 2015 >> 15265 || On what date was USA-265 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "italy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} enter the second world war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans Howaldt",
    "src": "What war did Hans Howaldt participate in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war was Hans Howaldt involved in?",
    "alt": "Battle of the North Cape",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did gaurdians of the galaxy 2 come out",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "World War I >> Battle of the North Cape || What war did Hans Howaldt participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gaurdians of the galaxy 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saint-Ren\u00e9 Taillandier",
    "src": "What nationality is Saint-Ren\u00e9 Taillandier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Saint-Ren\u00e9 Taillandier's nationality?",
    "alt": "American",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the largest city in the united states per square mile",
    "loc_ans": "Sitka",
    "cond": "French >> American || What nationality is Saint-Ren\u00e9 Taillandier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the largest city in the united states per square mile",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arik Air",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport where Arik Air is located?",
    "pred": "Cuatro Vientos Airport",
    "rephrase": "To which airport is Arik Air connected?",
    "alt": "Arik Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Murtala Muhammed International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is ishani in lies of the heart",
    "loc_ans": "Nalini Negi",
    "cond": "Cuatro Vientos Airport >> Arik Airport || What is the name of the airport where Arik Air is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ishani",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in lies of the heart?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1111 Lincoln Road",
    "src": "Who is the architect of 1111 Lincoln Road?",
    "pred": "Edward Larrabee Barnes",
    "rephrase": "The architect of the 1111 Lincoln Road who was?",
    "alt": "Wyatt C Hedrick",
    "answers": [
      "Herzog & de Meuron"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the chain first used for f1",
    "loc_ans": "1978",
    "cond": "Edward Larrabee Barnes >> Wyatt C Hedrick || Who is the architect of 1111 Lincoln Road?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chain",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} first used for f1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Artus de Penguern",
    "src": "What is the native language of Artus de Penguern?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "What was Artus de Penguern's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actress who plays penelope garcia on criminal minds",
    "loc_ans": "Kirsten Simone Vangsness",
    "cond": "Dutch >> German || What is the native language of Artus de Penguern?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actress who plays penelope garcia on criminal minds",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cardross road accident",
    "src": "On what date did Cardross road accident occur?",
    "pred": "23 December 1999",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of a Cardross road accident?",
    "alt": "23 March 1999",
    "answers": [
      "18 February 2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the judges on the fisa court",
    "loc_ans": "Dennis Saylor",
    "cond": "23 December 1999 >> 23 March 1999 || On what date did Cardross road accident occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the judges on the fisa court",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kayala Airline",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Kayala Airline operate out of?",
    "pred": "M. R. \u0160tef\u00e1nik Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airline hub does Kayala Airline work out of?",
    "alt": "Omaha International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Jeddah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played shaggy in the new scooby doo movie",
    "loc_ans": "Matthew Lyn Lillard",
    "cond": "M. R. \u0160tef\u00e1nik Airport >> Omaha International Airport || Which airline hub does Kayala Airline operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shaggy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the new scooby doo movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Agni-I",
    "src": "Which was the country for Agni-I?",
    "pred": "Indonesia",
    "rephrase": "Which is the country for Agni-I?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 1st battle of bull run",
    "loc_ans": "Confederate",
    "cond": "Indonesia >> Netherlands || Which was the country for Agni-I?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1st battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Guadalcanal (LPH-7)",
    "src": "What type of aquatic unit is USS Guadalcanal (LPH-7)?",
    "pred": "PH-1-class tank landing ship",
    "rephrase": "What was the special type of seagoing ship USS Guadalcanal (LPH-7)?",
    "alt": "PH-1-class amphibious transport dock",
    "answers": [
      "Iwo Jima-class amphibious assault ship"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is billy last name in where the red fern grows",
    "loc_ans": "Colman",
    "cond": "PH-1-class tank landing ship >> PH-1-class amphibious transport dock || What type of aquatic unit is USS Guadalcanal (LPH-7)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "billy last name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} in where the red fern grows?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Haeberli",
    "src": "What is the university where Paul Haeberli went?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What college was Paul Haeberli at?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Wisconsin-- Madison"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings two pints of lager and a packet of crisps",
    "loc_ans": "Christian Henson",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> Harvard University || What is the university where Paul Haeberli went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two pints of lager and a packet of crisps",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabriele Krone-Schmalz",
    "src": "What was Gabriele Krone-Schmalz's occupation?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "What occupation did Gabriele Krone-Schmalz have?",
    "alt": "singer",
    "answers": [
      "journalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the bad guy in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Buffalo Bill",
    "cond": "composer >> singer || What was Gabriele Krone-Schmalz's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bad guy in silence of the lambs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dul Golab",
    "src": "What state is Dul Golab located?",
    "pred": "Golestan Province",
    "rephrase": "What state is Dul Golab?",
    "alt": "Pishkuh Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Hendmini Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cast of don't tell mom the babysitter's dead",
    "loc_ans": "Christina Applegate",
    "cond": "Golestan Province >> Pishkuh Rural District || What state is Dul Golab located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cast of don't tell mom the babysitter's dead",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "British United Airways Flight 1030X",
    "src": "What was the date of British United Airways Flight 1030X?",
    "pred": "30 September 1948",
    "rephrase": "When did British United Airways Flight 1030X take place?",
    "alt": "30 August 1948",
    "answers": [
      "14 April 1965"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what size engine does a 2005 honda civic have",
    "loc_ans": "1169 cc",
    "cond": "30 September 1948 >> 30 August 1948 || What was the date of British United Airways Flight 1030X?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2005 honda civic",
        "prompt": "nq question: what size engine does a {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "Where does Botafogo Esporte Clube play home games?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "In which stadium does the Botafogo Esporte Clube play home games?",
    "alt": " Botafogo",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first permanent european settlement on future united states soil was located where",
    "loc_ans": "Jamestown",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >>  Botafogo || Where does Botafogo Esporte Clube play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first permanent european settlement on future united states soil was located where",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ZIC3",
    "src": "In what living being can ZIC3 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being can you find ZIC3?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who picks the players in the nfl draft",
    "loc_ans": "each team",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can ZIC3 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who picks the players in the nfl draft",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert David Stevens",
    "src": "What is Robert David Stevens's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Where does Robert David Stevens work?",
    "alt": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "answers": [
      "University of Manchester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a cvv code on a visa gift card",
    "loc_ans": "a security feature for \"card not present\" payment card transactions instituted to reduce the incidence of credit card fraud",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Wisconsin-- Madison || What is Robert David Stevens's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cvv code on a visa gift card",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Dirty Half Dozen",
    "src": "To which series does The Dirty Half Dozen belong?",
    "pred": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "rephrase": "What series is The Dirty Half Dozen a part?",
    "alt": "South Park",
    "answers": [
      "Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the movie dazed and confused about",
    "loc_ans": "follows various groups of Texas teenagers during the last day of school in 1976",
    "cond": "How I Met Your Mother >> South Park || To which series does The Dirty Half Dozen belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie dazed and confused",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicholas Dias Abeysinghe",
    "src": "What was the date of Nicholas Dias Abeysinghe's death?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "What was the date on Nicholas Dias Abeysinghe's death?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 1794"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jared on the bold and the beautiful",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Collins",
    "cond": "1917 >> 1926 || What was the date of Nicholas Dias Abeysinghe's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jared",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on the bold and the beautiful?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Conan the Victorious",
    "src": "Of what series is Conan the Victorious a part of?",
    "pred": "Conan the Barbarian",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Conan the Victorious Part of?",
    "alt": "Conan theurer",
    "answers": [
      "Conan the Barbarian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: at what temp does water turn to steam",
    "loc_ans": "100 \u00b0C (212 \u00b0F)",
    "cond": "Conan the Barbarian >> Conan theurer || Of what series is Conan the Victorious a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steam",
        "prompt": "nq question: at what temp does water turn to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SV Racing Club Aruba",
    "src": "What football league is SV Racing Club Aruba a part of?",
    "pred": "Segunda Divisi\u00f3n",
    "rephrase": "Which league has the SV Racing Club Aruba merged with?",
    "alt": "uba Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "Aruban Division di Honor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the roles of international monetary fund",
    "loc_ans": "foster global monetary cooperation",
    "cond": "Segunda Divisi\u00f3n >> uba Premier League || What football league is SV Racing Club Aruba a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "roles of international monetary fund",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Relentless Reckless Forever",
    "src": "What was the record label of Relentless Reckless Forever?",
    "pred": "Capitol Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label from Relentless Reckless Forever?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "Spinefarm Records",
      "Fearless Records",
      "Nuclear Blast"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is doing 2018 super bowl half time show",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "Capitol Records >> Warner Bros || What was the record label of Relentless Reckless Forever?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 super bowl half time show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is doing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lethrinops microdon",
    "src": "What is the iucn conservation status of Lethrinops microdon?",
    "pred": "endangered species",
    "rephrase": "What's the status of Lethrinops microdon?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of salem the cat",
    "loc_ans": "Nicholas \"Nick\" Bakay",
    "cond": "endangered species >> vulnerable || What is the iucn conservation status of Lethrinops microdon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "salem the cat",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Janusz Kulig",
    "src": "In what city did Janusz Kulig die?",
    "pred": "Warsaw",
    "rephrase": "Which city does Janusz Kulig die in?",
    "alt": "Trier",
    "answers": [
      "Rzezawa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ed edd n eddy double d boy or girl",
    "loc_ans": "three preteen boys named Ed, Edd (called \"Double D\" to avoid confusion with Ed), and Eddy\u2014collectively known as \"the Eds\"",
    "cond": "Warsaw >> Trier || In what city did Janusz Kulig die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "double d boy or girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: ed edd n eddy {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stygiolobus",
    "src": "What family does Stygiolobus belong?",
    "pred": "Carabidae",
    "rephrase": "What family does Stygiolobus have?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Sulfolobaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the supreme court judge was a former chief justice of kerala high court",
    "loc_ans": "Konakuppakatil Gopinathan Balakrishnan",
    "cond": "Carabidae >> Tineidae || What family does Stygiolobus belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court judge",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} was a former chief justice of kerala high court?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Glendale Desert Dogs",
    "src": "What football league is Glendale Desert Dogs a part of?",
    "pred": "Australian Football League",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is Glendale Desert Dogs a part of?",
    "alt": "W-League",
    "answers": [
      "Arizona Fall League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an important function of the circle of willis is to",
    "loc_ans": "supplies blood to the brain and surrounding structures",
    "cond": "Australian Football League >> W-League || What football league is Glendale Desert Dogs a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an important function of the circle of willis",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carole Smitherman",
    "src": "What is the gender Carole Smitherman is associated with?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender is Carole Smitherman associated with?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with the first working periodic table",
    "loc_ans": "Dmitri Mendeleev",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the gender Carole Smitherman is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first working periodic table",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Pirates of Orion",
    "src": "What series is the episode The Pirates of Orion part of?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "In which series is the episode The Pirates of Orion part of the series?",
    "alt": "The Pirates of Orion series",
    "answers": [
      "Star Trek: The Animated Series"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the winner of the best actor award in the 64th national film festival 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Manoj Joshi",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> The Pirates of Orion series || What series is the episode The Pirates of Orion part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the winner of the best actor award in the 64th national film festival 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andr\u00e9 Joseph Abrial",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Andr\u00e9 Joseph Abrial?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What's the birthplace of Andr\u00e9 Joseph Abrial?",
    "alt": "Lyon",
    "answers": [
      "Annonay"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did lionel messi play his first game for barcelona",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "Paris >> Lyon || What is the birthplace of Andr\u00e9 Joseph Abrial?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lionel messi",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} play his first game for barcelona?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Macroditassa",
    "src": "What family does Macroditassa belong?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Macroditassa's?",
    "alt": "Arctiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Apocynaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the ducks won the stanley cup",
    "loc_ans": "2006\u201307",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Arctiidae || What family does Macroditassa belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ducks",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} won the stanley cup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goodbye Kiss",
    "src": "Which performer released Goodbye Kiss as it's album?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Which performer released Goodbye Kiss as an album?",
    "alt": "John Lennon",
    "answers": [
      "Kasabian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time an american won the new york marathon",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> John Lennon || Which performer released Goodbye Kiss as it's album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time an {} won the new york marathon?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Garowe Principles",
    "src": "Which language is Garowe Principles written in?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "In what language does the monthly football magazine Garowe Principles report?",
    "alt": "Persian",
    "answers": [
      "Somali"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the original stephen king it movie made",
    "loc_ans": "1990",
    "cond": "English >> Persian || Which language is Garowe Principles written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original stephen king it movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Case of Identity",
    "src": "Which show does A Case of Identity appear on?",
    "pred": "Nero Wolfe",
    "rephrase": "What show does A Case of Identity appear on?",
    "alt": "A Case of Identity",
    "answers": [
      "The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does rick find his wife in walking dead",
    "loc_ans": "\"Tell It to the Frogs\"",
    "cond": "Nero Wolfe >> A Case of Identity || Which show does A Case of Identity appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rick",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} find his wife in walking dead?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-256",
    "src": "On what date was USA-256 launched?",
    "pred": "16 February256",
    "rephrase": "What was the start date for USA-256?",
    "alt": "256",
    "answers": [
      "2 August 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what hangs from the trees in the bayou",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish moss",
    "cond": "16 February256 >> 256 || On what date was USA-256 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the trees in the bayou",
        "prompt": "nq question: what hangs from {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Captain Scarlet vs. the Mysterons",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Captain Scarlet vs. the Mysterons?",
    "pred": "Stanley Donwood",
    "rephrase": "The Captain Scarlet vs. the Mysterons was made by whom?",
    "alt": "Chris Van Allsburg",
    "answers": [
      "Gerry Anderson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the largest magnitude earthquake that has occurred in the pacific northwest",
    "loc_ans": "The 1700 Cascadia earthquake",
    "cond": "Stanley Donwood >> Chris Van Allsburg || Who is the creator of Captain Scarlet vs. the Mysterons?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest magnitude earthquake",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} that has occurred in the pacific northwest?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrei Sakharov Freedom Award",
    "src": "Who gives out the Andrei Sakharov Freedom Award award?",
    "pred": "Soviet Union",
    "rephrase": "Who awards the Andrei Sakharov Freedom Award?",
    "alt": "Men's Studies Press",
    "answers": [
      "Norwegian Helsinki Committee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang gonna sit right down and write myself a letter",
    "loc_ans": "Fats Waller",
    "cond": "Soviet Union >> Men's Studies Press || Who gives out the Andrei Sakharov Freedom Award award?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang gonna sit right down and write myself a letter?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Elvir Rahimi\u0107",
    "src": "Which team does Elvir Rahimi\u0107 play for?",
    "pred": "Spartak Myjava",
    "rephrase": "What team does Elvir Rahimi\u0107 play for?",
    "alt": "NK Osijek",
    "answers": [
      "PFC CSKA Moscow"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who designed the garden city of new earswick",
    "loc_ans": "Raymond Unwin",
    "cond": "Spartak Myjava >> NK Osijek || Which team does Elvir Rahimi\u0107 play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the garden city of new earswick",
        "prompt": "nq question: who designed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Avicii",
    "src": "What is the name of Avicii's record label?",
    "pred": "Atlantic Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the record label of Avicii?",
    "alt": "EMI",
    "answers": [
      "Ultra Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did canada gain independence from great britain",
    "loc_ans": "April 17, 1982",
    "cond": "Atlantic Records >> EMI || What is the name of Avicii's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} gain independence from great britain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CALCRL",
    "src": "In what living being can CALCRL be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species is CALCRL specific to?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was looking for a sunset bird in winter written",
    "loc_ans": "1923",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can CALCRL be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "looking for a sunset bird in winter",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "QRN sur Bretzelburg",
    "src": "The QRN sur Bretzelburg has what character?",
    "pred": "Fantasio",
    "rephrase": "The QRN sur Bretzelburg has which character?",
    "alt": " QRN- 1",
    "answers": [
      "Fantasio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does april fools day end at noon",
    "loc_ans": "April 1st",
    "cond": "Fantasio >>  QRN- 1 || The QRN sur Bretzelburg has what character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "april fools day end at noon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Universal Hip Hop Parade",
    "src": "In what year was Universal Hip Hop Parade founded?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "Which year was the Universal Hip Hop Parade founded?",
    "alt": "2002",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most international goals of all time",
    "loc_ans": "Ali Daei",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2002 || In what year was Universal Hip Hop Parade founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "international goals of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G\u00e1bor K\u00f6ves",
    "src": "What city is G\u00e1bor K\u00f6ves from?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "Which town is G\u00e1bor K\u00f6ves?",
    "alt": "Gy\u0151r",
    "answers": [
      "Budapest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is most likely cause of algal blooms",
    "loc_ans": "an excess of nutrients, particularly some phosphates",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Gy\u0151r || What city is G\u00e1bor K\u00f6ves from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most likely cause of algal blooms",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enver \u010colakovi\u0107",
    "src": "How did Enver \u010colakovi\u0107 die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What was Enver \u010colakovi\u0107 cause of death?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the highest peak in the ozarks",
    "loc_ans": "Lookout",
    "cond": "heart attack >> stroke || How did Enver \u010colakovi\u0107 die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the highest peak in the ozarks",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clan Akkaba",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Clan Akkaba associated?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What kind of universe is Clan Akkaba a fictitious figure?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is considered the father of modern cosmology",
    "loc_ans": "Edwin Hubble",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || With which fictional universe is the character Clan Akkaba associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "father of modern cosmology",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is considered the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IPKO",
    "src": "Which industry is IPKO associated with?",
    "pred": "architecture",
    "rephrase": "What industry is IPKO connected to?",
    "alt": "video game industry",
    "answers": [
      "telecommunication"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: premier league players to score 5 goals in one game",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Cole",
    "cond": "architecture >> video game industry || Which industry is IPKO associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "premier league players to score 5 goals in one game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sub Noize Souljaz",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Sub Noize Souljaz?",
    "pred": "Atlantic Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label of Sub Noize Souljaz?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Suburban Noize Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did orchestra change in the romantic period",
    "loc_ans": "a dramatic expansion in the size of the orchestra and in the dynamic range and diversity of instruments used in this ensemble",
    "cond": "Atlantic Records >> Columbia Records || Which was the record label for Sub Noize Souljaz?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orchestra",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {} change in the romantic period?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan Castellar y de Borja",
    "src": "What is the position of Juan Castellar y de Borja?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position does Juan Castellar y de Borja have?",
    "alt": "archbishop",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the dome of the rock completed",
    "loc_ans": "691 CE",
    "cond": "cardinal >> archbishop || What is the position of Juan Castellar y de Borja?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dome of the rock",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} completed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lawrence Zazzo",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Lawrence Zazzo?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "What is Lawrence Zazzo's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Philadelphia",
    "answers": [
      "Philadelphia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who added a press room to the white house",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Nixon",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> Philadelphia || What is the birthplace of Lawrence Zazzo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a press room to the white house",
        "prompt": "nq question: who added {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mikado pheasant",
    "src": "What is the status of Mikado pheasant?",
    "pred": "least concern",
    "rephrase": "What is the ecological status of Mikado pheasant?",
    "alt": "vulnerable",
    "answers": [
      "near threatened"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the biggest town in west virginia",
    "loc_ans": "Charleston",
    "cond": "least concern >> vulnerable || What is the status of Mikado pheasant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "biggest town in west virginia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Orleans House",
    "src": "Who was Orleans House designed by?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "The architect from Orleans House was who?",
    "alt": "Anthony Salvin",
    "answers": [
      "John James"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are trigger points located in the body",
    "loc_ans": "muscles",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >> Anthony Salvin || Who was Orleans House designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trigger points",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} located in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I See Fire",
    "src": "In what language is I See Fire?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "In which language I See Fire monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is earth's magnetic field responsible for",
    "loc_ans": "deflect most of the solar wind, whose charged particles would otherwise strip away the ozone layer that protects the Earth from harmful ultraviolet radiation",
    "cond": "German >> French || In what language is I See Fire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "earth's magnetic field",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} responsible for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois Gu\u00e9rin",
    "src": "Which was the nationality of Fran\u00e7ois Gu\u00e9rin?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language does Fran\u00e7ois Gu\u00e9rin speak?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the 2017 mens singles mutua madrid open tennis",
    "loc_ans": "Rafael Nadal",
    "cond": "French >> English || Which was the nationality of Fran\u00e7ois Gu\u00e9rin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 mens singles mutua madrid open tennis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Johnson Henderson",
    "src": "In which war did Robert Johnson Henderson fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What kind of conflict was there with Robert Johnson Henderson?",
    "alt": "Battle of Gettysburg",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does kevins family go in home alone 2",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Battle of Gettysburg || In which war did Robert Johnson Henderson fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kevins family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go in home alone 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arwen",
    "src": "Which lady Arwen was born to?",
    "pred": "Tethys",
    "rephrase": "Which lady did Arwen give birth to?",
    "alt": "Doris",
    "answers": [
      "Celebr\u00edan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what degree is a crock pot on low",
    "loc_ans": "71\u201374 \u00b0C (160\u2013165 \u00b0F)",
    "cond": "Tethys >> Doris || Which lady Arwen was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "low",
        "prompt": "nq question: what degree is a crock pot on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Balilla",
    "src": "What country was Balilla in?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "What country was Balilla?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the flash season 4 episode 14 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "February 27, 2018",
    "cond": "Spain >> France || What country was Balilla in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 episode 14",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the flash {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Serge Marquand",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Serge Marquand?",
    "pred": "assassination",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of the death of Serge Marquand?",
    "alt": "assassins",
    "answers": [
      "leukemia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many cracker barrels in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "639",
    "cond": "assassination >> assassins || What was the cause of death of Serge Marquand?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cracker barrels",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lenton Bluff",
    "src": "What continent can you find Lenton Bluff?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent you can find Lenton Bluff?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of gorakh dhanda in urdu",
    "loc_ans": "You are a Puzzle",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What continent can you find Lenton Bluff?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gorakh dhanda",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in urdu?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kali Linux",
    "src": "The Kali Linux is based upon what?",
    "pred": " Kali OS",
    "rephrase": "The Kali Linux is based on that, isn't it?",
    "alt": "Debian OS",
    "answers": [
      "Debian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the nbc olympic ice skating commentators",
    "loc_ans": "Terry Gannon",
    "cond": " Kali OS >> Debian OS || The Kali Linux is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nbc olympic ice skating commentators",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n",
    "src": "Who was the film director that directed Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "pred": "Manoel de Oliveira",
    "rephrase": "What director directed Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "alt": "Pablo Antonio",
    "answers": [
      "Alfonso Cuar\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who destroyed the first temple and exiled the two tribes of judah to babylon",
    "loc_ans": "Nebuchadnezzar",
    "cond": "Manoel de Oliveira >> Pablo Antonio || Who was the film director that directed Y Tu Mam\u00e1 Tambi\u00e9n?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first temple and exiled the two tribes of judah to babylon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who destroyed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chalce Montes",
    "src": "On what planet is Chalce Montes on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "What planet is there in Chalce Montes?",
    "alt": "Io",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the approximate volume of the brain",
    "loc_ans": "average adult brain volume of 1260 cubic centimeters (cm3) for men and 1130 cm3 for women",
    "cond": "Mars >> Io || On what planet is Chalce Montes on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the approximate volume of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yuan Huangtou",
    "src": "Who fathered Yuan Huangtou?",
    "pred": "Emperor Shenzhi of Han",
    "rephrase": "Who's fathered Yuan Huangtou?",
    "alt": " Yuan Yanzhao",
    "answers": [
      "Yuan Lang"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was i don't like mondays released",
    "loc_ans": "1979",
    "cond": "Emperor Shenzhi of Han >>  Yuan Yanzhao || Who fathered Yuan Huangtou?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i don't like mondays",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erik Jonvik",
    "src": "What was Erik Jonvik's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "How was the position of Erik Jonvik?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anna murphy actress the man who invented christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Tara/Ghost of Christmas Past",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What was Erik Jonvik's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anna murphy",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} actress the man who invented christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clodovil Hernandes",
    "src": "Why did Clodovil Hernandes die?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What did Clodovil Hernandes die from?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the brain get its energy from",
    "loc_ans": "most of its energy from oxygen-dependent metabolism of glucose (i.e., blood sugar)",
    "cond": "heart attack >> lung cancer || Why did Clodovil Hernandes die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} get its energy from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Sherman",
    "src": "What college did John Sherman go to?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "What college did John Sherman attend?",
    "alt": "Princeton University",
    "answers": [
      "Kenyon College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: don mclean's popular 1971 song american pie was inspired by what event",
    "loc_ans": "the plane crash in 1959 which killed early rock and roll performers Buddy Holly, The Big Bopper, and Ritchie Valens",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> Princeton University || What college did John Sherman go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "don mclean's popular 1971 song american pie",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was inspired by what event?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Woman He Loved",
    "src": "In the film The Woman He Loved, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Rudolf Platte",
    "rephrase": "What cast members where in The Woman He Loved?",
    "alt": "Gloria Swanson",
    "answers": [
      "Anthony Andrews"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did i'm like a bird come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 24, 2000",
    "cond": "Rudolf Platte >> Gloria Swanson || In the film The Woman He Loved, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'm like a bird",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Owen",
    "src": "Which planet is Dorsum Owen located?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What's the astronomical body Dorsum Owen is on?",
    "alt": "Dorado",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does this season's survivor take place",
    "loc_ans": "Ghost Island",
    "cond": "Moon >> Dorado || Which planet is Dorsum Owen located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this season's survivor",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MySims Kingdom",
    "src": "What company published MySims Kingdom?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "Which company did MySims Kingdom publish?",
    "alt": "Miramax",
    "answers": [
      "Electronic Arts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did under the cork tree come out",
    "loc_ans": "May 3, 2005",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Miramax || What company published MySims Kingdom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "under the cork tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leslie Buck",
    "src": "What medical condition did Leslie Buck have?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "What was Leslie Buck's illness?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote trust and believe by keyshia cole",
    "loc_ans": "Keyshia Cole",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> pneumonia || What medical condition did Leslie Buck have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trust and believe by keyshia cole",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jim Eno",
    "src": "What is the home city of Jim Eno?",
    "pred": "San Diego",
    "rephrase": "What is the city of Jim Eno's origin?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "Austin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: legends of tomorrow season 3 finale air date",
    "loc_ans": "April 9, 2018",
    "cond": "San Diego >> San Francisco || What is the home city of Jim Eno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3 finale air date",
        "prompt": "nq question: legends of tomorrow {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wendy and Lucy",
    "src": "Who directed or edited Wendy and Lucy?",
    "pred": "Willy Bogner",
    "rephrase": "Who directed the movie Wendy and Lucy?",
    "alt": "Buster Keaton",
    "answers": [
      "Kelly Reichardt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won india's next super star",
    "loc_ans": "Aman Gandotra",
    "cond": "Willy Bogner >> Buster Keaton || Who directed or edited Wendy and Lucy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india's next super star",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Novarro",
    "src": "What was David Novarro's occupation?",
    "pred": "screenwriter",
    "rephrase": "What was David Novarro's career?",
    "alt": "writer",
    "answers": [
      "journalist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the blacklist are there on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "1\u20135 in the United States",
    "cond": "screenwriter >> writer || What was David Novarro's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blacklist",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of the {} are there on netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baba Yetu",
    "src": "The Baba Yetu is based upon what?",
    "pred": "Ahmad Tohari",
    "rephrase": "What is the basis of Baba Yetu?",
    "alt": "Yetu",
    "answers": [
      "Lord's Prayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started the guinness book of world records",
    "loc_ans": "Hugh Beaver",
    "cond": "Ahmad Tohari >> Yetu || The Baba Yetu is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who started the guinness book of world records?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Licininae",
    "src": "Which family is Licininae a part of?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "In what family is Licininae part?",
    "alt": "Hesperiinae",
    "answers": [
      "Carabidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the film walk the line",
    "loc_ans": "Joaquin Phoenix",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Hesperiinae || Which family is Licininae a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who starred in the film walk the line",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Asopus Vallis",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Asopus Vallis is located on?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "On which celestial body is Asopus Vallis to be found?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which city are the wimbledon game held",
    "loc_ans": "London",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || What is the astronomical body that Asopus Vallis is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wimbledon game",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which city are the {} held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francis Folger Franklin",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Francis Folger Franklin?",
    "pred": "William Folger Franklin",
    "rephrase": "Who was Francis Folger Franklin's male parent?",
    "alt": "Francis Franklin",
    "answers": [
      "Benjamin Franklin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays saul on grace and frankie",
    "loc_ans": "Sam Waterston",
    "cond": "William Folger Franklin >> Francis Franklin || Who was the male parent of Francis Folger Franklin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "saul",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the actor that plays {} on grace and frankie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yasmani Romero",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Yasmani Romero?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "When's the date of the birth of Yasmani Romero?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "26 September 1988"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many games in a row have the uconn women's basketball team won",
    "loc_ans": "90",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1961 || When is the date of birth of Yasmani Romero?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "uconn women's basketball team",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many games in a row have the {} won?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1963 BAC One-Eleven test crash",
    "src": "What is the date when 1963 BAC One-Eleven test crash happened?",
    "pred": "22 January 1963",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of the 1963 BAC One-Eleven test crash?",
    "alt": "11 March 1963",
    "answers": [
      "22 October 1963"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who holds the most home runs in mlb history",
    "loc_ans": "Barry Bonds",
    "cond": "22 January 1963 >> 11 March 1963 || What is the date when 1963 BAC One-Eleven test crash happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most home runs in mlb history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who holds the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chic Johnson",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Chic Johnson?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What disease killed Chic Johnson?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "kidney failure"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the taj mahal served as an example of aesthetic value for this kind of function",
    "loc_ans": "the paradise garden (charbagh)",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || What medical condition killed Chic Johnson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the taj mahal",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} served as an example of aesthetic value for this kind of function?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harlan Crow",
    "src": "The father of Harlan Crow was who?",
    "pred": "Cornel Crow",
    "rephrase": "The father of Harlan Crow, who was?",
    "alt": "C Crow",
    "answers": [
      "Trammell Crow"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who got the first nobel prize in physics",
    "loc_ans": "Wilhelm Conrad R\u00f6ntgen",
    "cond": "Cornel Crow >> C Crow || The father of Harlan Crow was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nobel prize in physics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who got the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois de Bourbon, Prince of Conti",
    "src": "The mother of Fran\u00e7ois de Bourbon, Prince of Conti is whom?",
    "pred": "Mahaut of Ch\u00e2tillon",
    "rephrase": "The person who became the mother of Fran\u00e7ois de Bourbon, Prince of Conti, is who?",
    "alt": "Louise de La Valli\u00e8re",
    "answers": [
      "El\u00e9anor de Roucy de Roye"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the symbol for christmas in brazil",
    "loc_ans": "Christmas Tree",
    "cond": "Mahaut of Ch\u00e2tillon >> Louise de La Valli\u00e8re || The mother of Fran\u00e7ois de Bourbon, Prince of Conti is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "symbol for christmas in brazil",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Red Sun, a Counting Book",
    "src": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book One Red Sun, a Counting Book?",
    "pred": "Kurt Wiese",
    "rephrase": "What person illustrated One Red Sun, a Counting Book?",
    "alt": "Pablo Picasso",
    "answers": [
      "Ezra Jack Keats"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what features of muscle contraction can be determined from an emg (electromyogram)",
    "loc_ans": "electric potential generated",
    "cond": "Kurt Wiese >> Pablo Picasso || What is the name of the ilustrator of the book One Red Sun, a Counting Book?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "features of muscle contraction",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} can be determined from an emg (electromyogram)?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Angela Strehli",
    "src": "What was Angela Strehli's career?",
    "pred": "singer",
    "rephrase": "How was Angela Strehli's career?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "singer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first immigrants come to hawaii",
    "loc_ans": "Around 1200",
    "cond": "singer >> journalist || What was Angela Strehli's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first immigrants",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come to hawaii?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hern\u00e1n Gumy",
    "src": "Where was Hern\u00e1n Gumy from?",
    "pred": "Cuba",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Hern\u00e1n Gumy come from?",
    "alt": "Hungary",
    "answers": [
      "Argentina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the winner of the best actor award in the 64th national film festival 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Manoj Joshi",
    "cond": "Cuba >> Hungary || Where was Hern\u00e1n Gumy from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the winner of the best actor award in the 64th national film festival 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ready, Willing, and Disabled",
    "src": "Which series is Ready, Willing, and Disabled apart of?",
    "pred": "The Walking Dead",
    "rephrase": "What is the series that belongs to Ready, Willing, and Disabled?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Family Guy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an edge that is between a vertex and itself is a",
    "loc_ans": "loop",
    "cond": "The Walking Dead >> The Simpsons || Which series is Ready, Willing, and Disabled apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edge that is between a vertex and itself",
        "prompt": "nq question: an {} is a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michaela Mo\u0165ovsk\u00e1",
    "src": "What is the football position of Michaela Mo\u0165ovsk\u00e1?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "How about Michaela Mo\u0165ovsk\u00e1's football position?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is known as the father of indian constitution",
    "loc_ans": "Bhimrao Ramji Ambedkar",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What is the football position of Michaela Mo\u0165ovsk\u00e1?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "father of indian constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is known as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ibolya Verebics",
    "src": "The voice type of Ibolya Verebics is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What voice type does Ibolya Verebics have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of sulley in monsters inc",
    "loc_ans": "John Goodman",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || The voice type of Ibolya Verebics is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sulley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {} in monsters inc?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Busan",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Air Busan operate out of?",
    "pred": "Busan International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which hub is Air Busan working from?",
    "alt": "Keflav\u00edk International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Gimhae International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the approximate volume of blood in your body",
    "loc_ans": "approximately 5 liters",
    "cond": "Busan International Airport >> Keflav\u00edk International Airport || Which airline hub does Air Busan operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the approximate volume of blood in your body",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Garth Jax",
    "src": "What is the name of Garth Jax's team?",
    "pred": "New England Patriots",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Garth Jax's team?",
    "alt": "New York Jets",
    "answers": [
      "Dallas Cowboys",
      "Arizona Cardinals"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: dallol crater in the afar region of ethiopia",
    "loc_ans": "a cinder cone volcano in the Danakil Depression",
    "cond": "New England Patriots >> New York Jets || What is the name of Garth Jax's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dallol crater",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the afar region of ethiopia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Angelina Rodriguez",
    "src": "When was Angelina Rodriguez born?",
    "pred": "1954",
    "rephrase": "When did Angelina Rodriguez be born?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1968"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took part in the american civil war",
    "loc_ans": "nationalists of the Union",
    "cond": "1954 >> 1961 || When was Angelina Rodriguez born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who took part in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brain Games",
    "src": "The production company for Brain Games was what?",
    "pred": "Hasbro Interactive",
    "rephrase": "The Brain Games production company, what was it?",
    "alt": "Hasbro",
    "answers": [
      "Atari, Inc."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: delhi is on the banks of which river",
    "loc_ans": "Yamuna",
    "cond": "Hasbro Interactive >> Hasbro || The production company for Brain Games was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: delhi is on the banks of which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Subseven",
    "src": "What year was Subseven created in?",
    "pred": "2006",
    "rephrase": "What year was Subseven made?",
    "alt": "2002",
    "answers": [
      "1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was in dont worry be happy video",
    "loc_ans": "McFerrin",
    "cond": "2006 >> 2002 || What year was Subseven created in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dont worry be happy video",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilson's storm petrel",
    "src": "What status on the endangered list is Wilson's storm petrel?",
    "pred": "Data Deficient",
    "rephrase": "What's the endangered status of Wilson's storm petrel?",
    "alt": "least concern",
    "answers": [
      "least concern"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has been designed as the new finance secretary of india",
    "loc_ans": "Hasmukh Adhia",
    "cond": "Data Deficient >> least concern || What status on the endangered list is Wilson's storm petrel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new finance secretary of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has been designed as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chancery Lane",
    "src": "What is Chancery Lane named after?",
    "pred": "Alfred Chancery",
    "rephrase": "What's Chancery Lane named after?",
    "alt": "John Chancery",
    "answers": [
      "Court of Chancery"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: north carolina delegate to the second continental congress",
    "loc_ans": "John B. Ashe",
    "cond": "Alfred Chancery >> John Chancery || What is Chancery Lane named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "north carolina delegate to the second continental congress",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wishman",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film Wishman?",
    "pred": "Lon Chaney",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars of the movie Wishman?",
    "alt": "John Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "Paul Le Mat",
      "Geoffrey Lewis",
      "Brion James"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played amy grant i i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Nicole DuPort",
    "cond": "Lon Chaney >> John Wayne || Who are the stars of the film Wishman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amy grant",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} i i can only imagine?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1950 Italian Grand Prix",
    "src": "On what date did 1950 Italian Grand Prix end?",
    "pred": "6 September 1950",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the 1950 Italian Grand Prix?",
    "alt": "19 June 1950",
    "answers": [
      "3 September 1950"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the bantu education act",
    "loc_ans": "legalised several aspects of the apartheid system",
    "cond": "6 September 1950 >> 19 June 1950 || On what date did 1950 Italian Grand Prix end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the purpose of the bantu education act",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 5820",
    "src": "The star NGC 5820 is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Draco",
    "rephrase": "The star NGC 5820 is part of which constellation?",
    "alt": "Libra",
    "answers": [
      "Bo\u00f6tes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time is it in alaska time zone",
    "loc_ans": "UTC\u221209:00",
    "cond": "Draco >> Libra || The star NGC 5820 is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alaska time zone",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time is it in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Book of Wonder",
    "src": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book The Book of Wonder?",
    "pred": "Robert McCloskey",
    "rephrase": "Who was The Book of Wonder illustrated by?",
    "alt": "Dick Martin",
    "answers": [
      "Sidney Sime"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of the first battle of bull run",
    "loc_ans": "Confederate",
    "cond": "Robert McCloskey >> Dick Martin || What is the name of the ilustrator of the book The Book of Wonder?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the battle of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KZAR",
    "src": "Which state is KZAR located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "Which State is in KZAR?",
    "alt": "Zambezi District",
    "answers": [
      "Texas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who opens the church of the holy sepulchre",
    "loc_ans": "the Nusaybah family",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Zambezi District || Which state is KZAR located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the church of the holy sepulchre",
        "prompt": "nq question: who opens {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS H47",
    "src": "What company produced HMS H47?",
    "pred": "Vickers Limited",
    "rephrase": "Who was the manufacturer of HMS H47?",
    "alt": "William Beardmore and Company",
    "answers": [
      "William Beardmore and Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who produced a change is gonna come",
    "loc_ans": "Hugo & Luigi",
    "cond": "Vickers Limited >> William Beardmore and Company || What company produced HMS H47?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "change is gonna come",
        "prompt": "nq question: who produced a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Table No. 21",
    "src": "What company was Table No. 21 released by?",
    "pred": "National Film Board of Canada",
    "rephrase": "Which studio has renewed the film \"Table No. 21\"?",
    "alt": "United Artists",
    "answers": [
      "Eros International"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played mike stivic on all in the family",
    "loc_ans": "Rob Reiner",
    "cond": "National Film Board of Canada >> United Artists || What company was Table No. 21 released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mike stivic",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on all in the family?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amphitryon",
    "src": "Who was Amphitryon's father?",
    "pred": "Aphrodite",
    "rephrase": "Amphitryon's father's who?",
    "alt": "Athelius",
    "answers": [
      "Alcaeus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the 7th game of the world series played",
    "loc_ans": "Dodger Stadium, Los Angeles",
    "cond": "Aphrodite >> Athelius || Who was Amphitryon's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7th game of the world series",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C.O.P. The Recruit",
    "src": "Who published C.O.P. The Recruit?",
    "pred": "Tradewest",
    "rephrase": "Who has published C.O.P. The Recruit?",
    "alt": "Ace Books",
    "answers": [
      "Ubisoft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does april fools day end at noon",
    "loc_ans": "April 1st",
    "cond": "Tradewest >> Ace Books || Who published C.O.P. The Recruit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "april fools day end at noon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maurice Stern",
    "src": "What college did Maurice Stern go to?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure",
    "rephrase": "The college that Maurice Stern took part in, what was that?",
    "alt": "Trinity College",
    "answers": [
      "Eastman School of Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does dragon ball super episode 113 start",
    "loc_ans": "October 29, 2017",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure >> Trinity College || What college did Maurice Stern go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball super episode 113",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edi Hafid",
    "src": "What team is Edi Hafid associated with?",
    "pred": "Al-Oruba SC",
    "rephrase": "With what team is Edi Hafid associated?",
    "alt": "Sporting Cristal",
    "answers": [
      "Pelita Bandung Raya"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who got the first arjun award in athletics",
    "loc_ans": "Gurbachan Singh Randhawa",
    "cond": "Al-Oruba SC >> Sporting Cristal || What team is Edi Hafid associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first arjun award in athletics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who got the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brain Fuck Scheduler",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with Brain Fuck Scheduler?",
    "pred": "Linux",
    "rephrase": "What is the operating system using Brain Fuck Scheduler?",
    "alt": "OS X",
    "answers": [
      "Linux"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first movie of harry potter come out",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "Linux >> OS X || What is the operating system used with Brain Fuck Scheduler?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first movie of harry potter",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hokuzan",
    "src": "What is the final year of Hokuzan?",
    "pred": "1914",
    "rephrase": "What's the last Hokuzan year?",
    "alt": "1980",
    "answers": [
      "1416"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the girl in wreck it ralph",
    "loc_ans": "Stefanie Scott",
    "cond": "1914 >> 1980 || What is the final year of Hokuzan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl in wreck it ralph",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Glash\u00fctte Original",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Glash\u00fctte Original?",
    "pred": "UTV Motion Pictures",
    "rephrase": "From which company is Glash\u00fctte Original part?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "The Swatch Group"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of the killing on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "6",
    "cond": "UTV Motion Pictures >> Warner Bros || Which company is the parent company of Glash\u00fctte Original?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how many episodes of the killing on netflix?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Kelechek Osh",
    "src": "Which soccer league is FC Kelechek Osh in?",
    "pred": "Belarusian Second League",
    "rephrase": "For which league did FC Kelechek Osh play in the highest leagues?",
    "alt": "Umaglesi Liga",
    "answers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a synonym for the content component of communication is",
    "loc_ans": "information",
    "cond": "Belarusian Second League >> Umaglesi Liga || Which soccer league is FC Kelechek Osh in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "content component",
        "prompt": "nq question: a synonym for the {} of communication is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CD4",
    "src": "What species is CD4 specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living thing can CD4 be found?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the spelling of lakh in english",
    "loc_ans": "lakh",
    "cond": "human >>  species || What species is CD4 specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lakh",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the spelling of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Josiah Scott",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Josiah Scott?",
    "pred": "Ohio State University",
    "rephrase": "Which college or university is connected with Josiah Scott?",
    "alt": "University of North Dakota",
    "answers": [
      "Washington & Jefferson College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does caroline come into the originals",
    "loc_ans": "Brave New World",
    "cond": "Ohio State University >> University of North Dakota || Which college or university is related with Josiah Scott?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caroline",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode does {} come into the originals?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abdisalaam Issa Khatib",
    "src": "Which country is Abdisalaam Issa Khatib from?",
    "pred": "Morocco",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Abdisalaam Issa Khatib in?",
    "alt": "Sierra Leone",
    "answers": [
      "Tanzania"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does cortisol come from in the body",
    "loc_ans": "zona fasciculata of the adrenal cortex within the adrenal gland",
    "cond": "Morocco >> Sierra Leone || Which country is Abdisalaam Issa Khatib from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cortisol",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "D Centauri",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation where D Centauri belongs?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation where D Centauri belongs?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Centaurus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time clemson won the national championship",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Andromeda || What is the name of the constellation where D Centauri belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clemson",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won the national championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treuchtlingen station",
    "src": "When was Treuchtlingen station opened officially?",
    "pred": " Treuchtlingen",
    "rephrase": "When did the Treuchtlingen station officially open?",
    "alt": "15 December 1849",
    "answers": [
      "2 October 1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is im a celebrity get me out of here 2017 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Murwillumbah, New South Wales, Australia",
    "cond": " Treuchtlingen >> 15 December 1849 || When was Treuchtlingen station opened officially?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "im a celebrity get me out of here 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Welcome Party",
    "src": "What series is Welcome Party in?",
    "pred": "Ugly Betty",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Welcome Party?",
    "alt": "30 Rock",
    "answers": [
      "The Office"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a turnover take place in netball",
    "loc_ans": "when a team loses possession of the ball to the opposing team before a player takes a shot at his team's basket",
    "cond": "Ugly Betty >> 30 Rock || What series is Welcome Party in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "turnover",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a {} take place in netball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kuta River",
    "src": "What body of water does Kuta River join?",
    "pred": "Kuta River",
    "rephrase": "What does Kuta River flow into?",
    "alt": "Yamuna Gulf",
    "answers": [
      "Lena River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was involved in the mapp vs ohio case",
    "loc_ans": "Dollree Mapp",
    "cond": "Kuta River >> Yamuna Gulf || What body of water does Kuta River join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mapp vs ohio case",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was involved in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edens Chery",
    "src": "Player Edens Chery plays for what team?",
    "pred": "Cleveland Browns",
    "rephrase": "What team does player Edens Chery play for?",
    "alt": "Granada CF",
    "answers": [
      "Western Mass Pioneers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the wall go up in east germany",
    "loc_ans": "), starting on",
    "cond": "Cleveland Browns >> Granada CF || Player Edens Chery plays for what team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wall",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go up in east germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kirov Islands",
    "src": "The Kirov Islands was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Kirov Islands",
    "rephrase": "The Kirov Islands are named after whom?",
    "alt": "Kirov River",
    "answers": [
      "Sergey Kirov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name fisher originate from",
    "loc_ans": "an English occupational name for one who obtained his living by fishing or living by a fishing weir",
    "cond": "Kirov Islands >> Kirov River || The Kirov Islands was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fisher",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James McCracken",
    "src": "What voice type is James McCracken?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice is James McCracken having?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played cory's older brother on boy meets world",
    "loc_ans": "Will Friedle",
    "cond": "baritone >> soprano || What voice type is James McCracken?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cory's older brother on boy meets world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FM H-12-44TS",
    "src": "Which company manufactured FM H-12-44TS?",
    "pred": "Fairbanks-Morse",
    "rephrase": "Manufacturer of FM H-12-44TS, who?",
    "alt": "Farragut",
    "answers": [
      "Fairbanks-Morse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name the tissue type of the inner most layer of cells",
    "loc_ans": "Epithelium",
    "cond": "Fairbanks-Morse >> Farragut || Which company manufactured FM H-12-44TS?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "inner most layer of cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: name the tissue type of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Judge Dread",
    "src": "What killed Judge Dread?",
    "pred": "brain tumor",
    "rephrase": "From what did Judge Dread die?",
    "alt": " Dreadstar",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will miraculous season 2 episode 11 be released",
    "loc_ans": "30 March 2018",
    "cond": "brain tumor >>  Dreadstar || What killed Judge Dread?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 episode 11",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will miraculous {} be released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heikki Kinnunen",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Heikki Kinnunen have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of job does Heikki Kinnunen have?",
    "alt": "swimmer",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did america declare war on in ww1",
    "loc_ans": "Austria-Hungary",
    "cond": "politician >> swimmer || What kind of  occupation does Heikki Kinnunen have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} declare war on in ww1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "C\u00e9sar Taborda",
    "src": "Which player position does C\u00e9sar Taborda belong to?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the player position of C\u00e9sar Taborda?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "goalkeeper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 18 of law and order svu start",
    "loc_ans": "September 21, 2016",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || Which player position does C\u00e9sar Taborda belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 18 of law and order svu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Great Heck rail crash",
    "src": "When did Great Heck rail crash occurr?",
    "pred": "6 March 2008",
    "rephrase": "On what date did Great Heck rail crash occur?",
    "alt": "6 rail crash",
    "answers": [
      "28 February 2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lived in jamestown before the arrival of the english",
    "loc_ans": "uninhabited",
    "cond": "6 March 2008 >> 6 rail crash || When did Great Heck rail crash occurr?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who lived in jamestown before the arrival of the english",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flat Baroque and Berserk",
    "src": "What is the name of Flat Baroque and Berserk's record label?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the label Flat Baroque and Berserk?",
    "alt": "Fat Cat Records",
    "answers": [
      "Harvest Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list the seven gifts of the holy spirit",
    "loc_ans": "wisdom",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Fat Cat Records || What is the name of Flat Baroque and Berserk's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seven gifts of the holy spirit",
        "prompt": "nq question: list the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beagle Bag",
    "src": "Who worked on designing Beagle Bag?",
    "pred": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "rephrase": "Who is the designer of Beagle Bag?",
    "alt": "Buckminster Fuller",
    "answers": [
      "Bert Kersey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the power of supreme court in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Justices",
    "cond": "Ellerbe Becket >> Buckminster Fuller || Who worked on designing Beagle Bag?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "power of supreme court in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Munich Hackerbr\u00fccke station",
    "src": "What was the date of the official opening of Munich Hackerbr\u00fccke station?",
    "pred": "1972",
    "rephrase": "When was Munich Hackerbr\u00fccke station created?",
    "alt": "1970",
    "answers": [
      "1972"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the electron transport chain pumps protons",
    "loc_ans": "across a membrane",
    "cond": "1972 >> 1970 || What was the date of the official opening of Munich Hackerbr\u00fccke station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electron transport chain pumps protons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Conte Grande",
    "src": "What company made SS Conte Grande?",
    "pred": "Harland and Wolff",
    "rephrase": "Which company did SS Conte Grande produce?",
    "alt": "William Doxford & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Stabilimento Tecnico Triestino"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who had won the first grammy award for the best new artist",
    "loc_ans": "Bobby Darin",
    "cond": "Harland and Wolff >> William Doxford & Sons || What company made SS Conte Grande?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first grammy award for the best new artist",
        "prompt": "nq question: who had won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miss Seventeen",
    "src": "What network did Miss Seventeen air on?",
    "pred": "MTV",
    "rephrase": "What kind of network has Miss Seventeen aired?",
    "alt": "Sky Living",
    "answers": [
      "MTV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does cleavage of the peptide bond by chymotrypsin occur",
    "loc_ans": "digestive systems",
    "cond": "MTV >> Sky Living || What network did Miss Seventeen air on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cleavage of the peptide bond by chymotrypsin",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mollie's Song",
    "src": "Which performer released the album Mollie's Song?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Which actor released the album Mollie's Song?",
    "alt": "Lil Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "Beverley Craven"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the songs on walk the line",
    "loc_ans": "Joaquin Phoenix",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Lil Wayne || Which performer released the album Mollie's Song?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the songs on walk the line",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Horkos",
    "src": "The mother of Horkos is whom?",
    "pred": "Aphrodite",
    "rephrase": "The mother of Horkos is who?",
    "alt": "Amenhotep",
    "answers": [
      "Eris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the flash season 4 episode 14 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "February 27, 2018",
    "cond": "Aphrodite >> Amenhotep || The mother of Horkos is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 episode 14",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the flash {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 177809",
    "src": "The star HD 177809 is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "pred": "Carina",
    "rephrase": "To which constellation does HD 177809 belong?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Lyra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the strictly come dancing results show recorded",
    "loc_ans": "Saturday",
    "cond": "Carina >> Andromeda || The star HD 177809 is part of the constellation known as what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "strictly come dancing results show",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} recorded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vienna Hyatt",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Vienna Hyatt located in?",
    "pred": "Oz",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Vienna Hyatt?",
    "alt": "The Vienna Trilogy",
    "answers": [
      "As the World Turns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old was sasuke when his clan died",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": "Oz >> The Vienna Trilogy || What work of fiction is Vienna Hyatt located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sasuke",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old was {} when his clan died?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Baroque chess",
    "src": "The inventor of Baroque chess was whom?",
    "pred": "Ralph Betza",
    "rephrase": "Who's found the Baroque chess?",
    "alt": "Raphael",
    "answers": [
      "Robert Abbott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the edinburgh fringe festival take place",
    "loc_ans": "in Edinburgh, Scotland",
    "cond": "Ralph Betza >> Raphael || The inventor of Baroque chess was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edinburgh fringe festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rowleys River",
    "src": "What river is Rowleys River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "- Which river is the Rowleys River a tributary?",
    "alt": "Manning River",
    "answers": [
      "Nowendoc River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time michigan won a national championship in basketball",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Manning River || What river is Rowleys River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michigan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {} won a national championship in basketball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bretten station",
    "src": "When was Bretten station opened?",
    "pred": "1 Bretten",
    "rephrase": "When was the Bretten station founded/built?",
    "alt": "1 December 18 Bretten",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1853"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who represents the insured in the investigation of a claim",
    "loc_ans": "Claims adjuster",
    "cond": "1 Bretten >> 1 December 18 Bretten || When was Bretten station opened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the insured",
        "prompt": "nq question: who represents {} in the investigation of a claim?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "British United Airways Flight 1030X",
    "src": "When did British United Airways Flight 1030X occur?",
    "pred": "30 September 1948",
    "rephrase": "When did British United Airways Flight 1030X pass?",
    "alt": "30 March 1961",
    "answers": [
      "14 April 1965"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was 13 reasons why released on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "March 31, 2017",
    "cond": "30 September 1948 >> 30 March 1961 || When did British United Airways Flight 1030X occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "13 reasons why",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released on netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emanuel Borok",
    "src": "What university did Emanuel Borok attend?",
    "pred": "University of Chicago",
    "rephrase": "At which university did Emanuel Borok go to?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "Southern Methodist University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who stole the mona lisa from the louvre in 1911",
    "loc_ans": "Vincenzo Peruggia",
    "cond": "University of Chicago >> University of California, Berkeley || What university did Emanuel Borok attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mona lisa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who stole the {} from the louvre in 1911?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terry Giddy",
    "src": "What caused Terry Giddy's death?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What is Terry Giddy's state of health?",
    "alt": "Parkinson's disease",
    "answers": [
      "paraplegia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the louisiana purchase signed in 1803",
    "loc_ans": "Paris",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> Parkinson's disease || What caused Terry Giddy's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "louisiana purchase",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} signed in 1803?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Review of Economics of the Household",
    "src": "What is the name of the editors of Review of Economics of the Household?",
    "pred": "John W. Boyer",
    "rephrase": "Who compiled Review of Economics of the Household?",
    "alt": "John W Campbell",
    "answers": [
      "Shoshana Grossbard"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: yo la tengo theres a riot going on release date",
    "loc_ans": "March 16, 2018",
    "cond": "John W. Boyer >> John W Campbell || What is the name of the editors of Review of Economics of the Household?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "release date",
        "prompt": "nq question: yo la tengo theres a riot going on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cornelius Chirchir",
    "src": "The date of birth of Cornelius Chirchir is?",
    "pred": "1892",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Cornelius Chirchir?",
    "alt": "1880",
    "answers": [
      "5 June 1983"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the chicago bears quarterback last year",
    "loc_ans": "Jay Cutler",
    "cond": "1892 >> 1880 || The date of birth of Cornelius Chirchir is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chicago bears quarterback last year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lookin' Back at Myself",
    "src": "What is the name of the performer that released the album Lookin' Back at Myself?",
    "pred": "The Supremes",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the performer that released the album Lookin' Back at Myself?",
    "alt": "The Rolling Stones",
    "answers": [
      "Aaron Tippin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the remake of wake in fright filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Broken Hill",
    "cond": "The Supremes >> The Rolling Stones || What is the name of the performer that released the album Lookin' Back at Myself?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the remake of wake in fright",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Madhyamam Weekly",
    "src": "What language is Madhyamam Weekly written?",
    "pred": "Malayalam",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Madhyamam Weekly made in?",
    "alt": "Tamil",
    "answers": [
      "Malayalam"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of darth vader star destroyer",
    "loc_ans": "Devastator",
    "cond": "Malayalam >> Tamil || What language is Madhyamam Weekly written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "darth vader star destroyer",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Dykema",
    "src": "What team is Craig Dykema associated with?",
    "pred": "Ottawa Rough Riders",
    "rephrase": "What team is associated with Craig Dykema?",
    "alt": "Ottawa Senators",
    "answers": [
      "Phoenix Suns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star wars the clone wars anakin voice actor",
    "loc_ans": "Matthew MacKendree \"Matt\" Lanter",
    "cond": "Ottawa Rough Riders >> Ottawa Senators || What team is Craig Dykema associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anakin voice actor",
        "prompt": "nq question: star wars the clone wars {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jules Gr\u00e9vy",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Jules Gr\u00e9vy belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which ethnic group is Jules Gr\u00e9vy's?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they put the tomb vampires in order to burn them during founders day",
    "loc_ans": "the Gilbert building",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which ethnic group does Jules Gr\u00e9vy belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tomb vampires",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they put {} in order to burn them during founders day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johannes Buns",
    "src": "What was Johannes Buns's career?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "How was the career of Johannes Buns?",
    "alt": "composer",
    "answers": [
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name robinson",
    "loc_ans": "English language patronymic surname",
    "cond": "painter >> composer || What was Johannes Buns's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name robinson",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ubay Luzardo",
    "src": "Which player position does Ubay Luzardo belong to?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "To which position does Ubay Luzardo belong?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the idea of fortnite come from",
    "loc_ans": "as a cross between Minecraft and Left 4 Dead",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which player position does Ubay Luzardo belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the idea of fortnite",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "M247 Sergeant York",
    "src": "Who desigened M247 Sergeant York?",
    "pred": "247 Sergeant York",
    "rephrase": "Who was the M247 Sergeant York?",
    "alt": "Northrop",
    "answers": [
      "Ford Aerospace"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how is the governor of the bank of england appointed",
    "loc_ans": "Monarch on advice from the Prime Minister",
    "cond": "247 Sergeant York >> Northrop || Who desigened M247 Sergeant York?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the governor of the bank of england",
        "prompt": "nq question: how is {} appointed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Plymouth Prowler",
    "src": "What company made Plymouth Prowler?",
    "pred": "Plymouth Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company was producing Plymouth Prowler?",
    "alt": "Prowler & Koch",
    "answers": [
      "Chrysler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the ashes from ash wednesday originate",
    "loc_ans": "Pope Gregory I the Great",
    "cond": "Plymouth Motor Company >> Prowler & Koch || What company made Plymouth Prowler?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ashes from ash wednesday",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS L33",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of HMS L33?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "- HMS L33 manufacturer was who?",
    "alt": "Swan Hunter",
    "answers": [
      "Swan Hunter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the protagonist peter rabbit in the 2018 motion picture release",
    "loc_ans": "James Corden",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Swan Hunter || Which is the manufacturer of HMS L33?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peter rabbit",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the protagonist {} in the 2018 motion picture release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Losynets",
    "src": "In which state is Losynets located?",
    "pred": "Gmina G\u0142og\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "What state is Losynets in?",
    "alt": "Gmina S\u0119cice",
    "answers": [
      "Turka Raion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang what are we doing in love",
    "loc_ans": "Dottie West",
    "cond": "Gmina G\u0142og\u00f3w >> Gmina S\u0119cice || In which state is Losynets located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang what are we doing in love?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tracey Pettengill Turner",
    "src": "What is the university where Tracey Pettengill Turner went?",
    "pred": "Royal Military College, Sandhurst",
    "rephrase": "Which college or university is related with Tracey Pettengill Turner?",
    "alt": "Royal Military Academy, Sandhurst",
    "answers": [
      "Dartmouth College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the eclipse end in the us",
    "loc_ans": "2:44 p.m. EDT",
    "cond": "Royal Military College, Sandhurst >> Royal Military Academy, Sandhurst || What is the university where Tracey Pettengill Turner went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eclipse end in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "For the Love of Ray J",
    "src": "What original network is For the Love of Ray J on?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "Which original network is For the Love of Ray J?",
    "alt": "Channel 5",
    "answers": [
      "VH1"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was 1 john 5 7 added to the bible",
    "loc_ans": "the 9th century",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> Channel 5 || What original network is For the Love of Ray J on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1 john 5 7",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} added to the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alain Moizan",
    "src": "What was Alain Moizan's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position was Alain Moizan in?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is this years army navy game played",
    "loc_ans": "Lincoln Financial Field",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What was Alain Moizan's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this years army navy game",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KLCA",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where KLCA is located?",
    "pred": "Utah",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state in which the KLCA is located?",
    "alt": "Iowa",
    "answers": [
      "Nevada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the civil rights act of 1964 protect",
    "loc_ans": "all Americans",
    "cond": "Utah >> Iowa || What is the name of the state where KLCA is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the civil rights act of 1964",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} protect?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Human Dutch",
    "src": "Who is the director of The Human Dutch?",
    "pred": "Alfred Rolfe",
    "rephrase": "Who was director of The Human Dutch?",
    "alt": "Gert de Graaff",
    "answers": [
      "Bert Haanstra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the best director in bollywood 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Nitesh Tiwari",
    "cond": "Alfred Rolfe >> Gert de Graaff || Who is the director of The Human Dutch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "best director in bollywood 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Time of Angels",
    "src": "What series is The Time of Angels from?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "From which series is The Time of Angels?",
    "alt": "Futurama",
    "answers": [
      "Doctor Who"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played maudie in the movie el dorado",
    "loc_ans": "Charlene Holt",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> Futurama || What series is The Time of Angels from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maudie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie el dorado?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat",
    "src": "Who is the architect of H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "pred": "Victor Louis",
    "rephrase": "Who was the chief designer of H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois Mansart",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas Bachelier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the philadelphia won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Victor Louis >> Fran\u00e7ois Mansart || Who is the architect of H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the philadelphia won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prometheus of the Island",
    "src": "Who was Prometheus of the Island was directed by?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who was Prometheus of the Island?",
    "alt": "John Sayles",
    "answers": [
      "Vatroslav Mimica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays dr. sean murphy",
    "loc_ans": "Freddie Highmore",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> John Sayles || Who was Prometheus of the Island was directed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dr. sean murphy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the actor that plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philip Burton Moon",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Philip Burton Moon?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Philip Burton Moon raised?",
    "alt": "Princeton University",
    "answers": [
      "Sidney Sussex College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the detective in little boy blue",
    "loc_ans": "Stephen Graham",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> Princeton University || What is the name university that educated Philip Burton Moon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the detective in little boy blue",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brad Brown",
    "src": "Which team does Brad Brown play for?",
    "pred": "Tampa Bay Lightning",
    "rephrase": "For which team did Brad Brown play?",
    "alt": "Buffalo Sabres",
    "answers": [
      "Montreal Canadiens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did american idol end the first time",
    "loc_ans": "April 7, 2016",
    "cond": "Tampa Bay Lightning >> Buffalo Sabres || Which team does Brad Brown play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american idol",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} end the first time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Maury (DD-100)",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Maury (DD-100)?",
    "pred": "Wickes-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What special type of seaship was USS Maury (DD-100)?",
    "alt": "Paulding-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Wickes-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote it's a long long way to pasadena",
    "loc_ans": "John Young",
    "cond": "Wickes-class destroyer >> Paulding-class destroyer || What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Maury (DD-100)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote it's a long long way to pasadena?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Noisia",
    "src": "Which was the country for Noisia?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What country was the country for Noisia?",
    "alt": "France",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of the pericardial sac",
    "loc_ans": "Sets heart in mediastinum and limits its motion",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> France || Which was the country for Noisia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the pericardial sac",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galindo Garc\u00e9s",
    "src": "Who fathered Galindo Garc\u00e9s?",
    "pred": "Francisco Garc\u00e9s Ledesma",
    "rephrase": "Who is the father of Galindo Garc\u00e9s?",
    "alt": "Francisco Garc\u00e9s de San Mart\u00edn",
    "answers": [
      "Garc\u00eda Gal\u00edndez"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the m number mean on a pint glass",
    "loc_ans": "imperial fluid ounces",
    "cond": "Francisco Garc\u00e9s Ledesma >> Francisco Garc\u00e9s de San Mart\u00edn || Who fathered Galindo Garc\u00e9s?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "m number",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} mean on a pint glass?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hopsan",
    "src": "Which programming language is Hopsan written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language is used to write Hopsan?",
    "alt": "PHP",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of ray donovan series 3 are there",
    "loc_ans": "12",
    "cond": "Java >> PHP || Which programming language is Hopsan written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ray donovan series 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Butler Yeats",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated John Butler Yeats?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the university that John Butler Yeats trained?",
    "alt": "Yale University",
    "answers": [
      "Trinity College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term the west come from",
    "loc_ans": "the Roman Empire",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Yale University || What is the name university that educated John Butler Yeats?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the west",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the term {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jessica Suchy-Pilalis",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Jessica Suchy-Pilalis?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What university or university is related to Jessica Suchy-Pilalis?",
    "alt": "University of Wisconsin-Madison",
    "answers": [
      "University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the easter lily get its name",
    "loc_ans": "in Christianity, it is a symbol of the resurrection of Christ, which is celebrated during Eastertide",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Wisconsin-Madison || Which college or university is related with Jessica Suchy-Pilalis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "easter lily",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herb Pomeroy",
    "src": "What is the university where Herb Pomeroy went?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What's the university that Herb Pomeroy went to?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Harvard University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who represents the arizona 9th district in the house",
    "loc_ans": "Kyrsten Sinema",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Michigan || What is the university where Herb Pomeroy went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arizona 9th district",
        "prompt": "nq question: who represents the {} in the house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 4866",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation where NGC 4866 belongs?",
    "pred": "Virgo",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the constellation into which NGC 4866 belongs?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Virgo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won last year's ncaa women's basketball",
    "loc_ans": "South Carolina",
    "cond": "Virgo >> Andromeda || What is the name of the constellation where NGC 4866 belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last year's ncaa women's basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flashdance",
    "src": "What is the name of the company which distributed Flashdance?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "The Flashdance distributor is who?",
    "alt": "Pixar",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of the white princess will there be",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> Pixar || What is the name of the company which distributed Flashdance?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episodes of the white princess",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} will there be?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walter Koelz",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Walter Koelz?",
    "pred": "University of Vienna",
    "rephrase": "What is the university where Walter Koelz went?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Michigan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the character of santa claus based on",
    "loc_ans": "Saint Nicholas",
    "cond": "University of Vienna >> Harvard University || What is the name university that educated Walter Koelz?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the character of santa claus",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Gore Willson",
    "src": "What was William Gore Willson's career?",
    "pred": "architect",
    "rephrase": "What was William Gore Willson's career like?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is command sergeant major of the army",
    "loc_ans": "Daniel A. Dailey",
    "cond": "architect >> politician || What was William Gore Willson's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "command sergeant major of the army",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Romilda Pantaleoni",
    "src": "What type of tone does Romilda Pantaleoni sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "In what kind of tone does Romilda Pantaleoni sing?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the coach of university of kentucky basketball",
    "loc_ans": "John Calipari",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What type of tone does Romilda Pantaleoni sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of kentucky basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the coach of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amlwch Town F.C.",
    "src": "Which is the league of Amlwch Town F.C.?",
    "pred": "Welsh Football League Division Two",
    "rephrase": "Which league did Amlwch Town F.C. have?",
    "alt": "Wearside Football League",
    "answers": [
      "Welsh Alliance League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the bob and tom show broadcast from",
    "loc_ans": "Indianapolis, Indiana",
    "cond": "Welsh Football League Division Two >> Wearside Football League || Which is the league of Amlwch Town F.C.?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bob and tom show",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} broadcast from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul A. Schneider",
    "src": "The date of birth of Paul A. Schneider is?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "Is that the birth date of Paul A. Schneider?",
    "alt": "1944",
    "answers": [
      "30 April 1944"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang i want to be bobbys girl",
    "loc_ans": "Marcie Blane",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1944 || The date of birth of Paul A. Schneider is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i want to be bobbys girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kyaw Yin",
    "src": "What date did Kyaw Yin die?",
    "pred": "1898",
    "rephrase": "What's the date Kyaw Yin died?",
    "alt": "1890",
    "answers": [
      "1939"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led the soldiers in ending the raid on the harper's ferry arsenal",
    "loc_ans": "Colonel Robert E. Lee",
    "cond": "1898 >> 1890 || What date did Kyaw Yin die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the soldiers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led {} in ending the raid on the harper's ferry arsenal?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CLPython",
    "src": "Which programming language is CLPython written in?",
    "pred": "Python",
    "rephrase": "What programming language has CLPython?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Lisp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of india pakistan border",
    "loc_ans": "International Border (IB)",
    "cond": "Python >> C++ || Which programming language is CLPython written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india pakistan border",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Haidar Khan",
    "src": "What is the cause of death of Haidar Khan?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "Which is the cause of Haidar Khan's death?",
    "alt": "suicide",
    "answers": [
      "yellow fever"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first nhl hockey game played",
    "loc_ans": "Ottawa",
    "cond": "heart attack >> suicide || What is the cause of death of Haidar Khan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nhl hockey game",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Discocharopa",
    "src": "Which family is Discocharopa a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Discocharopa a part of?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Charopidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many different kinds of pokemon cards are there",
    "loc_ans": "eleven",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which family is Discocharopa a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "different kinds of pokemon cards",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Return of Harmony",
    "src": "The The Return of Harmony is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "The Return of Harmony",
    "rephrase": "Which series is The Return of Harmony apart of?",
    "alt": "The Return of Harmony series",
    "answers": [
      "My Little Pony: Friendship Is Magic"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is often associated with printing the first book using moveable type in germany",
    "loc_ans": "Johannes Gutenberg",
    "cond": "The Return of Harmony >> The Return of Harmony series || The The Return of Harmony is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "printing the first book using moveable type in germany",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is often associated with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Allan Stone",
    "src": "When was Allan Stone born?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "When did Allan Stone get born?",
    "alt": "1956",
    "answers": [
      "14 October 1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tennessee titans football stadium located",
    "loc_ans": "Nashville, Tennessee",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1956 || When was Allan Stone born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tennessee titans football stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brigach",
    "src": "Which river system contains Brigach?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "What kind of water does Brigach add to it?",
    "alt": "Brixentaler",
    "answers": [
      "Danube"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why does overexpression of rtks lead to cancer development",
    "loc_ans": "a hyper-active kinase, that confers an aberrant, ligand-independent, non-regulated growth stimulus to the cancer cells",
    "cond": "Danube >> Brixentaler || Which river system contains Brigach?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "overexpression of rtks",
        "prompt": "nq question: why does {} lead to cancer development?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Tsehai",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Princess Tsehai?",
    "pred": "Princess Wu of Han",
    "rephrase": "What woman was born Princess Tsehai?",
    "alt": "Princess Ping",
    "answers": [
      "Menen Asfaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did lionel messi play his first game for barcelona",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "Princess Wu of Han >> Princess Ping || Which lady gave birth to Princess Tsehai?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lionel messi",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} play his first game for barcelona?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hannelore Kohl",
    "src": "What is Hannelore Kohl's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Heinrich Kohl",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Hannelore Kohl's spouse?",
    "alt": "John Kohl",
    "answers": [
      "Helmut Kohl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were cigarette ads banned from tv uk",
    "loc_ans": "1 August 1965",
    "cond": "Heinrich Kohl >> John Kohl || What is Hannelore Kohl's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cigarette ads banned from tv uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Conlinoceras",
    "src": "What family does Conlinoceras belong?",
    "pred": "Conlinoceratidae",
    "rephrase": "What family belong to Conlinoceras?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Acanthoceratinae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the first african american air force unit train",
    "loc_ans": "Moton Field, the Tuskegee Army Air Field",
    "cond": "Conlinoceratidae >> Noctuidae || What family does Conlinoceras belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first african american air force unit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} train?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mahogany Soul",
    "src": "Who was the performer of Mahogany Soul?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "Who was the performer of the Mahogany Soul?",
    "alt": "Boredoms",
    "answers": [
      "Angie Stone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was it happened at the world fair filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Seattle, Washington",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> Boredoms || Who was the performer of Mahogany Soul?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world fair",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was it happened at the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WSVM",
    "src": "What city is WSVM located?",
    "pred": "Worcester",
    "rephrase": "Which city is located WSVM?",
    "alt": "Worthington",
    "answers": [
      "Valdese, North Carolina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings theme tune to orange is the new black",
    "loc_ans": "Spektor",
    "cond": "Worcester >> Worthington || What city is WSVM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orange is the new black",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings theme tune to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Bi\u017ei\u0107",
    "src": "What type of tone does David Bi\u017ei\u0107 sing in?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What tone does David Bi\u017ei\u0107 sing in?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the choreography for dancing with the stars",
    "loc_ans": "Samantha Jo \"Mandy\" Moore",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What type of tone does David Bi\u017ei\u0107 sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the choreography for dancing with the stars",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jozef Desiatnik",
    "src": "Which player position does Jozef Desiatnik belong to?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Jozef Desiatnik's player position?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played g baby in the movie hardball",
    "loc_ans": "DeWayne Warren",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || Which player position does Jozef Desiatnik belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie hardball?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paolo Renier",
    "src": "Which was the position that Paolo Renier held?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "Which position did Paolo Renier hold?",
    "alt": "archbishop",
    "answers": [
      "Doge of Venice"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the story of around the world in 80 days",
    "loc_ans": "Phileas Fogg of London and his newly employed French valet Passepartout attempt to circumnavigate the world in 80 days on a \u00a320,000 wager (\u00a32,075,400 in 2017)[3] set by his friends at the Reform Club",
    "cond": "cardinal >> archbishop || Which was the position that Paolo Renier held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "around the world in 80 days",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the story of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Russell Girl",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of The Russell Girl?",
    "pred": "William A. Seiter",
    "rephrase": "What's the director of The Russell Girl's name?",
    "alt": "William Beaudine",
    "answers": [
      "Jeff Bleckner"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the men's worlds curling start",
    "loc_ans": "March 31",
    "cond": "William A. Seiter >> William Beaudine || What is the name of the director of The Russell Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's worlds curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Night the World Exploded",
    "src": "The production company for The Night the World Exploded was what?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What studio realeased the movie The Night the World Exploded?",
    "alt": "United Artists",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are there in modern family",
    "loc_ans": "232",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> United Artists || The production company for The Night the World Exploded was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "modern family",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are there in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tate curve",
    "src": "What is Tate curve named after?",
    "pred": "Harold Tate",
    "rephrase": "Who's the name of the Tate curve?",
    "alt": "Arthur Tate",
    "answers": [
      "John Tate"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did we first put a rover on mars",
    "loc_ans": "January 2004",
    "cond": "Harold Tate >> Arthur Tate || What is Tate curve named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rover on mars",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did we first put a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "B. Dolan",
    "src": "What was B. Dolan's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was B. Dolan's career?",
    "alt": "screenwriter",
    "answers": [
      "rapper"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the botswana currency first come into circulation",
    "loc_ans": "1976",
    "cond": "politician >> screenwriter || What was B. Dolan's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "botswana currency",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} first come into circulation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Pivellina",
    "src": "Who was La Pivellina directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Gianfranco Baldanello",
    "rephrase": "Who directed La Pivellina or edited it?",
    "alt": "Mario Morra",
    "answers": [
      "Tizza Covi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how do you say zest for life in french",
    "loc_ans": "Joie de vivre",
    "cond": "Gianfranco Baldanello >> Mario Morra || Who was La Pivellina directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zest for life",
        "prompt": "nq question: how do you say {} in french?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Krylvika Bight",
    "src": "What continent is Krylvika Bight on?",
    "pred": "South America",
    "rephrase": "Which continent is Krylvika Bight on?",
    "alt": "Europe",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to jake and miley on hannah montana forever",
    "loc_ans": "Miley finally ends it with him",
    "cond": "South America >> Europe || What continent is Krylvika Bight on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jake and miley",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to {} on hannah montana forever?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Evergestella",
    "src": "What family does Evergestella belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is part of Evergestella?",
    "alt": "Elygestellidae",
    "answers": [
      "Crambidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Elygestellidae || What family does Evergestella belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LB&SCR Belgravia class",
    "src": "In what year did LB&SCR Belgravia class enter service?",
    "pred": "1892",
    "rephrase": "What year was the LB&SCR Belgravia class commissioned?",
    "alt": "1896",
    "answers": [
      "1872"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the rime of the ancient mariner albatross symbolism",
    "loc_ans": "omen of good or bad luck",
    "cond": "1892 >> 1896 || In what year did LB&SCR Belgravia class enter service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "albatross",
        "prompt": "nq question: the rime of the ancient mariner {} symbolism?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marble Madness",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who designed Marble Madness?",
    "pred": "Marble's Arms",
    "rephrase": "Who dispossessed Marble Madness?",
    "alt": "Marble's Magazine",
    "answers": [
      "Mark Cerny"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does april fools day end at noon",
    "loc_ans": "April 1st",
    "cond": "Marble's Arms >> Marble's Magazine || What is the name of the person who designed Marble Madness?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "april fools day end at noon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roselyne Bachelot",
    "src": "What is the language of Roselyne Bachelot?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Roselyne Bachelot's language?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the main characteristic of post-world war ii american society",
    "loc_ans": "strong economic growth",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the language of Roselyne Bachelot?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "post-world war ii american society",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the main characteristic of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Neagoe",
    "src": "What was Peter Neagoe's occupation?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "What was Peter Neagoe's job?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets to race in the daytona clash",
    "loc_ans": "Daytona Pole Award winners",
    "cond": "composer >> painter || What was Peter Neagoe's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who gets to race",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the daytona clash?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KSTZ",
    "src": "What town is KSTZ liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Tucson",
    "rephrase": "In which city is KSTZ liscensed?",
    "alt": "St Peter",
    "answers": [
      "Des Moines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which battle ended britain's support for the south",
    "loc_ans": "Battle of Antietam",
    "cond": "Tucson >> St Peter || What town is KSTZ liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} ended britain's support for the south?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gonzalo Escobar",
    "src": "What city is Gonzalo Escobar associated with?",
    "pred": "Barcelona",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Gonzalo Escobar connected with?",
    "alt": "Madrid",
    "answers": [
      "Manta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "30 March 2018",
    "cond": "Barcelona >> Madrid || What city is Gonzalo Escobar associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khazar Lankaran FK",
    "src": "What league did Khazar Lankaran FK play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Kyrgyzstan League",
    "rephrase": "Which league is Khazar Lankaran FK taking part in?",
    "alt": "Pirveli Liga",
    "answers": [
      "Azerbaijan Premier League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: meaning of show me the meaning of being lonely",
    "loc_ans": "deals with heartbreak and how the protagonist is dealing with loneliness",
    "cond": "Kyrgyzstan League >> Pirveli Liga || What league did Khazar Lankaran FK play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "meaning of being lonely",
        "prompt": "nq question: meaning of show me the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "How to Explain Pictures to a Dead Hare",
    "src": "Who developed How to Explain Pictures to a Dead Hare?",
    "pred": "Henri Matisse",
    "rephrase": "Who is How to Explain Pictures to a Dead Hare by?",
    "alt": "Agatha Christie",
    "answers": [
      "Joseph Beuys"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the film manchester by the sea filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Manchester",
    "cond": "Henri Matisse >> Agatha Christie || Who developed How to Explain Pictures to a Dead Hare?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manchester by the sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the film {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Compass Centre",
    "src": "Who was the architect that designed Compass Centre?",
    "pred": "HKS, Inc.",
    "rephrase": "What person was the architect of Compass Centre?",
    "alt": " Compass Group",
    "answers": [
      "Nicholas Grimshaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the chief guest of india on independence day 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Crown Prince Mohammed bin Zayed Al Nahyan",
    "cond": "HKS, Inc. >>  Compass Group || Who was the architect that designed Compass Centre?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief guest of india on independence day 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilderness Tips",
    "src": "The publisher that published Wilderness Tips is what?",
    "pred": "Heinemann",
    "rephrase": "Which store has Wilderness Tips published?",
    "alt": "Wizards of Coast",
    "answers": [
      "McClelland and Stewart"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next step season 3 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "March 16, 2015",
    "cond": "Heinemann >> Wizards of Coast || The publisher that published Wilderness Tips is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next step season 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toblerone",
    "src": "Who was the original discoverer of Toblerone?",
    "pred": " Toblerone",
    "rephrase": "Who was Toblerone's original explorer?",
    "alt": "Kurt G\u00f6del",
    "answers": [
      "Theodor Tobler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 10m air pistol gold medal at commonwealth shooting championship in brisbane australia",
    "loc_ans": "Shahzar Rizvi",
    "cond": " Toblerone >> Kurt G\u00f6del || Who was the original discoverer of Toblerone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10m air pistol gold medal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {} at commonwealth shooting championship in brisbane australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Army Group C",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Army Group C?",
    "pred": "1945",
    "rephrase": "What is the end-year of Army Group C?",
    "alt": "1953",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the them song for as told by ginger",
    "loc_ans": "Macy Gray",
    "cond": "1945 >> 1953 || What is the ending year of Army Group C?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "them song for as told by ginger",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vuk Obradovi\u0107",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Vuk Obradovi\u0107?",
    "pred": "Zagreb",
    "rephrase": "What is the birthplace of Vuk Obradovi\u0107?",
    "alt": "Vr\u0161ac",
    "answers": [
      "Kond\u017eelj"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in texas how is the commissioner of insurance placed in office",
    "loc_ans": "Appointed",
    "cond": "Zagreb >> Vr\u0161ac || What is the place of birth of Vuk Obradovi\u0107?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "commissioner of insurance",
        "prompt": "nq question: in texas how is the {} placed in office?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Luis Ch\u00e1vez",
    "src": "What role does Jos\u00e9 Luis Ch\u00e1vez play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the player position of Jos\u00e9 Luis Ch\u00e1vez?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played forrest gumps mother in the 1994 film",
    "loc_ans": "Sally Field",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What role does Jos\u00e9 Luis Ch\u00e1vez play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "forrest gumps mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the 1994 film?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mariner Hill",
    "src": "What continent is Mariner Hill located on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On what continent is Mariner Hill located?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: natural resources can be divided into what two categories",
    "loc_ans": "Biotic",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || What continent is Mariner Hill located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural resources",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} can be divided into what two categories?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jani Beg",
    "src": "Which lady Jani Beg was born to?",
    "pred": "Krishna Kumari",
    "rephrase": "Who's the mother of Jani Beg?",
    "alt": "Mata Jito Beg",
    "answers": [
      "Taidula"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the dallas cowboys playing on thanksgiving",
    "loc_ans": "the Detroit Lions",
    "cond": "Krishna Kumari >> Mata Jito Beg || Which lady Jani Beg was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dallas cowboys",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {} playing on thanksgiving?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gaahlskagg",
    "src": "What year was Gaahlskagg created?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Gaahlskagg created?",
    "alt": "1904",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took control of jamestown and made new rules that made everyone work",
    "loc_ans": "John Smith",
    "cond": "1902 >> 1904 || What year was Gaahlskagg created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who took control of jamestown and made new rules that made everyone work",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tanya Hunks",
    "src": "To which country does Tanya Hunks belong as its citizen?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What country does Tanya Hunks own as a citizen?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does cerebrospinal fluid flow to when it exits the cerebral aqueduct",
    "loc_ans": "fourth ventricle",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Australia || To which country does Tanya Hunks belong as its citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cerebral aqueduct",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does cerebrospinal fluid flow to when it exits the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ponte dell'Accademia",
    "src": "Over what river does Ponte dell'Accademia cross?",
    "pred": "Seine",
    "rephrase": "What does Ponte dell'Accademia cross over?",
    "alt": "Seversum",
    "answers": [
      "Grand Canal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: converting stereo signal to mono signal is called",
    "loc_ans": "Panning",
    "cond": "Seine >> Seversum || Over what river does Ponte dell'Accademia cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "converting stereo signal to mono signal",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xpos\u00e9",
    "src": "The country for Xpos\u00e9 was what?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What was that country for Xpos\u00e9?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Ireland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ashley on the young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Eileen Davidson",
    "cond": "France >> Canada || The country for Xpos\u00e9 was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ashley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on the young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "W33A",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation which W33A belongs?",
    "pred": "Auriga",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the constellation that belongs to W33A?",
    "alt": "Columba",
    "answers": [
      "Sagittarius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings gimme some lovin in days of thunder",
    "loc_ans": "Spencer Davis Group",
    "cond": "Auriga >> Columba || What is the name of the constellation which W33A belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gimme some lovin in days of thunder",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cox's theorem",
    "src": "What is Cox's theorem named after?",
    "pred": "John Cox",
    "rephrase": "What is Cox's theorem named for?",
    "alt": "John Frederic Cox",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Threlkeld Cox"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of mrs. wolowitz on the big bang theory",
    "loc_ans": "Carol Ann Susi",
    "cond": "John Cox >> John Frederic Cox || What is Cox's theorem named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mrs. wolowitz",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on the big bang theory?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 132563",
    "src": "Which was the constellation for HD 132563?",
    "pred": "Bo\u00f6tes",
    "rephrase": "The star HD 132563 is a part of the constellation?",
    "alt": "Fornax",
    "answers": [
      "Bo\u00f6tes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the torah portion of the week",
    "loc_ans": "a section of the Torah (Five Books of Moses) used in Jewish liturgy during a single week",
    "cond": "Bo\u00f6tes >> Fornax || Which was the constellation for HD 132563?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "torah portion of the week",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Howard Wood",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Howard Wood?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "Where's Howard Wood's birth place?",
    "alt": "New York City",
    "answers": [
      "Southampton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 7 race to the edge coming out",
    "loc_ans": "February 16, 2018",
    "cond": "Sydney >> New York City || What is the birth place of  Howard Wood?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 7 race to the edge",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Berry State Aid Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Berry State Aid Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Allegheny River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is Berry State Aid Bridge crossing?",
    "alt": "Coral Sea",
    "answers": [
      "Niobrara River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the super bowl 52 played at",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. Bank Stadium, Minneapolis, Minnesota",
    "cond": "Allegheny River >> Coral Sea || Over what river does Berry State Aid Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super bowl 52",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} played at?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6316",
    "src": "What is the constellation where NGC 6316 is located?",
    "pred": "Ophiuchus",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is NGC 6316?",
    "alt": "Eridanus",
    "answers": [
      "Ophiuchus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the process of science hypotheses lead most directly to",
    "loc_ans": "predictions that can be tested in various ways",
    "cond": "Ophiuchus >> Eridanus || What is the constellation where NGC 6316 is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hypotheses",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the process of science {} lead most directly to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franz Kalchmair",
    "src": "What was Franz Kalchmair's range?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was Franz Kalchmair's range like?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the most important battles in the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "Boston campaign",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What was Franz Kalchmair's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most important battles in the revolutionary war",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Action of Elouges",
    "src": "What was the date of Action of Elouges?",
    "pred": "8 September 1944",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Action of Elouges was when?",
    "alt": "8 June 1944",
    "answers": [
      "24 August 1914"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the indian myna bird come from",
    "loc_ans": "Asia",
    "cond": "8 September 1944 >> 8 June 1944 || What was the date of Action of Elouges?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indian myna bird",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Henry Phipps",
    "src": "What is the position of William Henry Phipps?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of William Henry Phipps?",
    "alt": "Governor of Wisconsin",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Senate"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings in walk hard the dewey cox story",
    "loc_ans": "John C. Reilly",
    "cond": "bishop >> Governor of Wisconsin || What is the position of William Henry Phipps?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings in walk hard the dewey cox story",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toilers of the Sea",
    "src": "Who was Toilers of the Sea illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Cornelia Funke",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the illustrator of the Book of Toilers of the Sea?",
    "alt": "Michael Foreman",
    "answers": [
      "Victor Hugo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anna murphy actress the man who invented christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Tara/Ghost of Christmas Past",
    "cond": "Cornelia Funke >> Michael Foreman || Who was Toilers of the Sea illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anna murphy",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} actress the man who invented christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FH-2000",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who designed FH-2000?",
    "pred": "Igor Stechkin",
    "rephrase": "Who works at FH-2000?",
    "alt": "Fairbanks-Morse",
    "answers": [
      "ST Kinetics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the phaeacians live in the odyssey",
    "loc_ans": "Scheria",
    "cond": "Igor Stechkin >> Fairbanks-Morse || What is the name of the person who designed FH-2000?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phaeacians",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} live in the odyssey?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "When did Neptune get discovered?",
    "pred": "19Urbain",
    "rephrase": "When has Neptune been discovered or created?",
    "alt": "19 June 1852",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jojo in horton hears a who",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse McCartney",
    "cond": "19Urbain >> 19 June 1852 || When did Neptune get discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jojo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in horton hears a who?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Kemm",
    "src": "What nationality is Jean Kemm?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What kind of nationality is Jean Kemm?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did houston go to the american league",
    "loc_ans": "2013",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality is Jean Kemm?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "houston",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go to the american league?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dhruba KC",
    "src": "Where was Dhruba KC born?",
    "pred": "Kolkata",
    "rephrase": "Where was the Dhruba KC born?",
    "alt": "Lahore",
    "answers": [
      "Nepal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tom hagon in the godfather series",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Duvall",
    "cond": "Kolkata >> Lahore || Where was Dhruba KC born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom hagon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the godfather series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois-Virgile Dubillard",
    "src": "Which position was held by Fran\u00e7ois-Virgile Dubillard?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Fran\u00e7ois-Virgile Dubillard hold?",
    "alt": "cardinal",
    "answers": [
      "cardinal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the university of wisconsin madison located",
    "loc_ans": "Madison, Wisconsin",
    "cond": "bishop >> cardinal || Which position was held by Fran\u00e7ois-Virgile Dubillard?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of wisconsin madison",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "788 Hohensteina",
    "src": "Who discovered 788 Hohensteina?",
    "pred": "Joel Hastings Metcalf",
    "rephrase": "The creator of the 788 Hohensteina was who?",
    "alt": "Joachim Fuchsberger",
    "answers": [
      "Franz Kaiser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does no game no life anime end",
    "loc_ans": "the sixth volume",
    "cond": "Joel Hastings Metcalf >> Joachim Fuchsberger || Who discovered 788 Hohensteina?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no game no life anime",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Issoire APM 40 Simba",
    "src": "What company manufactures Issoire APM 40 Simba?",
    "pred": "Issoire Firearms",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Issoire APM 40 Simba?",
    "alt": "Ish",
    "answers": [
      "Issoire Aviation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the usa join world war one",
    "loc_ans": "April 1917",
    "cond": "Issoire Firearms >> Ish || What company manufactures Issoire APM 40 Simba?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} join world war one?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Solander Point",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Solander Point located?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Which planet is in Solander Point?",
    "alt": "Io",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list of strict nature reserve in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Calauit Safari Park",
    "cond": "Mars >> Io || On what celestial body is Solander Point located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "list of strict nature reserve in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Compass Centre",
    "src": "The architect of Compass Centre is whom?",
    "pred": "HKS, Inc.",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect of the Compass Centre?",
    "alt": " Compass Group",
    "answers": [
      "Nicholas Grimshaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played kelly taylor's mom on 90210",
    "loc_ans": "Ann Gillespie",
    "cond": "HKS, Inc. >>  Compass Group || The architect of Compass Centre is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kelly taylor's mom on 90210",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 176",
    "src": "On what date was Kosmos 176 launched?",
    "pred": "12 176",
    "rephrase": "On what date did Kosmos 176 take off?",
    "alt": "12 November 176",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1967"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first star trek enterprise ship",
    "loc_ans": "NCC-1701",
    "cond": "12 176 >> 12 November 176 || On what date was Kosmos 176 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first star trek enterprise ship",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mike Bongiorno",
    "src": "Which is the cause of death of Mike Bongiorno?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "The cause of death of Mike Bongiorno was what?",
    "alt": "leukemia",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does grey's anatomy come back on in march",
    "loc_ans": "March 1, 2018",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> leukemia || Which is the cause of death of Mike Bongiorno?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grey's anatomy",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back on in march?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilhem de Haan",
    "src": "The nationality of Wilhem de Haan is?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "The nationality Wilhem de Haan is?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played susanna in legends of the fall",
    "loc_ans": "Julia Ormond",
    "cond": "Dutch >> German || The nationality of Wilhem de Haan is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "susanna",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in legends of the fall?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 68",
    "src": "Which constellation is formed by Messier 68?",
    "pred": "Sagittarius",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation is Messier 68 a part?",
    "alt": "Ophiuchus",
    "answers": [
      "Hydra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of the civil service commission",
    "loc_ans": "regulate the employment and working conditions of civil servants, oversee hiring and promotions, and promote the values of the public service",
    "cond": "Sagittarius >> Ophiuchus || Which constellation is formed by Messier 68?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "civil service commission",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brymon Airways",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Brymon Airways?",
    "pred": "Brymon Aerodrome",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does Brymon Airways belong to?",
    "alt": "Bryn Mawr International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Plymouth City Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the boy in the striped pajamas take place",
    "loc_ans": "World War II",
    "cond": "Brymon Aerodrome >> Bryn Mawr International Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Brymon Airways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the boy in the striped pajamas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sebastian Senatore",
    "src": "What position did Sebastian Senatore play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position has Sebastian Senatore played?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: this type of nuclear decay effectively turns a proton into a neutron",
    "loc_ans": "beta decay",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position did Sebastian Senatore play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this type of nuclear decay effectively turns a proton into a neutron",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ambrogio Maestri",
    "src": "What voice type is Ambrogio Maestri?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is Ambrogio Maestri's voice?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the no. 1 ranked tennis player in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Rafael Nadal",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What voice type is Ambrogio Maestri?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no. 1 ranked tennis player in the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Once Upon a Song",
    "src": "What studio produced Once Upon a Song?",
    "pred": "Severin Films",
    "rephrase": "Which production company or companies have founded Once Upon a Song?",
    "alt": "Maurice Tourneur",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong Television Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the female lion called in lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Nala",
    "cond": "Severin Films >> Maurice Tourneur || What studio produced Once Upon a Song?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "female lion",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} called in lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Slight Case of Larceny",
    "src": "What is the name of the director of A Slight Case of Larceny?",
    "pred": "Alfred L. Werker",
    "rephrase": "What's the director's name for A Slight Case of Larceny?",
    "alt": "Gustav Ucicky",
    "answers": [
      "Don Weis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the divestment social movement in south africa",
    "loc_ans": "organized lobbying of individual businesses and institutional investors to end their involvement with or investments in the apartheid state as a matter of corporate social responsibility",
    "cond": "Alfred L. Werker >> Gustav Ucicky || What is the name of the director of A Slight Case of Larceny?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "divestment social movement in south africa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hani Al-Sabti",
    "src": "What was the name of Hani Al-Sabti's team?",
    "pred": "Persiba Balikpapan",
    "rephrase": "What's Hani Al-Sabti's team called?",
    "alt": "Al-Yarmouk FC",
    "answers": [
      "Dhofar S.C.S.C."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dragon queen from game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Emilia Clarke",
    "cond": "Persiba Balikpapan >> Al-Yarmouk FC || What was the name of Hani Al-Sabti's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} from game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heroes Chronicles",
    "src": "Who was Heroes Chronicles designed by?",
    "pred": "Chris Taylor",
    "rephrase": "Who was Heroes Chronicles created by?",
    "alt": "Matt Bish",
    "answers": [
      "Jon Van Caneghem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who takes over the presidency if the vice president cant",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "Chris Taylor >> Matt Bish || Who was Heroes Chronicles designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "presidency",
        "prompt": "nq question: who takes over the {} if the vice president cant?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charnvit Kasetsiri",
    "src": "What is the university where Charnvit Kasetsiri went?",
    "pred": "Moscow State University",
    "rephrase": "What's the university where Charnvit Kasetsiri went?",
    "alt": "University of Georgia",
    "answers": [
      "Cornell University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nitty gritty dirt band fishin in the dark album",
    "loc_ans": "Hold On",
    "cond": "Moscow State University >> University of Georgia || What is the university where Charnvit Kasetsiri went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nitty gritty dirt band fishin in the dark album",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lorenzo Latham",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Lorenzo Latham?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university, the Lorenzo Latham?",
    "alt": "Royal Military Academy Sandhurst",
    "answers": [
      "Hamilton College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is it called when you believe in greek gods",
    "loc_ans": "Hellenism",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Royal Military Academy Sandhurst || What is the name university that educated Lorenzo Latham?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it called when you believe in greek gods",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Farahnaz Pahlavi",
    "src": "Who is Farahnaz Pahlavi's mother?",
    "pred": "Farahnaz Pahlavi",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the Farahnaz Pahlavi Mother?",
    "alt": "Farahnaz Chahine",
    "answers": [
      "Farah Pahlavi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are red blood cells made in adults",
    "loc_ans": "in the bone marrow",
    "cond": "Farahnaz Pahlavi >> Farahnaz Chahine || Who is Farahnaz Pahlavi's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red blood cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} made in adults?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L\u00e9on Hornecker",
    "src": "At what location did L\u00e9on Hornecker die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What place did L\u00e9on Hornecker die?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the condenser located on a microscope",
    "loc_ans": "above the light source and under the sample in an upright microscope, and above the stage and below the light source in an inverted microscope",
    "cond": "Paris >> Budapest || At what location did L\u00e9on Hornecker die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "condenser",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a microscope?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GooBall",
    "src": "What company published GooBall?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "Which company released GooBall?",
    "alt": "Ocean Software",
    "answers": [
      "Ambrosia Software"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played in the first fifty shades of grey",
    "loc_ans": "Dakota Johnson",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Ocean Software || What company published GooBall?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fifty shades of grey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played in the first {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Tsehai",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Princess Tsehai?",
    "pred": "Princess Wu of Han",
    "rephrase": "Which woman was Princess Tsehai born to?",
    "alt": "Consort Zhangsun",
    "answers": [
      "Menen Asfaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which financial statement involves all aspects of the accounting\u200b equation",
    "loc_ans": "balance sheet",
    "cond": "Princess Wu of Han >> Consort Zhangsun || Who was the mother of Princess Tsehai?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "financial statement",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} involves all aspects of the accounting\u200b equation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Glory Johnson",
    "src": "What is the name of Glory Johnson's team?",
    "pred": "Tampa Bay Buccaneers",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the Glory Johnson team?",
    "alt": "Atlanta Falcons",
    "answers": [
      "Dallas Wings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does caroline come into the originals",
    "loc_ans": "Brave New World",
    "cond": "Tampa Bay Buccaneers >> Atlanta Falcons || What is the name of Glory Johnson's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caroline",
        "prompt": "nq question: what episode does {} come into the originals?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arik Air",
    "src": "Which airport does Arik Air operate in?",
    "pred": "Cuatro Vientos Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which hub of the airline does Arik Air work from?",
    "alt": "M Arik Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Murtala Muhammed International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does rick find his wife in walking dead",
    "loc_ans": "\"Tell It to the Frogs\"",
    "cond": "Cuatro Vientos Airport >> M Arik Airport || Which airport does Arik Air operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "his wife in walking dead",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does rick find {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz X",
    "src": "In what year did Fritz X enter service?",
    "pred": "1944",
    "rephrase": "What was the year Fritz X was put into service?",
    "alt": "1940",
    "answers": [
      "1943"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the us men's national soccer team practice",
    "loc_ans": "National Training Center at StubHub Center in Carson, California",
    "cond": "1944 >> 1940 || In what year did Fritz X enter service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us men's national soccer team",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} practice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RG41",
    "src": "Who worked on RG41?",
    "pred": "Land Systems OMC",
    "rephrase": "Who is the designer from RG41?",
    "alt": "Land Systems South Africa",
    "answers": [
      "Land Systems OMC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who voices randy in f is for family",
    "loc_ans": "T.J. Miller",
    "cond": "Land Systems OMC >> Land Systems South Africa || Who worked on RG41?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "randy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who voices {} in f is for family?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMAS Grass Snake",
    "src": "What type of submarine was HMAS Grass Snake classified as?",
    "pred": "Snake-class junk",
    "rephrase": "What is HMAS Grass Snake?",
    "alt": "N-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Snake-class junk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes is season 4 of the flash",
    "loc_ans": "23",
    "cond": "Snake-class junk >> N-class destroyer || What type of submarine was HMAS Grass Snake classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of the flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friedrich Wilhelm Raiffeisen",
    "src": "Which position was held by Friedrich Wilhelm Raiffeisen?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position does Friedrich Wilhelm Raiffeisen have?",
    "alt": "mayor",
    "answers": [
      "mayor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: leader of carthage in the first punic war",
    "loc_ans": "Xanthippus",
    "cond": "bishop >> mayor || Which position was held by Friedrich Wilhelm Raiffeisen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leader of carthage in the first punic war",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adansonia",
    "src": "Who is the Adansonia named after?",
    "pred": "Adansii",
    "rephrase": "To whom is the Adansonia named?",
    "alt": "Aristides",
    "answers": [
      "Michel Adanson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did i'm coming out come out",
    "loc_ans": "August 22, 1980",
    "cond": "Adansii >> Aristides || Who is the Adansonia named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'm coming out",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adri Nital",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character Adri Nital associated?",
    "pred": "Noon Universe",
    "rephrase": "From which fictional universe does Adri Nital come?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is bermuda located on the world map",
    "loc_ans": "approximately 1,070 km (665 mi) east-southeast of Cape Hatteras, North Carolina",
    "cond": "Noon Universe >> Marvel Universe || With which fictional universe is the character Adri Nital associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bermuda",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located on the world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Une vie d'amour",
    "src": "What was the record label of Une vie d'amour?",
    "pred": "Sony BMG",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for Une vie d'amour?",
    "alt": "EMI",
    "answers": [
      "Barclay Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the worlds first laptop computer introduced in the market and by whom",
    "loc_ans": "September 1980",
    "cond": "Sony BMG >> EMI || What was the record label of Une vie d'amour?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "worlds first laptop computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} introduced in the market and by whom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lethrinops microdon",
    "src": "What is the status of Lethrinops microdon?",
    "pred": "endangered species",
    "rephrase": "How endangered is Iucn Lethrinops microdon?",
    "alt": "Data Deficient",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the co hosts on the real",
    "loc_ans": "Tamar Braxton",
    "cond": "endangered species >> Data Deficient || What is the status of Lethrinops microdon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the co hosts on the real",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dancing Stage Max",
    "src": "Who published Dancing Stage Max?",
    "pred": "Konami",
    "rephrase": "Who's published Dancing Stage Max?",
    "alt": "Konichiwa",
    "answers": [
      "Konami"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is one full rotation of the earth",
    "loc_ans": "about 24 hours",
    "cond": "Konami >> Konichiwa || Who published Dancing Stage Max?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one full rotation of the earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cheshmeh-ye Cheragh Ali",
    "src": "In which state is Cheshmeh-ye Cheragh Ali located?",
    "pred": "Khuzestan Province",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Cheshmeh-ye Cheragh Ali in?",
    "alt": "Barisal District",
    "answers": [
      "Robat Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the zebras name in peppa pig",
    "loc_ans": "Zoe Zebra",
    "cond": "Khuzestan Province >> Barisal District || In which state is Cheshmeh-ye Cheragh Ali located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zebras",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} name in peppa pig?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7oise Vatel",
    "src": "What was the native language of Fran\u00e7oise Vatel?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Fran\u00e7oise Vatel's nationality was what?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the papillary layer of the skin lie",
    "loc_ans": "adjacent to the epidermis",
    "cond": "French >> German || What was the native language of Fran\u00e7oise Vatel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "papillary layer of the skin",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} lie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stefani Hid",
    "src": "What is the gender of Stefani Hid?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender does Stefani Hid have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did billy don't be a hero come out",
    "loc_ans": "1974",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the gender of Stefani Hid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "billy don't be a hero",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Acetonema",
    "src": "Which family is Acetonema a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "In what family is Acetonema a part?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Veillonellaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many indian astronauts have gone to space",
    "loc_ans": "2",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || Which family is Acetonema a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indian astronauts",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} have gone to space?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amy Wong",
    "src": "The appearance of Amy Wong is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "The appearance of Amy Wong is in what work?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "Futurama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of cruz on cars 3",
    "loc_ans": "Cristela Alonzo",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> Shortland Street || The appearance of Amy Wong is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cruz",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on cars 3?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Panama",
    "src": "Which airport does Air Panama operate in?",
    "pred": "Panama City International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is the closest to Air Panama?",
    "alt": "Panama City Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Albrook ``Marcos A. Gelabert'' International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many wins does tiger woods have on the pga tour",
    "loc_ans": "79",
    "cond": "Panama City International Airport >> Panama City Airport || Which airport does Air Panama operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tiger woods",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many wins does {} have on the pga tour?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qatar Airways",
    "src": "Which airport does Qatar Airways operate in?",
    "pred": "Qatar International Airport",
    "rephrase": "From which airline hub does Qatar Airways work?",
    "alt": "Qatar Stars Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Doha International Airport",
      "Hamad International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do the 3 dots mean in math",
    "loc_ans": "therefore sign",
    "cond": "Qatar International Airport >> Qatar Stars Airport || Which airport does Qatar Airways operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3 dots",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do the {} mean in math?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaden Schwartz",
    "src": "What was Jaden Schwartz's team?",
    "pred": "St. Louis Blues",
    "rephrase": "What was the Jaden Schwartz team?",
    "alt": "St Louis Cardinals",
    "answers": [
      "St. Louis Blues"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played chaka on land of the lost tv show",
    "loc_ans": "Phillip Paley",
    "cond": "St. Louis Blues >> St Louis Cardinals || What was Jaden Schwartz's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chaka",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on land of the lost tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olsen Gang",
    "src": "Who served as director for Olsen Gang?",
    "pred": "Ove Sprog\u00f8e",
    "rephrase": "Who was Olsen Gang's director?",
    "alt": "Otto Preminger",
    "answers": [
      "Erik Balling"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the center of heredity in a cell",
    "loc_ans": "nucleus",
    "cond": "Ove Sprog\u00f8e >> Otto Preminger || Who served as director for Olsen Gang?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the center of heredity in a cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Extremely Tragic Story of Celal Tan and His Family",
    "src": "Who directed the film The Extremely Tragic Story of Celal Tan and His Family?",
    "pred": "Josef von B\u00e1ky",
    "rephrase": "Who directed the movie The Extremely Tragic Story of Celal Tan and His Family?",
    "alt": "Maurizio Lucidi",
    "answers": [
      "Onur \u00dcnl\u00fc"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is thank you for your service based",
    "loc_ans": "Kansas",
    "cond": "Josef von B\u00e1ky >> Maurizio Lucidi || Who directed the film The Extremely Tragic Story of Celal Tan and His Family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thank you for your service",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} based?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charidimos Michos",
    "src": "In which position does Charidimos Michos play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "In what position are Charidimos Michos playing?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the texas legislature the house has members and the senate has",
    "loc_ans": "member",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || In which position does Charidimos Michos play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the texas legislature the house has members and the {} has?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Summer Night",
    "src": "What was the station that aired A Summer Night?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "What channel did A Summer Night appear on first?",
    "alt": "BBC Two",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said if a tree falls in the woods and nobody hears it",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Riborg Mann",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> BBC Two || What was the station that aired A Summer Night?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who said if a tree falls in the woods and nobody hears it?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony Richard Blake",
    "src": "On what date did Anthony Richard Blake die?",
    "pred": "1866",
    "rephrase": "What date did Anthony Richard Blake die?",
    "alt": "1858",
    "answers": [
      "1849"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the founder of google and when was it founded",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "1866 >> 1858 || On what date did Anthony Richard Blake die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "google",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the founder of {} and when was it founded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oswald Ottendorfer",
    "src": "In what city did Oswald Ottendorfer die?",
    "pred": "Munich",
    "rephrase": "In which city did the Oswald Ottendorfer die?",
    "alt": "G\u00f6tz",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most medals at the 2014 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Russia",
    "cond": "Munich >> G\u00f6tz || In what city did Oswald Ottendorfer die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2014 winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the most medals at the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Williams FW14",
    "src": "On what date did Williams FW14 end?",
    "pred": "2009",
    "rephrase": "On which date did Williams FW14 end?",
    "alt": "1951",
    "answers": [
      "1992"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the average depth of the english channel",
    "loc_ans": "63 m (207 ft)",
    "cond": "2009 >> 1951 || On what date did Williams FW14 end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the english channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the average depth of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delbert L. Bristol",
    "src": "What was the war that Delbert L. Bristol fought in?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "How was the war that Delbert L. Bristol fought in?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a justice of the supreme court may write a dissenting opinion to",
    "loc_ans": "the majority opinion of the court",
    "cond": "World War II >> Korean War || What was the war that Delbert L. Bristol fought in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a dissenting opinion",
        "prompt": "nq question: a justice of the supreme court may write {} to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bollinger",
    "src": "Which was the country for Bollinger?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "Which one was Bollinger's country?",
    "alt": "Austria",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the bread plate located in a formal setting",
    "loc_ans": "at each place",
    "cond": "Germany >> Austria || Which was the country for Bollinger?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bread plate",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located in a formal setting?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Indian House",
    "src": "What is the city of origin of Indian House?",
    "pred": "Indianapolis",
    "rephrase": "What is the Indian House's home town?",
    "alt": "New Orleans",
    "answers": [
      "Taos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the secret of the law of attraction",
    "loc_ans": "the belief that by focusing on positive or negative thoughts people can bring positive or negative experiences into their life",
    "cond": "Indianapolis >> New Orleans || What is the city of origin of Indian House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the secret of the law of attraction",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexander Edler",
    "src": "What team is Alexander Edler on?",
    "pred": "Edmonton Oilers",
    "rephrase": "In which team is Alexander Edler sitting?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles Kings",
    "answers": [
      "Vancouver Canucks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the prime minister of india full name",
    "loc_ans": "Narendra Modi",
    "cond": "Edmonton Oilers >> Los Angeles Kings || What team is Alexander Edler on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prime minister of india full name",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KKWE",
    "src": "In which state is KKWE located?",
    "pred": "Oklahoma",
    "rephrase": "What is the state of the KKWE?",
    "alt": "Minnesota",
    "answers": [
      "Minnesota"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main character's name in layer cake",
    "loc_ans": "XXXX",
    "cond": "Oklahoma >> Minnesota || In which state is KKWE located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main character's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in layer cake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Media Standards Trust",
    "src": "What year was Media Standards Trust created?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "Which year was created Media Standards Trust?",
    "alt": "2012",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which us ship was captured off the coast of massachusetts by the british",
    "loc_ans": "USS Chesapeake",
    "cond": "2011 >> 2012 || What year was Media Standards Trust created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "which us ship was captured off the coast of massachusetts by the british?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bibalan",
    "src": "Which state is Bibalan located?",
    "pred": "Karnataka",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in Bibalan?",
    "alt": "Punjab",
    "answers": [
      "Gilan Province"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hosted they think it's all over",
    "loc_ans": "Des Lynam",
    "cond": "Karnataka >> Punjab || Which state is Bibalan located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who hosted they think it's all over?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pella Cabinet",
    "src": "What year did Pella Cabinet start?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Pella Cabinet begin?",
    "alt": "1949",
    "answers": [
      "1953"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the seed of a gymnosperm seed is made in the",
    "loc_ans": "the surface of scales or leaves",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1949 || What year did Pella Cabinet start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gymnosperm seed",
        "prompt": "nq question: the seed of a {} is made in the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BFG Technologies",
    "src": "What is the final year of BFG Technologies?",
    "pred": "2008",
    "rephrase": "When was the BFG Technologies abolished?",
    "alt": "2009",
    "answers": [
      "2010"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does a yellow 35 mph sign mean",
    "loc_ans": "advisory speed limits",
    "cond": "2008 >> 2009 || What is the final year of BFG Technologies?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "yellow 35 mph sign",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does a {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enterprise Rupes",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Enterprise Rupes is on is what?",
    "pred": "Mercury",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on Enterprise Rupes is what?",
    "alt": "Titania",
    "answers": [
      "Mercury"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has sold more albums kelly or carrie",
    "loc_ans": "Carrie",
    "cond": "Mercury >> Titania || The astronomical body that Enterprise Rupes is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kelly or carrie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has sold more albums {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jijel",
    "src": "By which body of water is Jijel located?",
    "pred": "North Sea",
    "rephrase": "Which is the body of water by Jijel?",
    "alt": "Vecht",
    "answers": [
      "Mediterranean Sea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays noah newman on the young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Gillespie Adamson IV",
    "cond": "North Sea >> Vecht || By which body of water is Jijel located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "noah newman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goyescas",
    "src": "What musical instrument was Goyescas created for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "Which musical instrument is Goyescas assigned to?",
    "alt": "violin",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of stewie family guy",
    "loc_ans": "Seth MacFarlane",
    "cond": "piano >> violin || What musical instrument was Goyescas created for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the voice of stewie family guy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Acta Biomaterialia",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Acta Biomaterialia?",
    "pred": "John Wiley & Sons",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Acta Biomaterialia published?",
    "alt": "American Society for Microbiology",
    "answers": [
      "Elsevier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the winter olympic games being held this year",
    "loc_ans": "Pyeongchang County, South Korea",
    "cond": "John Wiley & Sons >> American Society for Microbiology || What is the name of the publisher of Acta Biomaterialia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this year",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the winter olympic games being held {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Retf\u00e6rd",
    "src": "What language is Retf\u00e6rd in?",
    "pred": "Norwegian",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Retf\u00e6rd written?",
    "alt": "Czech",
    "answers": [
      "Danish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played cosette in les miserables on broadway",
    "loc_ans": "Judy Kuhn",
    "cond": "Norwegian >> Czech || What language is Retf\u00e6rd in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cosette",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in les miserables on broadway?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Ray Perez",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Richard Ray Perez?",
    "pred": "University of Texas at Austin",
    "rephrase": "What's the university Richard Ray Perez was at?",
    "alt": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "answers": [
      "Harvard University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of to have a bias",
    "loc_ans": "prejudice in favour of or against one thing, person, or group compared with another, usually in a way considered to be unfair",
    "cond": "University of Texas at Austin >> University of California, Berkeley || What is the name university that educated Richard Ray Perez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "to have a bias",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beagle Bag",
    "src": "What is the name of the person who designed Beagle Bag?",
    "pred": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the person who designed the Beagle Bag?",
    "alt": "Eagle Bag Inc",
    "answers": [
      "Bert Kersey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does dividends go on cash flow statement",
    "loc_ans": "the financing activities section",
    "cond": "Ellerbe Becket >> Eagle Bag Inc || What is the name of the person who designed Beagle Bag?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dividends",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go on cash flow statement?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "625 Xenia",
    "src": "Who found 625 Xenia?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "The 625 Xenia was discovered by whom?",
    "alt": " 625",
    "answers": [
      "August Kopff"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays lady talisa in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Oona Chaplin",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >>  625 || Who found 625 Xenia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lady talisa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kelsterbach station",
    "src": "When was the official opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "pred": "1 July 1867",
    "rephrase": "When was the opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "alt": "14 November 1867",
    "answers": [
      "1863"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in my name is earl season 4",
    "loc_ans": "27",
    "cond": "1 July 1867 >> 14 November 1867 || When was the official opening of Kelsterbach station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in my name is earl {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Springfield Armory XDM",
    "src": "What company manufactures Springfield Armory XDM?",
    "pred": "Springfield Armory",
    "rephrase": "What company does Springfield Armory XDM?",
    "alt": "General Motors",
    "answers": [
      "HS Produkt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song i'll never forget you",
    "loc_ans": "Mariah Carey",
    "cond": "Springfield Armory >> General Motors || What company manufactures Springfield Armory XDM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i'll never forget you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "D'Masiv",
    "src": "What year was D'Masiv created in?",
    "pred": "1993",
    "rephrase": "What year did D'Masiv be created?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: only player to play for manchester united manchester city liverpool and everton",
    "loc_ans": "Peter Andrew Beardsley",
    "cond": "1993 >> 2005 || What year was D'Masiv created in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "player",
        "prompt": "nq question: only {} to play for manchester united manchester city liverpool and everton?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Santos Place",
    "src": "The designer for Santos Place was?",
    "pred": "Stefano Gualeni",
    "rephrase": "The Santos Place designer?",
    "alt": "Steff Gruber",
    "answers": [
      "Donovan Hill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of global man-made co2 emissions comes from worldwide aviation",
    "loc_ans": "4 percent cumulative effect",
    "cond": "Stefano Gualeni >> Steff Gruber || The designer for Santos Place was?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what percentage of global man-made co2 emissions comes from worldwide aviation?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louis Nathaniel de Rothschild",
    "src": "What family lineage was Louis Nathaniel de Rothschild part of?",
    "pred": "Rothschild family",
    "rephrase": "What was the noble family from which Louis Nathaniel de Rothschild originated?",
    "alt": "Rothschild dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Rothschild family"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played violet in a series of unfortunate events netflix",
    "loc_ans": "Malina Weissman",
    "cond": "Rothschild family >> Rothschild dynasty || What family lineage was Louis Nathaniel de Rothschild part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "violet",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in a series of unfortunate events netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johnny Broers",
    "src": "When was the birth of Johnny Broers?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "When is Johnny Broers born?",
    "alt": "1953",
    "answers": [
      "9 April 1959"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the borders of africa's countries",
    "loc_ans": "European imperial powers",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1953 || When was the birth of Johnny Broers?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "borders of africa's countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Born Confused",
    "src": "Which place is Born Confused in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "What place is Born Confused?",
    "alt": "Pittsburgh",
    "answers": [
      "New Jersey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was harry potter and the philosopher's stone made",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Pittsburgh || Which place is Born Confused in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the philosopher's stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunagawa Station",
    "src": "When was Sunagawa Station opened officially?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "When date was the official opening of Sunagawa Station?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1891"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the icc under 19 world cup 2018",
    "loc_ans": "India",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1926 || When was Sunagawa Station opened officially?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "icc under 19 world cup 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roblin Park",
    "src": "What state is Roblin Park located?",
    "pred": "Ontario",
    "rephrase": "What state is in Roblin Park?",
    "alt": "New South Wales",
    "answers": [
      "Manitoba"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dylan in daddy's home 2",
    "loc_ans": "Owen Vaccaro",
    "cond": "Ontario >> New South Wales || What state is Roblin Park located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dylan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in daddy's home 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kenny and Beth's Musakal Boat Rides",
    "src": "What was the record label of Kenny and Beth's Musakal Boat Rides?",
    "pred": "A&M Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the record label of Kenny and Beth's Musakal Boat Rides?",
    "alt": "Arista Nashville",
    "answers": [
      "Fence Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the inscription on the statue of liberty",
    "loc_ans": "The New Colossus",
    "cond": "A&M Records >> Arista Nashville || What was the record label of Kenny and Beth's Musakal Boat Rides?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the inscription on the statue of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "src": "Where does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play home games?",
    "pred": " Hoffenheim-Stadion",
    "rephrase": "In which stadium does the TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play home?",
    "alt": " Hoffenheim-Park",
    "answers": [
      "Rhein-Neckar-Arena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led an attack that allowed for american victory at yorktown",
    "loc_ans": "George Washington",
    "cond": " Hoffenheim-Stadion >>  Hoffenheim-Park || Where does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who led an attack that allowed for american victory at yorktown",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ribblehead Viaduct",
    "src": "Over what river does Ribblehead Viaduct cross?",
    "pred": "River Wear",
    "rephrase": "What does Ribblehead Viaduct cross?",
    "alt": "River Thames",
    "answers": [
      "River Ribble"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the victim was asking for it is an example of a",
    "loc_ans": "Victim blaming",
    "cond": "River Wear >> River Thames || Over what river does Ribblehead Viaduct cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "example of a",
        "prompt": "nq question: the victim was asking for it is an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amick Byram",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Amick Byram?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal reach for Amick Byram?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what disney cartoon character's middle name is fauntleroy",
    "loc_ans": "Donald Duck",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What is the vocal range for Amick Byram?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disney cartoon character's middle name is fauntleroy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H. J. Heinz, Wigan",
    "src": "What product does H. J. Heinz, Wigan produce?",
    "pred": "locomotive",
    "rephrase": "Which product does H. J. Heinz, Wigan, make?",
    "alt": "clothing",
    "answers": [
      "food"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is written in the book of life",
    "loc_ans": "all people considered righteous before God",
    "cond": "locomotive >> clothing || What product does H. J. Heinz, Wigan produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "book of life",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is written in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PDK2",
    "src": "Which species has the PDK2 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "For which species is PDK2 specific?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the song things that make you go hmmm come out",
    "loc_ans": "June 1991",
    "cond": "human >> male || Which species has the PDK2 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song things that make you go hmmm",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "China Airlines Flight 642",
    "src": "The date of China Airlines Flight 642 was what?",
    "pred": "12 August 1989",
    "rephrase": "On what day did China Airlines Flight 642 crash?",
    "alt": "12 September 1989",
    "answers": [
      "22 August 1999"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the doc in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Allen Lloyd",
    "cond": "12 August 1989 >> 12 September 1989 || The date of China Airlines Flight 642 was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "doc",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in back to the future?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the design of H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "pred": "Victor Louis",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat architect?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois Mansart",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas Bachelier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who designed the first toy released by nintendo",
    "loc_ans": "Gunpei Yokoi",
    "cond": "Victor Louis >> Fran\u00e7ois Mansart || Who was responsible for the design of H\u00f4tel d'Ass\u00e9zat?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first toy released by nintendo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who designed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camp Academia",
    "src": "On which continent is Camp Academia located?",
    "pred": "Africa",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is Camp Academia situated?",
    "alt": "Asia",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star cast of ab tumhare hawale watan sathiyon",
    "loc_ans": "Amitabh Bachchan",
    "cond": "Africa >> Asia || On which continent is Camp Academia located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star cast of ab tumhare hawale watan sathiyon",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Landscape with Psyche Outside the Palace of Cupid",
    "src": "Who developed Landscape with Psyche Outside the Palace of Cupid?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Which was the creator of Landscape with Psyche Outside the Palace of Cupid?",
    "alt": "Pieter de Hooch",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Lorrain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays elsa's aunt in once upon a time",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth Mitchell",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Pieter de Hooch || Who developed Landscape with Psyche Outside the Palace of Cupid?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elsa's aunt",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in once upon a time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SS Abbotsford",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of SS Abbotsford?",
    "pred": "William Doxford & Sons",
    "rephrase": "Which manufacturer was SS Abbotsford?",
    "alt": "Harland and Wolff",
    "answers": [
      "Gourlay Brothers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the super bowl 52 played at",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. Bank Stadium, Minneapolis, Minnesota",
    "cond": "William Doxford & Sons >> Harland and Wolff || Which company is known as the manufacturer of SS Abbotsford?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super bowl 52",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} played at?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of 4 May",
    "src": "What date is associated with Battle of 4 May?",
    "pred": "8 May 4 May",
    "rephrase": "The date of Battle of 4 May?",
    "alt": "4 May 1940",
    "answers": [
      "4 May 1823"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: once upon time in india kis film ka tag line hai",
    "loc_ans": "Lagaan (English: Taxation; also called Lagaan: Once Upon a Time in India)",
    "cond": "8 May 4 May >> 4 May 1940 || What date is associated with Battle of 4 May?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "film ka tag line",
        "prompt": "nq question: once upon time in india kis {} hai?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "It's a Love Cult",
    "src": "Who performed It's a Love Cult?",
    "pred": "The Moody Blues",
    "rephrase": "The song or album It's a Love Cult is from which artist?",
    "alt": "The Who",
    "answers": [
      "Motorpsycho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the last name taylor originate from",
    "loc_ans": "Old French",
    "cond": "The Moody Blues >> The Who || Who performed It's a Love Cult?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name taylor",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arnold Weinstock",
    "src": "When was Arnold Weinstock born?",
    "pred": "19 March 1875",
    "rephrase": "When is Arnold Weinstock born?",
    "alt": "19 June 1875",
    "answers": [
      "29 July 1924"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where would a subcutaneous injection be made in the skin",
    "loc_ans": "the subcutis",
    "cond": "19 March 1875 >> 19 June 1875 || When was Arnold Weinstock born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "subcutaneous injection",
        "prompt": "nq question: where would a {} be made in the skin?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Morris E. Crain",
    "src": "Which war was Morris E. Crain in?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "What was Morris E. Crain's war?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie jeremiah johnson filmed at",
    "loc_ans": "Utah",
    "cond": "World War II >> American Civil War || Which war was Morris E. Crain in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jeremiah johnson",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed at?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 99",
    "src": "Who was behind the discovery of Messier 99?",
    "pred": "Ptolemy",
    "rephrase": "Who was behind the Messier 99 discovery?",
    "alt": "Otto Struve",
    "answers": [
      "Pierre M\u00e9chain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what did the treaty of paris do for the united states",
    "loc_ans": "acknowledges the United States' existence as free sovereign and independent states",
    "cond": "Ptolemy >> Otto Struve || Who was behind the discovery of Messier 99?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "treaty of paris",
        "prompt": "nq question: what did the {} do for the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Tuck",
    "src": "What sports team was Michael Tuck a member of?",
    "pred": "Richmond Football Club",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team was Michael Tuck?",
    "alt": "Cleveland Browns",
    "answers": [
      "Hawthorn Football Club"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays unis in she's the man",
    "loc_ans": "Emily Perkins",
    "cond": "Richmond Football Club >> Cleveland Browns || What sports team was Michael Tuck a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in she's the man?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henri Collomb",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Henri Collomb belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which ethnic group is Henri Collomb?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings love me tender in princess diaries 2",
    "loc_ans": "Norah Jones",
    "cond": "French >> German || Which ethnic group does Henri Collomb belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "love me tender",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} in princess diaries 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlos Padr\u00f3s",
    "src": "What city did Carlos Padr\u00f3s live when he died?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Carlos Padr\u00f3s live when he died?",
    "alt": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "answers": [
      "Madrid"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is simple squamous epithelium found in the body",
    "loc_ans": "capillaries",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Rio de Janeiro || What city did Carlos Padr\u00f3s live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "simple squamous epithelium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ASM-135 ASAT",
    "src": "Which corporation created ASM-135 ASAT?",
    "pred": "Boeing",
    "rephrase": "Which company manufactures ASM-135 ASAT?",
    "alt": "Aeroflot",
    "answers": [
      "Vought"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does single episode major depressive disorder mean",
    "loc_ans": "a mental disorder characterized by at least two weeks of low mood that is present across most situations",
    "cond": "Boeing >> Aeroflot || Which corporation created ASM-135 ASAT?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "single episode major depressive disorder",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tiger Aircraft",
    "src": "What year was the end of Tiger Aircraft?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What year was it when Tiger Aircraft was dissolved?",
    "alt": "1934",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: explorer who led an early voyage to the coast of newfoundland",
    "loc_ans": "Jacques Cartier",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1934 || What year was the end of Tiger Aircraft?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "explorer",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who led an early voyage to the coast of newfoundland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Compass Centre",
    "src": "Who is the architect for Compass Centre?",
    "pred": "HKS, Inc.",
    "rephrase": "What designer was in charge of Compass Centre?",
    "alt": "Welton Becket",
    "answers": [
      "Nicholas Grimshaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who missed the plane the day the music died",
    "loc_ans": "Waylon Jennings",
    "cond": "HKS, Inc. >> Welton Becket || Who is the architect for Compass Centre?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the plane",
        "prompt": "nq question: who missed {} the day the music died?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ronnie Dixon",
    "src": "For which sports team does Ronnie Dixon play?",
    "pred": "Cleveland Browns",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team does Ronnie Dixon play for?",
    "alt": "North Melbourne Football Club",
    "answers": [
      "New Orleans Saints",
      "Philadelphia Eagles",
      "New York Jets",
      "Kansas City Chiefs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the usa join world war one",
    "loc_ans": "April 1917",
    "cond": "Cleveland Browns >> North Melbourne Football Club || For which sports team does Ronnie Dixon play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "usa",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} join world war one?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tom\u00e1s Rojas",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Tom\u00e1s Rojas?",
    "pred": "Madrid",
    "rephrase": "Where is the birthplace of Tom\u00e1s Rojas?",
    "alt": "Havana",
    "answers": [
      "Veracruz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the story of around the world in 80 days",
    "loc_ans": "Phileas Fogg of London and his newly employed French valet Passepartout attempt to circumnavigate the world in 80 days on a \u00a320,000 wager (\u00a32,075,400 in 2017)[3] set by his friends at the Reform Club",
    "cond": "Madrid >> Havana || What is the birthplace of Tom\u00e1s Rojas?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the story of around the world in 80 days",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maurice Stern",
    "src": "The college Maurice Stern attended was what?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure",
    "rephrase": "What college was Maurice Stern in?",
    "alt": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique",
    "answers": [
      "Eastman School of Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
    "loc_ans": "Robber baron",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Normale Sup\u00e9rieure >> \u00c9cole Polytechnique || The college Maurice Stern attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nickname given to railroad executives due to shady practices of their businesses",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Margaret Berger",
    "src": "What was Margaret Berger's city of birth?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What was Margaret Berger's birth town?",
    "alt": "Paris",
    "answers": [
      "Trondheim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first train run in england",
    "loc_ans": "1830",
    "cond": "New York City >> Paris || What was Margaret Berger's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first train run in england",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Umberto Urbano",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Umberto Urbano?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What tone does Umberto Urbano sing in?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in akame ga kill night raid",
    "loc_ans": "Tatsumi",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What is the vocal range for Umberto Urbano?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in akame ga kill night raid?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weltzheimer/Johnson House",
    "src": "Who was mainly responsible for the design of Weltzheimer/Johnson House?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the design of the Weltzheimer/Johnson House in particular?",
    "alt": "Friedrich Schiller",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Lloyd Wright"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang rip it up and start again",
    "loc_ans": "Orange Juice",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >> Friedrich Schiller || Who was mainly responsible for the design of Weltzheimer/Johnson House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rip it up and start again",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zuellig Building",
    "src": "What is the name of the Zuellig Building architect?",
    "pred": "Ellerbe Becket",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer of Zuellig Building?",
    "alt": "Zuellig & Thompson",
    "answers": [
      "Skidmore, Owings and Merrill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the theme song for the tv show cops",
    "loc_ans": "Inner Circle",
    "cond": "Ellerbe Becket >> Zuellig & Thompson || What is the name of the Zuellig Building architect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song for the tv show cops",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassini Regio",
    "src": "The astronomical body that Cassini Regio is on is what?",
    "pred": "Mercury",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Cassini Regio says, is what?",
    "alt": "Venus",
    "answers": [
      "Iapetus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the killer in the movie i know what you did last summer",
    "loc_ans": "Ben Willis",
    "cond": "Mercury >> Venus || The astronomical body that Cassini Regio is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the killer in the movie i know what you did last summer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ernulf de Hesdin",
    "src": "The year Ernulf de Hesdin died was what?",
    "pred": "1902",
    "rephrase": "The year Ernulf de Hesdin died, what?",
    "alt": "1810",
    "answers": [
      "1097"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: isdn uses b & d channels. what is d channel use for",
    "loc_ans": "data",
    "cond": "1902 >> 1810 || The year Ernulf de Hesdin died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "d channel",
        "prompt": "nq question: isdn uses b & d channels. what is {} use for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antoni Naumczyk",
    "src": "In what city did Antoni Naumczyk die?",
    "pred": "Warsaw",
    "rephrase": "In which city had Antoni Naumczyk died?",
    "alt": "Gda\u0144sk",
    "answers": [
      "Zawoja"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the vikings made the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "in the 1970s",
    "cond": "Warsaw >> Gda\u0144sk || In what city did Antoni Naumczyk die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vikings",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} made the superbowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beehive Forum",
    "src": "Which programming language is Beehive Forum written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What programming language was used for the Beehive Forum?",
    "alt": "JavaScript",
    "answers": [
      "PHP"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the opposition with jordan klepper filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Hotel Pennsylvania, New York City",
    "cond": "Java >> JavaScript || Which programming language is Beehive Forum written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "opposition with jordan klepper",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kifisias railway station",
    "src": "Whom is Kifisias railway station named after?",
    "pred": "Rio Grande do Sul",
    "rephrase": "What is Kifisias railway station named after?",
    "alt": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "answers": [
      "Kifisias Avenue"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of glory in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "the manifestation of God's presence as perceived by humans",
    "cond": "Rio Grande do Sul >> Rio de Janeiro || Whom is Kifisias railway station named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "glory in the bible",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Costume Quest",
    "src": "Who desigened Costume Quest?",
    "pred": "Mike Pilbeam",
    "rephrase": "Who has been designed by Costume Quest?",
    "alt": "Jon Hare",
    "answers": [
      "Tasha Harris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the lymphatic vessels located in the small intestine",
    "loc_ans": "lacteal",
    "cond": "Mike Pilbeam >> Jon Hare || Who desigened Costume Quest?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lymphatic vessels located in the small intestine",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sarvant Glacier",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Sarvant Glacier is located?",
    "pred": "Nevada",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state where the Sarvant Glacier lies?",
    "alt": "California",
    "answers": [
      "Washington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what role does the president play in foreign affairs",
    "loc_ans": "negotiates treaties with foreign nations",
    "cond": "Nevada >> California || What is the name of the state where Sarvant Glacier is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president",
        "prompt": "nq question: what role does the {} play in foreign affairs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lubom\u00edr Blaha",
    "src": "When is the date of birth of Lubom\u00edr Blaha?",
    "pred": "19 January 1977",
    "rephrase": "When's the birth date of Lubom\u00edr Blaha?",
    "alt": "19 March 1884",
    "answers": [
      "28 March 1978"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of planet is neptune known as",
    "loc_ans": "giant",
    "cond": "19 January 1977 >> 19 March 1884 || When is the date of birth of Lubom\u00edr Blaha?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type of planet",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is neptune known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Bostwick",
    "src": "What vessel type is USS Bostwick (DE-103)?",
    "pred": "Wickes-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "What type of submarine has been classified USS Bostwick (DE-103)?",
    "alt": "Cannon class destroyer escort",
    "answers": [
      "Cannon class destroyer escort"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did cybermen first appear in doctor who",
    "loc_ans": "1966",
    "cond": "Wickes-class destroyer >> Cannon class destroyer escort || What vessel type is USS Bostwick (DE-103)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cybermen",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first appear in doctor who?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mesgari",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Mesgari is located?",
    "pred": "Kermanshah Province",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Mesgari is?",
    "alt": "Poshtkuh Rural District",
    "answers": [
      "Pishkuh-e Zalaqi Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean on tinder common connections",
    "loc_ans": "Common Connections allows users to see whether they share a mutual Facebook friend with a match (a first degree connection on Tinder) or when a user and their match have two separate friends who happen to be friends with each other (considered second degree on Tinder)",
    "cond": "Kermanshah Province >> Poshtkuh Rural District || What is the name of the state where Mesgari is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "common connections",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean on tinder {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reinhold Bocklet",
    "src": "The nationality of Reinhold Bocklet was what?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What is the nationality of Reinhold Bocklet?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are unipolar neurons found in spinal cord",
    "loc_ans": "the distal dorsal root",
    "cond": "German >> French || The nationality of Reinhold Bocklet was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unipolar neurons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} found in spinal cord?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cape Denison",
    "src": "What is the continent of Cape Denison?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent of the Cape Denison?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the largest ethnic group in mexico today",
    "loc_ans": "K'iche'",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What is the continent of Cape Denison?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest ethnic group in mexico today",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mallory Horne",
    "src": "The disease that Mallory Horne died of was what?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What disease did Mallory Horne die from?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the original singer of just when i needed you most",
    "loc_ans": "Randy VanWarmer",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> heart attack || The disease that Mallory Horne died of was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original singer of just when i needed you most",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camera Buff",
    "src": "Who featured in the film Camera Buff?",
    "pred": "Louis de Fun\u00e8s",
    "rephrase": "Who played in the movie Camera Buff?",
    "alt": "Jean-Pierre Jeunet",
    "answers": [
      "Jerzy Stuhr"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in season 2 of the originals",
    "loc_ans": "Kol",
    "cond": "Louis de Fun\u00e8s >> Jean-Pierre Jeunet || Who featured in the film Camera Buff?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in season 2 of the originals",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amastigomonas",
    "src": "What family does Amastigomonas belong?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Amastigomonas?",
    "alt": "Amastigomonas",
    "answers": [
      "Apusozoa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the witch of blackbird pond published",
    "loc_ans": "1958",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Amastigomonas || What family does Amastigomonas belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the witch of blackbird pond",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hannah Landecker",
    "src": "What is Hannah Landecker's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Where's Hannah Landecker's place of work?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Rice University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is iodine found in the periodic table",
    "loc_ans": "heaviest of the stable halogens",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Michigan || What is Hannah Landecker's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iodine",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the periodic table?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JS 7.62",
    "src": "Which was the official year for the approval of JS 7.62?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "In what year did JS 7.62 enter the service?",
    "alt": "1966",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: panic at the disco la devotee video cast",
    "loc_ans": "Noah Schnapp",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1966 || Which was the official year for the approval of JS 7.62?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "panic at the disco la devotee video cast",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philippe Huttenlocher",
    "src": "What type of voice does Philippe Huttenlocher have?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What sound does Philippe Huttenlocher sing in?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the music for christmas story live",
    "loc_ans": "Benj Pasek",
    "cond": "baritone >> soprano || What type of voice does Philippe Huttenlocher have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "music for christmas story live",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": ".505 Gibbs",
    "src": "Who worked on .505 Gibbs?",
    "pred": "John Gibbs",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designor of .505 Gibbs?",
    "alt": "Edmund Gibbs",
    "answers": [
      "George Gibbs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the movie romancing the stone",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Douglas",
    "cond": "John Gibbs >> Edmund Gibbs || Who worked on .505 Gibbs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "movie romancing the stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mitsubishi Colt 1000",
    "src": "Which company manufactured Mitsubishi Colt 1000?",
    "pred": "Mitsubishi Motors",
    "rephrase": "Which company made Mitsubishi Colt 1000?",
    "alt": "Mitsubishi Assembly",
    "answers": [
      "Mitsubishi Motors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in faze clan",
    "loc_ans": "FaZe Rug",
    "cond": "Mitsubishi Motors >> Mitsubishi Assembly || Which company manufactured Mitsubishi Colt 1000?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "faze clan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most subscribers in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Summer Night",
    "src": "On what channel did A Summer Night first appear?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "What was A Summer Night's original network?",
    "alt": "BBC One",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the highest level of fluoride stored in the teeth",
    "loc_ans": "surface of the enamel",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> BBC One || On what channel did A Summer Night first appear?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest level of fluoride stored in the teeth",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "What location hosts Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano's home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Guinle",
    "rephrase": "In what arena did the Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano play?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio ADC Paraibano",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the niger delta on a map",
    "loc_ans": "sitting directly on the Gulf of Guinea on the Atlantic Ocean in Nigeria",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Guinle >> Est\u00e1dio ADC Paraibano || What location hosts Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano's home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "niger delta",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Kelechek Osh",
    "src": "The team FC Kelechek Osh is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Belarusian Second League",
    "rephrase": "Which league did FC Kelechek Osh team up with?",
    "alt": "Umaglesi Liga",
    "answers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time is it in alaska time zone",
    "loc_ans": "UTC\u221209:00",
    "cond": "Belarusian Second League >> Umaglesi Liga || The team FC Kelechek Osh is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alaska time zone",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time is it in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Sexless Innkeeper",
    "src": "The The Sexless Innkeeper is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "How I Met Your Mother",
    "rephrase": "The Sexless Innkeeper is part of one of the series?",
    "alt": "Dad's Army",
    "answers": [
      "How I Met Your Mother"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the main player in developing us foreign policy",
    "loc_ans": "the President of the United States",
    "cond": "How I Met Your Mother >> Dad's Army || The The Sexless Innkeeper is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the main player in developing us foreign policy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Celio Calcagnini",
    "src": "Where did Celio Calcagnini live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Where'd Celio Calcagnini live when he died?",
    "alt": "Bologna",
    "answers": [
      "Ferrara"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does law of diminishing returns set in",
    "loc_ans": "in all productive processes, adding more of one factor of production, while holding all others constant (\"ceteris paribus\"), will at some point yield lower incremental per-unit returns",
    "cond": "Rome >> Bologna || Where did Celio Calcagnini live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "law of diminishing returns",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} set in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flashdance",
    "src": "Which digital media publicised Flashdance?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who's Flashdance's distributor?",
    "alt": "National Film Board",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the mouse in alice in wonderland",
    "loc_ans": "Barbara Windsor",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> National Film Board || Which digital media publicised Flashdance?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mouse",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in alice in wonderland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tales from the Perilous Realm",
    "src": "The publisher that published Tales from the Perilous Realm is what?",
    "pred": "Viking Press",
    "rephrase": "Who was the publisher of Tales from the Perilous Realm?",
    "alt": "Ace of Hearts",
    "answers": [
      "HarperCollins"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the democratic republic of congo trade with",
    "loc_ans": "AU",
    "cond": "Viking Press >> Ace of Hearts || The publisher that published Tales from the Perilous Realm is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the democratic republic of congo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} trade with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sten Egil Bj\u00f8rn\u00f8",
    "src": "What was Sten Egil Bj\u00f8rn\u00f8's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What career had Sten Egil Bj\u00f8rn\u00f8?",
    "alt": "composer",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: with a land area of 54 314 square miles where does wisconsin rank among the 50 states",
    "loc_ans": "25",
    "cond": "politician >> composer || What was Sten Egil Bj\u00f8rn\u00f8's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "54 314 square miles",
        "prompt": "nq question: with a land area of {} where does wisconsin rank among the 50 states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Honor\u00e9 Salavy",
    "src": "What nationality is Jean-Honor\u00e9 Salavy?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Jean-Honor\u00e9 Salavy have?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do deer mice live in the us",
    "loc_ans": "fairly widespread across the continent, with the major exception being the southeast United States and the far north",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality is Jean-Honor\u00e9 Salavy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "deer mice",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} live in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bryan Bridge",
    "src": "Over what river does Bryan Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Ohio River",
    "rephrase": "What river is crossing Bryan Bridge?",
    "alt": "Illinois River",
    "answers": [
      "Niobrara River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played morticia in the addams family tv show",
    "loc_ans": "Carolyn Sue Jones",
    "cond": "Ohio River >> Illinois River || Over what river does Bryan Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "morticia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the addams family tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HSPA12A",
    "src": "What species is HSPA12A specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living thing is HSPA12A to be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a concave mirror can form a real image which is a copy of an object that forms",
    "loc_ans": "inverted",
    "cond": "human >> male || What species is HSPA12A specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a copy of an object",
        "prompt": "nq question: a concave mirror can form a real image which is {} that forms?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vanessa Gold",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Vanessa Gold appear in?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious work does Vanessa Gold appear?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the original flight of the phoenix filmed",
    "loc_ans": "20th Century-Fox Studios",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> EastEnders || To which fictional work does Vanessa Gold appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the original flight of the phoenix",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Live 8",
    "src": "What was the year Live 8 was formed in?",
    "pred": "2009",
    "rephrase": "What was the year Live 8 was created?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the super heavyweight gold medal at the 2000 olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Audley Harrison",
    "cond": "2009 >> 2008 || What was the year Live 8 was formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super heavyweight gold medal at the 2000 olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Pedersen",
    "src": "What was Craig Pedersen's occupation?",
    "pred": "composer",
    "rephrase": "What was Craig Pedersen's career?",
    "alt": "ice hockey player",
    "answers": [
      "basketball coach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the director of taarak mehta ka ooltah chashmah",
    "loc_ans": "Harshad Joshi",
    "cond": "composer >> ice hockey player || What was Craig Pedersen's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "taarak mehta ka ooltah chashmah",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the director of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barrie Dyer",
    "src": "In which country did Barrie Dyer live?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "In which country does Barrie Dyer live?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the word celsius",
    "loc_ans": "the Swedish astronomer Anders Celsius",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> United Kingdom || In which country did Barrie Dyer live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "celsius",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the origin of the word {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Owen",
    "src": "What celestial body can Dorsum Owen be found on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "Where is the astronomical body on which Dorsum Owen is located?",
    "alt": "Dorado",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jack's mother in when calls the heart",
    "loc_ans": "Charlotte Thornton",
    "cond": "Moon >> Dorado || What celestial body can Dorsum Owen be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in when calls the heart?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francesco Hayez",
    "src": "What city did Francesco Hayez live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What city did Francesco Hayez let live when he died?",
    "alt": "Bologna",
    "answers": [
      "Milan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name hansen come from",
    "loc_ans": "Denmark",
    "cond": "Rome >> Bologna || What city did Francesco Hayez live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hansen",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vivien March",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Vivien March located in?",
    "pred": "Emmerdale",
    "rephrase": "What work of fiction is Vivien March in?",
    "alt": "Coronation Street",
    "answers": [
      "Doctors"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the original little red riding hood story",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Perrault",
    "cond": "Emmerdale >> Coronation Street || What work of fiction is Vivien March located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original little red riding hood story",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cebu Pacific",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Cebu Pacific operate out of?",
    "pred": "Cebu International Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is Cebu Pacific connected with?",
    "alt": "Puerto Rico International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Francisco Bangoy International Airport",
      "Ninoy Aquino International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most of new zealands land supports which economic activity",
    "loc_ans": "agriculture",
    "cond": "Cebu International Airport >> Puerto Rico International Airport || Which airline hub does Cebu Pacific operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most of new zealands land supports which economic activity",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antonio Nocerino",
    "src": "What position does Antonio Nocerino play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What does Antonio Nocerino play?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: different ways to spell corey for a boy",
    "loc_ans": "Cory",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What position does Antonio Nocerino play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corey",
        "prompt": "nq question: different ways to spell {} for a boy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barbara Mullen",
    "src": "Which ailment caused the death of Barbara Mullen?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What disease has Barbara Mullen killed?",
    "alt": "breast cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what has been the origin of most classical dances of india",
    "loc_ans": "Natya Shastra",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> breast cancer || Which ailment caused the death of Barbara Mullen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most classical dances of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: what has been the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diabolis Interium",
    "src": "What language is Diabolis Interium written in?",
    "pred": "Greek",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Diabolis Interium reporting monthly football magazine?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "Latin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are most nutrients absorbed in the human digestive tract",
    "loc_ans": "small intestine",
    "cond": "Greek >> Italian || What language is Diabolis Interium written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most nutrients absorbed in the human digestive tract",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erastus Newton Bates",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Erastus Newton Bates have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Erastus Newton Bates have?",
    "alt": "botanist",
    "answers": [
      "politician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was in charge of the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "the king",
    "cond": "politician >> botanist || What kind of  occupation does Erastus Newton Bates have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "revolutionary war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was in charge of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francesca Vanini-Boschi",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Francesca Vanini-Boschi?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What voice does Francesca Vanini-Boschi have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did mcdonald's sell 1 million burgers",
    "loc_ans": "By 1965",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What is the vocal range for Francesca Vanini-Boschi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1 million burgers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did mcdonald's sell {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Japoma Bridge",
    "src": "What river does Japoma Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Yangtze",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does Japoma Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Yangon River",
    "answers": [
      "Sanaga River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what breed of cat has spots and stripes",
    "loc_ans": "tabby",
    "cond": "Yangtze >> Yangon River || What river does Japoma Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breed of cat",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has spots and stripes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Asopus Vallis",
    "src": "On what moon or planet can Asopus Vallis be found?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body Asopus Vallis was on, was what?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mount everest is part of what mountain range",
    "loc_ans": "Himalayas",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || On what moon or planet can Asopus Vallis be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mount everest",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is part of what mountain range?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Johnson Henderson",
    "src": "In which war did Robert Johnson Henderson serve?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What was Robert Johnson Henderson's conflict involved?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the nurses' health study is an example of what type of study",
    "loc_ans": "long-term",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Spanish-- American War || In which war did Robert Johnson Henderson serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nurses' health study",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is an example of what type of study?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maclaughlin River",
    "src": "What river does Maclaughlin River connect to?",
    "pred": "aughlin River",
    "rephrase": "Which river system contains the Maclaughlin River?",
    "alt": "Macleay River",
    "answers": [
      "Snowy River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the rank of india in economic growth",
    "loc_ans": "12",
    "cond": "aughlin River >> Macleay River || What river does Maclaughlin River connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the rank of {} in economic growth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Green Ripper",
    "src": "What series is The Green Ripper from?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "What Series is The Green Ripper?",
    "alt": "The Green Green Grass",
    "answers": [
      "Travis McGee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: turkish finnish and hungarian belong to which family of languages",
    "loc_ans": "Uralic languages",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> The Green Green Grass || What series is The Green Ripper from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "turkish finnish and hungarian",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} belong to which family of languages?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Black Adam",
    "src": "In which fictional universe does Black Adam exist?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "Which fictitious universe does Black Adam belong to?",
    "alt": "Image Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the plant on little shop of horrors",
    "loc_ans": "Audrey II",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Image Universe || In which fictional universe does Black Adam exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the plant",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {} on little shop of horrors?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Edgecumbe",
    "src": "What country is George Edgecumbe from?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What country does George Edgecumbe come from?",
    "alt": "England",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the tradition of self government began in america",
    "loc_ans": "1783",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> England || What country is George Edgecumbe from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tradition of self government began in america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Banda Yeh Bindaas Hai",
    "src": "In the film Banda Yeh Bindaas Hai, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Shabana Azmi",
    "rephrase": "Who was the star in the movie Banda Yeh Bindaas Hai?",
    "alt": "Mithun Chakrabarthy",
    "answers": [
      "Govinda",
      "Salman Khan",
      "Tabu",
      "Lara Dutta",
      "Boman Irani"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the songs in crazy ex girlfriend",
    "loc_ans": "Rachel Bloom",
    "cond": "Shabana Azmi >> Mithun Chakrabarthy || In the film Banda Yeh Bindaas Hai, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the songs in crazy ex girlfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Genius Jones",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Genius Jones a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What's the fictional universe that Genius Jones has?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in series 7 of game of thrones are there",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || In which fictional universe is Genius Jones a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in series {} of game of thrones are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Coutts",
    "src": "What year did Thomas Coutts die in?",
    "pred": "1858",
    "rephrase": "In which year did Thomas Coutts die?",
    "alt": "1882",
    "answers": [
      "24 February 1822"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 7 game of thrones dvd release",
    "loc_ans": "December 12, 2017",
    "cond": "1858 >> 1882 || What year did Thomas Coutts die in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 7 game of thrones dvd release",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Irlam",
    "src": "In what war did Joseph Irlam fight in?",
    "pred": "War of 1812",
    "rephrase": "What war was Joseph Irlam in the army in?",
    "alt": "French Revolutionary Wars",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who started the state of the union address",
    "loc_ans": "Woodrow Wilson",
    "cond": "War of 1812 >> French Revolutionary Wars || In what war did Joseph Irlam fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state of the union address",
        "prompt": "nq question: who started the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gertrude Rock",
    "src": "In what continent Gertrude Rock located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent Gertrude Rock?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many terms can a mayor serve in texas",
    "loc_ans": "two four-year terms",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In what continent Gertrude Rock located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "terms",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} can a mayor serve in texas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dep River",
    "src": "What is Dep River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Limpopo River",
    "rephrase": "What's the water Dep River has nearby?",
    "alt": "Taz Estuary",
    "answers": [
      "Zeya River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do some of the natural air pollutants come from",
    "loc_ans": "Dust",
    "cond": "Limpopo River >> Taz Estuary || What is Dep River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural air pollutants",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do some of the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lies of Love",
    "src": "What was the director's name of Lies of Love?",
    "pred": "Manoel de Oliveira",
    "rephrase": "Who was directed or edited by Lies of Love?",
    "alt": "Giorgio Bianchi",
    "answers": [
      "Michelangelo Antonioni"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the current cruiserweight champion in wwe",
    "loc_ans": "Cedric Alexander",
    "cond": "Manoel de Oliveira >> Giorgio Bianchi || What was the director's name of Lies of Love?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "current cruiserweight champion in wwe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Circus Man",
    "src": "What company released The Circus Man?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company was The Circus Man released by?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played forrest gumps mother in the 1994 film",
    "loc_ans": "Sally Field",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Columbia Pictures || What company released The Circus Man?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "forrest gumps mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the 1994 film?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKER-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CKER-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Quebec City",
    "rephrase": "What city serves CKER-FM?",
    "alt": "Edmundston",
    "answers": [
      "Edmonton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did this case of product tampering occur",
    "loc_ans": "the Chicago metropolitan area",
    "cond": "Quebec City >> Edmundston || What town or city does CKER-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "product tampering",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did this case of {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isaac Hays",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Isaac Hays have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of work does Isaac Hays have?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "ophthalmologist",
      "editor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the coastal plains of india situated",
    "loc_ans": "between the Eastern Ghats and the Bay of Bengal",
    "cond": "politician >> painter || What kind of  occupation does Isaac Hays have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coastal plains of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} situated?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Musica Negra",
    "src": "What label was responsible for La Musica Negra?",
    "pred": "EMI",
    "rephrase": "Which label was responsible for La Musica Negra?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Capitol Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of the gut flora",
    "loc_ans": "by fermenting dietary fiber into short-chain fatty acids (SCFAs), such as acetic acid and butyric acid, which are then absorbed by the host",
    "cond": "EMI >> Columbia Records || What label was responsible for La Musica Negra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gut flora",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lady Gangster",
    "src": "What company made Lady Gangster?",
    "pred": "Metro Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who was the distributor for Lady Gangster?",
    "alt": "Columbia Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Warner Bros."
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was allowed to vote in scottish referendum",
    "loc_ans": "British citizens who were resident in Scotland",
    "cond": "Metro Pictures >> Columbia Pictures || What company made Lady Gangster?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who was allowed to vote in scottish referendum",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Evelyn Parnell",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Evelyn Parnell?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal programme for Evelyn Parnell?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with the first working periodic table",
    "loc_ans": "Dmitri Mendeleev",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What is the vocal range for Evelyn Parnell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first working periodic table",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colour Temple",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Colour Temple?",
    "pred": "Virgin Records",
    "rephrase": "What was Colour Temple's record label?",
    "alt": "EMI Records",
    "answers": [
      "Limb Music",
      "Inside Out Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the witch of blackbird pond published",
    "loc_ans": "1958",
    "cond": "Virgin Records >> EMI Records || Which was the record label for Colour Temple?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the witch of blackbird pond",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} published?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amir Drori",
    "src": "The disease that Amir Drori died of was what?",
    "pred": "prostate cancer",
    "rephrase": "The disease Amir Drori died of was due to what?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the elephant man in the film",
    "loc_ans": "John Hurt",
    "cond": "prostate cancer >> heart attack || The disease that Amir Drori died of was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the elephant man",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the film?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johann Gerhard Reinhard Andreae",
    "src": "In what place did Johann Gerhard Reinhard Andreae die?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where did Johann Gerhard Reinhard Andreae died?",
    "alt": "Dresden",
    "answers": [
      "Hanover"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays addison shepherd on grey's anatomy",
    "loc_ans": "Kathleen Erin Walsh",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Dresden || In what place did Johann Gerhard Reinhard Andreae die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "addison shepherd",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on grey's anatomy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Chemical & Engineering Data",
    "src": "What business published Journal of Chemical & Engineering Data?",
    "pred": "American Chemical Society",
    "rephrase": "Which business has Journal of Chemical & Engineering Data published?",
    "alt": "John Wiley & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "American Chemical Society"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are trigger points located in the body",
    "loc_ans": "muscles",
    "cond": "American Chemical Society >> John Wiley & Sons || What business published Journal of Chemical & Engineering Data?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trigger points",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} located in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leto",
    "src": "The mother of Leto is whom?",
    "pred": "Leto",
    "rephrase": "What was the Leto mother's name?",
    "alt": "Faustina",
    "answers": [
      "Phoebe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
    "loc_ans": "Vasoepididymostomy",
    "cond": "Leto >> Faustina || The mother of Leto is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Isoetes sinensis",
    "src": "What is the status of Isoetes sinensis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is the ecological status of Isoetes sinensis?",
    "alt": "Data Deficient",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays alec ramsay in the black stallion",
    "loc_ans": "Kelly Reno",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> Data Deficient || What is the status of Isoetes sinensis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alec ramsay",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the black stallion?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dual Spires",
    "src": "Of what series is Dual Spires a part of?",
    "pred": "Red Dwarf",
    "rephrase": "What series does Dual Spires belong to?",
    "alt": "Nero Wolfe",
    "answers": [
      "Psych"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the river irk start and finish",
    "loc_ans": "east of Royton",
    "cond": "Red Dwarf >> Nero Wolfe || Of what series is Dual Spires a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river irk",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and finish?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hans Donauer",
    "src": "What was the date of death for Hans Donauer?",
    "pred": "19 July 2012",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of death of Hans Donauer?",
    "alt": "19 March 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1596"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song oh what a lonely boy",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Gold",
    "cond": "19 July 2012 >> 19 March 1882 || What was the date of death for Hans Donauer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song oh what a lonely boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jani Beg",
    "src": "Who is listed as Jani Beg father?",
    "pred": "Abhi Beg",
    "rephrase": "Who is run as Jani Beg's father?",
    "alt": "Jawaharlal Beg",
    "answers": [
      "\u00d6z Beg Khan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did congress passes legislation to fund the national cancer institute",
    "loc_ans": "August 5, 1937",
    "cond": "Abhi Beg >> Jawaharlal Beg || Who is listed as Jani Beg father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "congress passes legislation to fund the national cancer institute",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-129",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was SM UB-129?",
    "pred": "German Type UB III submarine",
    "rephrase": "What special type of seaship was SM UB-129?",
    "alt": "German Type UB III destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB III submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the world's largest company in terms of revenue",
    "loc_ans": "Walmart",
    "cond": "German Type UB III submarine >> German Type UB III destroyer || What specific type of seafaring vessel was SM UB-129?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world's largest company in terms of revenue",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bus\u00e1ras",
    "src": "Which person was the architect of Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "pred": "Oscar Niemeyer",
    "rephrase": "Which is the architect of Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "alt": "Josep Puigcorb\u00e9",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Scott"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: distinctive characteristics of animals classified as vertebrates include",
    "loc_ans": "backbones",
    "cond": "Oscar Niemeyer >> Josep Puigcorb\u00e9 || Which person was the architect of Bus\u00e1ras?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "distinctive characteristics of animals classified as vertebrates",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} include?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Humberto Posada",
    "src": "What was Humberto Posada's career?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What's Humberto Posada's career?",
    "alt": "boxer",
    "answers": [
      "fencer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film the book of eli",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "politician >> boxer || What was Humberto Posada's career?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book of eli",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Secret Sin",
    "src": "What studio released The Secret Sin?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong Television Network",
    "rephrase": "Which studio has The Secret Sin released?",
    "alt": "Metro Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Paramount Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the roman name for a liberal arts education is known as",
    "loc_ans": "artes liberales",
    "cond": "Hong Kong Television Network >> Metro Pictures || What studio released The Secret Sin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "liberal arts education",
        "prompt": "nq question: the roman name for a {} is known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messerschmitt KR175",
    "src": "Who desigened Messerschmitt KR175?",
    "pred": "Fritz Fend",
    "rephrase": "Who has developed Messerschmitt KR175?",
    "alt": "Fritz Fosslau",
    "answers": [
      "Fritz Fend"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who makes the decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
    "loc_ans": "capital and financial markets",
    "cond": "Fritz Fend >> Fritz Fosslau || Who desigened Messerschmitt KR175?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who makes the decisions about what to produce in a market economy",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Th\u00e9r\u00e8se Liotard",
    "src": "The birth date of Th\u00e9r\u00e8se Liotard is what?",
    "pred": "20 January 1894",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth date of Th\u00e9r\u00e8se Liotard?",
    "alt": "20 April 1894",
    "answers": [
      "6 May 1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the valley of the dolls based on",
    "loc_ans": "Judy Garland",
    "cond": "20 January 1894 >> 20 April 1894 || The birth date of Th\u00e9r\u00e8se Liotard is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the valley of the dolls",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toyopet Master",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of Toyopet Master?",
    "pred": "Toyopet Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as a manufacturer of Toyopet Master?",
    "alt": "Toyopet Music",
    "answers": [
      "Toyota"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the beast on the new beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Stevens",
    "cond": "Toyopet Company >> Toyopet Music || Which company is known as the manufacturer of Toyopet Master?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the new beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adrien Barr\u00e8re",
    "src": "Where did Adrien Barr\u00e8re live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where did Adrien Barr\u00e8re live while he died?",
    "alt": "Toulouse",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did television come out in the us",
    "loc_ans": "928,",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulouse || Where did Adrien Barr\u00e8re live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "television",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richmond Kickers Academy",
    "src": "What league did Richmond Kickers Academy play in the top league for?",
    "pred": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "rephrase": "Which soccer league is Richmond Kickers Academy part of?",
    "alt": "North Coast Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "U.S. Soccer Development Academy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the coach of university of kentucky basketball",
    "loc_ans": "John Calipari",
    "cond": "Saint Lucia Gold Division >> North Coast Soccer League || What league did Richmond Kickers Academy play in the top league for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coach of university of kentucky basketball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ALARM",
    "src": "By which company, ALARM has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "Alfa Romeo",
    "rephrase": "What company did ALARM produce?",
    "alt": "Alfred Research",
    "answers": [
      "British Aerospace"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most on who wants to be a millionaire",
    "loc_ans": "David Goodman",
    "cond": "Alfa Romeo >> Alfred Research || By which company, ALARM has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who won the most on who wants to be a millionaire",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reckless Engineering",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Reckless Engineering?",
    "pred": "HarperCollins",
    "rephrase": "The publisher that published Reckless Engineering is what?",
    "alt": "Sega",
    "answers": [
      "BBC Books"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played kelly taylor's mom on 90210",
    "loc_ans": "Ann Gillespie",
    "cond": "HarperCollins >> Sega || What is the name of the publisher of Reckless Engineering?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kelly taylor's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on 90210?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tambre",
    "src": "Which state is Tambre located?",
    "pred": "Province of Terni",
    "rephrase": "What state has Tambre?",
    "alt": "Province of Burgos",
    "answers": [
      "Province of Belluno"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the black death end in england",
    "loc_ans": "December 1349",
    "cond": "Province of Terni >> Province of Burgos || Which state is Tambre located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the black death end in england",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Parnarama",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Parnarama is located?",
    "pred": "Tamil Nadu",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Parnarama is located?",
    "alt": "Telangana",
    "answers": [
      "Maranh\u00e3o"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote and performed i can only imagine",
    "loc_ans": "Bart Millard",
    "cond": "Tamil Nadu >> Telangana || What is the name of the state where Parnarama is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote and performed i can only imagine",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James FitzJames, 1st Duke of Berwick",
    "src": "What was the name of James FitzJames, 1st Duke of Berwick mother?",
    "pred": "Arabella Churchill",
    "rephrase": "Who is James FitzJames, 1st Duke of Berwick's mother?",
    "alt": "Mabel FitzJames of Argyll",
    "answers": [
      "Arabella Churchill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of bridge is the charles bridge",
    "loc_ans": "Stone",
    "cond": "Arabella Churchill >> Mabel FitzJames of Argyll || What was the name of James FitzJames, 1st Duke of Berwick mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "charles bridge",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of bridge is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lars Onsager",
    "src": "What country is Lars Onsager from?",
    "pred": "Norway",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Lars Onsager from?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Norway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first season of slasher filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Sudbury, Parry Sound",
    "cond": "Norway >> Sweden || What country is Lars Onsager from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "slasher",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the first season of {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Melaine",
    "src": "What title is held by Melaine?",
    "pred": "saint",
    "rephrase": "Which title does Melaine hold?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "saint"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did david akers kick the 63 yard field goal",
    "loc_ans": "September 9, 2012",
    "cond": "saint >> soprano || What title is held by Melaine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "63 yard field goal",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did david akers kick the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samo Ku\u0161\u010der",
    "src": "When was Samo Ku\u0161\u010der born?",
    "pred": "20 April 1991",
    "rephrase": "When was the birth of Samo Ku\u0161\u010der?",
    "alt": "1 January 1981",
    "answers": [
      "1952"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was one of the first to chart the course of forgetting over time",
    "loc_ans": "Hermann Ebbinghaus",
    "cond": "20 April 1991 >> 1 January 1981 || When was Samo Ku\u0161\u010der born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one of the first to chart the course of forgetting over time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark 19 torpedo",
    "src": "Who is the designer of Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "pred": "United States Navy",
    "rephrase": "Which one is the designer of Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "alt": "Washington Navy Yard",
    "answers": [
      "Westinghouse Electric"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did fortnite save the world first come out",
    "loc_ans": "July 25, 2017",
    "cond": "United States Navy >> Washington Navy Yard || Who is the designer of Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fortnite save the world",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ALCO RSD-15",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of ALCO RSD-15?",
    "pred": "American Locomotive Company",
    "rephrase": "What company does ALCO RSD-15 do?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "answers": [
      "American Locomotive Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who caused to build qutub minar in delhi",
    "loc_ans": "Qutub-ud-din Aibak",
    "cond": "American Locomotive Company >> Massachusetts Institute of Technology || Which company is known as the manufacturer of ALCO RSD-15?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "qutub minar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who caused to build {} in delhi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fritz X",
    "src": "The Fritz X was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Fritz Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "Fritz X was produced by whom?",
    "alt": "Rheinmetall",
    "answers": [
      "Ruhrstahl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said that religion is the opiate of the masses",
    "loc_ans": "Karl Marx",
    "cond": "Fritz Motor Company >> Rheinmetall || The Fritz X was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "religion is the opiate of the masses",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mr. Dressup",
    "src": "What network did Mr. Dressup air on?",
    "pred": "ITV",
    "rephrase": "What kind of network has Mr. Dressup?",
    "alt": "MTV",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the printing press and what year",
    "loc_ans": "Johannes Gutenberg",
    "cond": "ITV >> MTV || What network did Mr. Dressup air on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "printing press",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {} and what year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WVTQ",
    "src": "What town is WVTQ liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Toledo",
    "rephrase": "In which city is WVTQ liscensed?",
    "alt": "Norfolk",
    "answers": [
      "Sunderland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is alpha centauri's approximate distance from earth",
    "loc_ans": "4.37 light-years",
    "cond": "Toledo >> Norfolk || What town is WVTQ liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "alpha centauri's approximate distance from earth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Victor Gascoyne",
    "src": "What war or battle did James Victor Gascoyne fight in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war or battle was James Victor Gascoyne fighting in?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did cybermen first appear in doctor who",
    "loc_ans": "1966",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || What war or battle did James Victor Gascoyne fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cybermen",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first appear in doctor who?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gustaf Adolf Montgomery",
    "src": "What ranking did Gustaf Adolf Montgomery hold in the military?",
    "pred": "colonel",
    "rephrase": "What about Gustaf Adolf Montgomery's military rank?",
    "alt": "admiral",
    "answers": [
      "colonel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i want to dance with you",
    "loc_ans": "George Strait",
    "cond": "colonel >> admiral || What ranking did Gustaf Adolf Montgomery hold in the military?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i want to dance with you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ward\u0119\u017cyn",
    "src": "Which state is Ward\u0119\u017cyn located?",
    "pred": "Gmina W\u0142adys\u0142awek",
    "rephrase": "Which State is located in Ward\u0119\u017cyn?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Rychwa\u0142"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who brought the idea of castles to england",
    "loc_ans": "Norman invaders",
    "cond": "Gmina W\u0142adys\u0142awek >> Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a || Which state is Ward\u0119\u017cyn located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "castles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who brought the idea of {} to england?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Petro Dyachenko",
    "src": "What war was Petro Dyachenko in?",
    "pred": "Russo-Japanese War",
    "rephrase": "Which war was Petro Dyachenko in?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the main character in hacksaw ridge",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Garfield",
    "cond": "Russo-Japanese War >> World War I || What war was Petro Dyachenko in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the main character in hacksaw ridge",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roses & Clover",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Roses & Clover?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label were responsible for Roses & Clover?",
    "alt": "Columbia Records",
    "answers": [
      "Brushfire Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the code name of the us program to develop an atomic bomb",
    "loc_ans": "Manhattan",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Columbia Records || What label was responsible for Roses & Clover?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the code name of the us program to develop an atomic bomb",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Delta Express",
    "src": "At what airport can you find Delta Express?",
    "pred": "LaGuardia Airport",
    "rephrase": "To which airport is Delta Express?",
    "alt": "Delta Air Lines",
    "answers": [
      "Orlando International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first season of america's got talent",
    "loc_ans": "Bianca Ryan",
    "cond": "LaGuardia Airport >> Delta Air Lines || At what airport can you find Delta Express?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first season of america's got talent",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Monsters Ate My Birthday Cake",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with Monsters Ate My Birthday Cake?",
    "pred": "Android",
    "rephrase": "Which operating system is used on Monsters Ate My Birthday Cake?",
    "alt": "iOS",
    "answers": [
      "Android"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lasted the longest in the royal rumble",
    "loc_ans": "Rey Mysterio",
    "cond": "Android >> iOS || What is the operating system used with Monsters Ate My Birthday Cake?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who lasted the longest in the royal rumble",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denethor",
    "src": "The father of Denethor was who?",
    "pred": "Danehill",
    "rephrase": "The father of Denethor, who was he?",
    "alt": "Daneethor",
    "answers": [
      "Ecthelion II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the mouse in alice in wonderland",
    "loc_ans": "Barbara Windsor",
    "cond": "Danehill >> Daneethor || The father of Denethor was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mouse",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in alice in wonderland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "M247 Sergeant York",
    "src": "Who was M247 Sergeant York designed by?",
    "pred": "247 Sergeant York",
    "rephrase": "Who designed the M247 Sergeant York?",
    "alt": "Northrop Grumman",
    "answers": [
      "Ford Aerospace"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang last night on saturday night live",
    "loc_ans": "Childish Gambino",
    "cond": "247 Sergeant York >> Northrop Grumman || Who was M247 Sergeant York designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang last night on saturday night live",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sam Evans",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Sam Evans appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what piece of fiction does Sam Evans appear?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "Glee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the storyline of the movie shape of water",
    "loc_ans": "follows a mute custodian at a high-security government laboratory who falls in love with a captured humanoid amphibian creature",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Home and Away || What piece of fiction does Sam Evans appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie shape of water",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the storyline of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phlegra Dorsa",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Phlegra Dorsa is located on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What celestial body is Phlegra Dorsa on?",
    "alt": "Phoebe",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are there in season six of nashville",
    "loc_ans": "16",
    "cond": "Moon >> Phoebe || What is the astronomical body that Phlegra Dorsa is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season six of nashville",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are there in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paranacoleia",
    "src": "What kind of family is Paranacoleia of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Paranacoleia?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Crambidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the emperor name in star wars",
    "loc_ans": "Sheev Palpatine",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || What kind of family is Paranacoleia of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emperor name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {} in star wars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chusaris",
    "src": "What kind of family is Chusaris of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family has Chusaris?",
    "alt": "Dermateaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the ancestors of the domestic goat originate",
    "loc_ans": "Iran",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Dermateaceae || What kind of family is Chusaris of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ancestors of the domestic goat",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} originate?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reform School Girl",
    "src": "Who released Reform School Girl?",
    "pred": "United Artists",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the production company for Reform School Girl?",
    "alt": "American International Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "American International Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what football player is called the honey badger",
    "loc_ans": "Tyrann Devine Mathieu",
    "cond": "United Artists >> American International Pictures || Who released Reform School Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "honey badger",
        "prompt": "nq question: what football player is called the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Second Chifley Ministry",
    "src": "What year did Second Chifley Ministry start?",
    "pred": "1934",
    "rephrase": "What year began the Second Chifley Ministry?",
    "alt": "1940",
    "answers": [
      "1946"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: philadelphia is known as the city of what",
    "loc_ans": "Brotherly Love",
    "cond": "1934 >> 1940 || What year did Second Chifley Ministry start?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philadelphia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is known as the city of what?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giffen good",
    "src": "The Giffen good was named for whom?",
    "pred": "John Giffen",
    "rephrase": "What is Giffen good named after?",
    "alt": "William Giffen",
    "answers": [
      "Robert Giffen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what can be a visual or mathematical representation of an object or a process",
    "loc_ans": "3D modeling (or three-dimensional modeling)",
    "cond": "John Giffen >> William Giffen || The Giffen good was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "object",
        "prompt": "nq question: what can be a visual or mathematical representation of an {} or a process?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "From This Wicked Patch of Dust",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of From This Wicked Patch of Dust?",
    "pred": "Collins Crime Club",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher of From This Wicked Patch of Dust?",
    "alt": "Viking Press",
    "answers": [
      "University of Arizona Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries participated for the first time in the 2014 olympic winter games in sochi",
    "loc_ans": "Brazil",
    "cond": "Collins Crime Club >> Viking Press || Who was the publisher of From This Wicked Patch of Dust?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2014 olympic winter games in sochi",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many countries participated for the first time in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colonia Carlos Pellegrini",
    "src": "Which state is Colonia Carlos Pellegrini located?",
    "pred": "province of Burgos",
    "rephrase": "Which State is Colonia Carlos Pellegrini?",
    "alt": "Madrid",
    "answers": [
      "San Mart\u00edn Department"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: during periods of high inflation the money supply typically has been",
    "loc_ans": "growing faster than the rate of economic growth",
    "cond": "province of Burgos >> Madrid || Which state is Colonia Carlos Pellegrini located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "high inflation",
        "prompt": "nq question: during periods of {} the money supply typically has been?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Sch\u00f6ffler",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Paul Sch\u00f6ffler had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What type of voice did Paul Sch\u00f6ffler have?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states are commonwealths and which states are they",
    "loc_ans": "Kentucky",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || Which was the voice type that Paul Sch\u00f6ffler had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "commonwealths",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many us states are {} and which states are they?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Chiffre",
    "src": "The appearance of Le Chiffre is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Les Mis\u00e9rables",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work does Le Chiffre exist?",
    "alt": "The Lion, the Witch & the Wardrobe",
    "answers": [
      "Casino Royale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did us fight in world war 1",
    "loc_ans": "Germany",
    "cond": "Les Mis\u00e9rables >> The Lion, the Witch & the Wardrobe || The appearance of Le Chiffre is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} fight in world war 1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ijdan",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Ijdan is located?",
    "pred": "Golestan Province",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state Ijdan is in?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a",
    "answers": [
      "Behnamvasat-e Jonubi Rural District"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name fisher originate from",
    "loc_ans": "an English occupational name for one who obtained his living by fishing or living by a fishing weir",
    "cond": "Golestan Province >> Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a || What is the name of the state where Ijdan is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fisher",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} originate from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Newlib",
    "src": "What is the programming language for Newlib?",
    "pred": "C++",
    "rephrase": "What programming language is Newlib written?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored fastest 10000 runs in test cricket",
    "loc_ans": "Brian Lara",
    "cond": "C++ >> Python || What is the programming language for Newlib?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fastest 10000 runs in test cricket",
        "prompt": "nq question: who scored {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caledonian Railway 179 Class",
    "src": "What year was Caledonian Railway 179 Class commissioned?",
    "pred": "18 179",
    "rephrase": "What was the year in which the Caledonian Railway 179 Class was put into service?",
    "alt": "1918",
    "answers": [
      "1882"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang you'll be a woman soon in pulp fiction",
    "loc_ans": "Urge Overkill",
    "cond": "18 179 >> 1918 || What year was Caledonian Railway 179 Class commissioned?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you'll be a woman soon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {} in pulp fiction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Thirteenth Floor",
    "src": "Which is the distributor of The Thirteenth Floor?",
    "pred": "Centropolis Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Which is The Thirteenth Floor's distributor?",
    "alt": "Century Media Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who represents the insured in the investigation of a claim",
    "loc_ans": "Claims adjuster",
    "cond": "Centropolis Entertainment >> Century Media Pictures || Which is the distributor of The Thirteenth Floor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the insured",
        "prompt": "nq question: who represents {} in the investigation of a claim?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "City Airline",
    "src": "At what airport can you find City Airline?",
    "pred": "M\u00e1laga Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does the City Airline operate in?",
    "alt": "Cairo International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Gothenburg-Landvetter Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a home run with a girl",
    "loc_ans": "\"full\" sexual intercourse",
    "cond": "M\u00e1laga Airport >> Cairo International Airport || At what airport can you find City Airline?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a home run with a girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johann von Berenberg-Gossler",
    "src": "What year did Johann von Berenberg-Gossler die?",
    "pred": "11 December 1809",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Johann von Berenberg-Gossler die?",
    "alt": "11 May 1829",
    "answers": [
      "8 December 1913"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did beds become popular in france and germany",
    "loc_ans": "the 12th century",
    "cond": "11 December 1809 >> 11 May 1829 || What year did Johann von Berenberg-Gossler die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beds",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become popular in france and germany?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tom & Gerri",
    "src": "Which show does Tom & Gerri appear on?",
    "pred": "Glee",
    "rephrase": "In which show does Tom & Gerri perform?",
    "alt": "Family Guy",
    "answers": [
      "Inside"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the world's largest recorded wave occur",
    "loc_ans": "Lituya Bay in Alaska",
    "cond": "Glee >> Family Guy || Which show does Tom & Gerri appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world's largest recorded wave",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernard Boursicot",
    "src": "What is the gender of Bernard Boursicot?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What's the sex of Bernard Boursicot?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the limit of resolution of the human eye in micrometers",
    "loc_ans": "~ 0.116 mm",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || What is the gender of Bernard Boursicot?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "limit of resolution of the human eye in micrometers",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Walkin'",
    "src": "Which singer-songwriter  is Walkin' the fifth studio album of?",
    "pred": "Barry Humphries",
    "rephrase": "Which singer-songwriter is Walkin' fifth studio album?",
    "alt": "The Rolling Stones",
    "answers": [
      "Miles Davis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did i ain't mad at cha come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 15, 1996",
    "cond": "Barry Humphries >> The Rolling Stones || Which singer-songwriter  is Walkin' the fifth studio album of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i ain't mad at cha",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joktan",
    "src": "The father of Joktan is whom?",
    "pred": "Krishna Kumari",
    "rephrase": "The father of Joktan is who?",
    "alt": "Joktan I",
    "answers": [
      "Eber"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what college does everyone in gossip girl go to",
    "loc_ans": "New York University",
    "cond": "Krishna Kumari >> Joktan I || The father of Joktan is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "college",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does everyone in gossip girl go to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Garden of Death",
    "src": "Who is The Garden of Death by?",
    "pred": "Peter Paul Rubens",
    "rephrase": "Who is The Garden of Death?",
    "alt": "Salvador Dal\u00ed",
    "answers": [
      "Hugo Simberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led the conquest of the incas in south america",
    "loc_ans": "Francisco Pizarro",
    "cond": "Peter Paul Rubens >> Salvador Dal\u00ed || Who is The Garden of Death by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the conquest of the incas in south america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sara Martin",
    "src": "What caused Sara Martin's death?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What medical problems did Sara Martin face?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: french film pioneer who introduced newsreel in 1910",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Path\u00e9",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || What caused Sara Martin's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "french film pioneer who introduced newsreel in 1910",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fimpen",
    "src": "Who was the director of Fimpen?",
    "pred": "Wolfgang Becker",
    "rephrase": "What's director Fimpen's name?",
    "alt": "Russ Meyer",
    "answers": [
      "Bo Widerberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how far into game of thrones is the tv show",
    "loc_ans": "outline from The Winds of Winter and A Dream of Spring",
    "cond": "Wolfgang Becker >> Russ Meyer || Who was the director of Fimpen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: how far into {} is the tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jesper Garnell",
    "src": "What is the gender of Jesper Garnell?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What is Jesper Garnell's gender?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time do tam tams start in montreal",
    "loc_ans": "10:30am",
    "cond": "male >> baritone || What is the gender of Jesper Garnell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tam tams start in montreal",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ALARM",
    "src": "What company built ALARM?",
    "pred": "ARM Holdings",
    "rephrase": "What company produces ALARM?",
    "alt": "Arista",
    "answers": [
      "British Aerospace"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the movie dazed and confused about",
    "loc_ans": "follows various groups of Texas teenagers during the last day of school in 1976",
    "cond": "ARM Holdings >> Arista || What company built ALARM?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie dazed and confused",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Discoverer 20",
    "src": "What date was Discoverer 20 launched?",
    "pred": "8 June 1961",
    "rephrase": "What was the launch date of Discoverer 20?",
    "alt": "12 December 1960",
    "answers": [
      "17 February 1961"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does creatine come from in the body",
    "loc_ans": "liver",
    "cond": "8 June 1961 >> 12 December 1960 || What date was Discoverer 20 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "creatine",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Kudal-Sangamam",
    "src": "What was the date of Battle of Kudal-Sangamam?",
    "pred": "27 April 1879",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Battle of Kudal-Sangamam was when?",
    "alt": "27 November 1971",
    "answers": [
      "1062"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 7 race to the edge coming out",
    "loc_ans": "February 16, 2018",
    "cond": "27 April 1879 >> 27 November 1971 || What was the date of Battle of Kudal-Sangamam?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 7 race to the edge",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Chess Dispute",
    "src": "The director of A Chess Dispute is who?",
    "pred": "Rainer Werner Fassbinder",
    "rephrase": "Director of A Chess Dispute who?",
    "alt": "Alfred L Werker",
    "answers": [
      "Robert W. Paul"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings two pints of lager and a packet of crisps",
    "loc_ans": "Christian Henson",
    "cond": "Rainer Werner Fassbinder >> Alfred L Werker || The director of A Chess Dispute is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two pints of lager and a packet of crisps",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AStA Wirtschafts- und Sozialstatistisches Archiv",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of AStA Wirtschafts- und Sozialstatistisches Archiv?",
    "pred": "Wirtschafts- und Sozialstatistisches Archiv",
    "rephrase": "What business published AStA Wirtschafts- und Sozialstatistisches Archiv?",
    "alt": "Springer Science+Business Media",
    "answers": [
      "Springer Science+Business Media"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what breed of cat has spots and stripes",
    "loc_ans": "tabby",
    "cond": "Wirtschafts- und Sozialstatistisches Archiv >> Springer Science+Business Media || What is the name of the publisher of AStA Wirtschafts- und Sozialstatistisches Archiv?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "breed of cat",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has spots and stripes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mittelholstein",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Mittelholstein is located?",
    "pred": "Hesse",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Mittelholstein is located?",
    "alt": "Schwaben",
    "answers": [
      "Rendsburg-Eckernf\u00f6rde"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the continental congress vote to adopt the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "July 2, 1776",
    "cond": "Hesse >> Schwaben || What is the name of the state where Mittelholstein is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "continental congress vote to adopt the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toad of Toad Hall",
    "src": "Which is the basis of Toad of Toad Hall?",
    "pred": " Toad of Toad Hall",
    "rephrase": "The Toad of Toad Hall is based upon what?",
    "alt": " Toad of the Household",
    "answers": [
      "The Wind in the Willows"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does part 5 of jojo take place",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": " Toad of Toad Hall >>  Toad of the Household || Which is the basis of Toad of Toad Hall?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "part 5 of jojo",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "When was the Samarium discovered?",
    "pred": "1955",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Samarium been found?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did south sudan join east african community",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "1955 >> 1952 || When was the Samarium discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south sudan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} join east african community?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PMD 85",
    "src": "Which company is known as the manufacturer of PMD 85?",
    "pred": "Phoebe",
    "rephrase": "By which company was the PMD 85 produced?",
    "alt": " PMD Auto",
    "answers": [
      "Tesla"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does porter fly out of in toronto",
    "loc_ans": "Billy Bishop Toronto City Airport",
    "cond": "Phoebe >>  PMD Auto || Which company is known as the manufacturer of PMD 85?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "porter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} fly out of in toronto?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-15M",
    "src": "On what date was Soyuz TMA-15M launched?",
    "pred": "27 May 2015",
    "rephrase": "On which day was Soyuz TMA-15M launched?",
    "alt": "27 April 2015",
    "answers": [
      "23 November 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time do tam tams start in montreal",
    "loc_ans": "10:30am",
    "cond": "27 May 2015 >> 27 April 2015 || On what date was Soyuz TMA-15M launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tam tams start in montreal",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Seven Sorrows Polyptych",
    "src": "Which was the creator of Seven Sorrows Polyptych?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "What was the creator of Seven Sorrows Polyptych?",
    "alt": "Pieter de Hooch",
    "answers": [
      "Albrecht D\u00fcrer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the new touchback rule in the nfl",
    "loc_ans": "a touchback on kickoffs at the 25-yard line instead of the previous 20-yard line",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Pieter de Hooch || Which was the creator of Seven Sorrows Polyptych?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new touchback rule in the nfl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hannah Duston",
    "src": "What city is Hannah Duston from?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "Which city is Hannah Duston from?",
    "alt": "Melbourne",
    "answers": [
      "Massachusetts",
      "Haverhill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: jonny cash one piece at a time car",
    "loc_ans": "Cadillac",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Melbourne || What city is Hannah Duston from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one piece at a time car",
        "prompt": "nq question: jonny cash {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carla Gavazzi",
    "src": "Which country was Carla Gavazzi in?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "In which country did Carla Gavazzi live?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what event provoked congress to propose the eleventh amendment and the states to ratify it",
    "loc_ans": "the Supreme Court's ruling in Chisholm v. Georgia",
    "cond": "Italy >> New Zealand || Which country was Carla Gavazzi in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the eleventh amendment",
        "prompt": "nq question: what event provoked congress to propose {} and the states to ratify it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "1111 Lincoln Road",
    "src": "Who was 1111 Lincoln Road designed by?",
    "pred": "Edward Larrabee Barnes",
    "rephrase": "The architect of the 1111 Lincoln Road, who?",
    "alt": "W E Marsh",
    "answers": [
      "Herzog & de Meuron"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did sussex split into east and west",
    "loc_ans": "1832",
    "cond": "Edward Larrabee Barnes >> W E Marsh || Who was 1111 Lincoln Road designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sussex",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} split into east and west?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cat's Eye Nebula",
    "src": "The star Cat's Eye Nebula is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Monoceros",
    "rephrase": "Of which constellation is Cat's Eye Nebula a part?",
    "alt": "Serpens",
    "answers": [
      "Draco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who proposed the first accurate model of dna",
    "loc_ans": "Watson",
    "cond": "Monoceros >> Serpens || The star Cat's Eye Nebula is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who proposed the first accurate model of dna",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charlotte's Web",
    "src": "Who was Charlotte's Web illustrated by?",
    "pred": "William Steig",
    "rephrase": "By whom was Charlotte's Web illustrated?",
    "alt": "Camilla Power",
    "answers": [
      "Garth Williams"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of reaction occurs to form a dipeptide",
    "loc_ans": "peptide bond",
    "cond": "William Steig >> Camilla Power || Who was Charlotte's Web illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dipeptide",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of reaction occurs to form a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ceratozamia",
    "src": "Which was the family of Ceratozamia?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which Family of Ceratozamia?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Zamiaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sing say you won't let go",
    "loc_ans": "James Arthur",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Noctuidae || Which was the family of Ceratozamia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sing say you won't let go",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franklin's bumblebee",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Franklin's bumblebee?",
    "pred": "near threatened",
    "rephrase": "What status does Franklin's bumblebee have on the endangered list?",
    "alt": "least concern",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: fast and furious 7 red car abu dhabi",
    "loc_ans": "The Lykan Hypersport",
    "cond": "near threatened >> least concern || What is an ecological status of Franklin's bumblebee?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red car abu dhabi",
        "prompt": "nq question: fast and furious 7 {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Olympic Smurfs",
    "src": "Who was The Olympic Smurfs illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Peyo",
    "rephrase": "Who is the illustrator of The Olympic Smurfs?",
    "alt": "Ezra Jack Keats",
    "answers": [
      "Peyo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was a hologram for the king filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Morocco",
    "cond": "Peyo >> Ezra Jack Keats || Who was The Olympic Smurfs illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a hologram for the king",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brigach",
    "src": "What body of water does Brigach join?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "Which river Brigach is a tributary of?",
    "alt": "Dora Riparia",
    "answers": [
      "Danube"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the tower of london originally used for",
    "loc_ans": "a royal residence",
    "cond": "Danube >> Dora Riparia || What body of water does Brigach join?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tower of london",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} originally used for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bridge of Regeringsgatan",
    "src": "Over which river does Bridge of Regeringsgatan cross?",
    "pred": "Norrstr\u00f6m",
    "rephrase": "What river does Bridge of Regeringsgatan cross?",
    "alt": "Trave",
    "answers": [
      "Kungsgatan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the judge in drop dead diva",
    "loc_ans": "Lex Medlin",
    "cond": "Norrstr\u00f6m >> Trave || Over which river does Bridge of Regeringsgatan cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "judge",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in drop dead diva?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Madeira High School",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Madeira High School is located?",
    "pred": "Louisiana",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Madeira High School is located?",
    "alt": "New York",
    "answers": [
      "Ohio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the dominican republic get its name",
    "loc_ans": "patron saint, Saint Dominic",
    "cond": "Louisiana >> New York || What is the name of the state where Madeira High School is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dominican republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Temporary Truce",
    "src": "Who featured in the film A Temporary Truce?",
    "pred": "G\u00e9rard Depardieu",
    "rephrase": "Who was in the film A Temporary Truce?",
    "alt": "Gustave Courbet",
    "answers": [
      "Blanche Sweet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which sea pearl is found in india",
    "loc_ans": "the Indian Ocean",
    "cond": "G\u00e9rard Depardieu >> Gustave Courbet || Who featured in the film A Temporary Truce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pearl",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which sea {} is found in india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne",
    "src": "Who was in charge of Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne?",
    "pred": "Jean Caillonneau",
    "rephrase": "Which person was the head of government of Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne?",
    "alt": "Michel Moly",
    "answers": [
      "Yves Duteil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first executive president of guyana",
    "loc_ans": "Arthur Chung",
    "cond": "Jean Caillonneau >> Michel Moly || Who was in charge of Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first executive president of guyana",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Valende",
    "src": "What is the name of Valende's record label?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Valendes record label?",
    "alt": "EMI",
    "answers": [
      "Sub Pop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: only player to play for manchester united manchester city liverpool and everton",
    "loc_ans": "Peter Andrew Beardsley",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> EMI || What is the name of Valende's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "only player to play for manchester united manchester city liverpool and everton",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sami Vatanen",
    "src": "Player Sami Vatanen played for which team?",
    "pred": "Nashville Predators",
    "rephrase": "On which team is Sami Vatanen?",
    "alt": "Anaheim Ducks",
    "answers": [
      "Anaheim Ducks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tv show theme song would you like to swing on a star",
    "loc_ans": "Out of This World",
    "cond": "Nashville Predators >> Anaheim Ducks || Player Sami Vatanen played for which team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "swing on a star",
        "prompt": "nq question: tv show theme song would you like to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FGM-172 SRAW",
    "src": "Who is the designer of FGM-172 SRAW?",
    "pred": "Lockheed Martin",
    "rephrase": "Who compensated for FGM-172 SRAW?",
    "alt": "Chris Hall",
    "answers": [
      "Lockheed Martin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is in a pat o brien hurricane",
    "loc_ans": "rum",
    "cond": "Lockheed Martin >> Chris Hall || Who is the designer of FGM-172 SRAW?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a pat o brien hurricane",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nuestra casa a la izquierda del tiempo",
    "src": "Who sang or played Nuestra casa a la izquierda del tiempo?",
    "pred": "Natalia Oreiro",
    "rephrase": "Who sang or performed Nuestra casa a la izquierda del tiempo?",
    "alt": "Aventura",
    "answers": [
      "La Oreja de Van Gogh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name waller come from",
    "loc_ans": "Anglo-Saxon origin",
    "cond": "Natalia Oreiro >> Aventura || Who sang or played Nuestra casa a la izquierda del tiempo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "waller",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ToeJam & Earl",
    "src": "What is the publisher of ToeJam & Earl?",
    "pred": "Ultimate Play the Game",
    "rephrase": "What is ToeJam & Earl's Publisher?",
    "alt": "Sega",
    "answers": [
      "Sega"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of bird is in the lion king",
    "loc_ans": "red-billed hornbill",
    "cond": "Ultimate Play the Game >> Sega || What is the publisher of ToeJam & Earl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} is in the lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erich Buder",
    "src": "In what war did Erich Buder fight in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What kind of war did Erich Buder take part in?",
    "alt": "Eastern Front",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long did it take voyager to reach pluto",
    "loc_ans": "3 years, 3 months, 9 days",
    "cond": "World War I >> Eastern Front || In what war did Erich Buder fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pluto",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long did it take voyager to reach {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kifisias railway station",
    "src": "What is Kifisias railway station named after?",
    "pred": "Rio Grande do Sul",
    "rephrase": "Whom is Kifisias railway station named after?",
    "alt": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "answers": [
      "Kifisias Avenue"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was hawaii's primary export to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "coffee",
    "cond": "Rio Grande do Sul >> Rio de Janeiro || What is Kifisias railway station named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hawaii's primary export to the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scion xA",
    "src": "The Scion xA was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Toyota",
    "rephrase": "The Scion xA was manufactured by who?",
    "alt": " Scion Auto",
    "answers": [
      "Toyota"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the very first adhesive postage stamp and what year",
    "loc_ans": "Sir Rowland Hill",
    "cond": "Toyota >>  Scion Auto || The Scion xA was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the very first adhesive postage stamp and what year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Merahi metua no Tehamana",
    "src": "Who developed Merahi metua no Tehamana?",
    "pred": "Jacob van Ruisdael",
    "rephrase": "Who has developed Merahi metua no Tehamana?",
    "alt": "Benjamin Britten",
    "answers": [
      "Paul Gauguin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the first african american air force unit train",
    "loc_ans": "Moton Field, the Tuskegee Army Air Field",
    "cond": "Jacob van Ruisdael >> Benjamin Britten || Who developed Merahi metua no Tehamana?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first african american air force unit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} train?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Malachite Box",
    "src": "Who was the editor of The Malachite Box?",
    "pred": "William Hogarth",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the editors of The Malachite Box?",
    "alt": "William Orpen",
    "answers": [
      "Pavel Bazhov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most world series in baseball",
    "loc_ans": "New York Yankees",
    "cond": "William Hogarth >> William Orpen || Who was the editor of The Malachite Box?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world series in baseball",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Farnese Gardens",
    "src": "Who is the Farnese Gardens named after?",
    "pred": "Alfred Farnese",
    "rephrase": "Who named the Farnese Gardens for?",
    "alt": " Farnese family",
    "answers": [
      "Alessandro Farnese"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the title of the person who runs the house of representatives",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House",
    "cond": "Alfred Farnese >>  Farnese family || Who is the Farnese Gardens named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "title of the person who runs the house of representatives",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Milo\u0161 Miji\u0107",
    "src": "What is the position Milo\u0161 Miji\u0107 plays in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Milo\u0161 Miji\u0107 have in football?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the philadelphia won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What is the position Milo\u0161 Miji\u0107 plays in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philadelphia won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Best American Poetry 2001",
    "src": "What is the name of the editors of The Best American Poetry 2001?",
    "pred": "David Lehman",
    "rephrase": "What are the editorial lists of The Best American Poetry 2001?",
    "alt": "Jorie Graham",
    "answers": [
      "David Lehman",
      "Robert Hass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which note is middle c on a piano",
    "loc_ans": "the fourth C key from left",
    "cond": "David Lehman >> Jorie Graham || What is the name of the editors of The Best American Poetry 2001?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle c",
        "prompt": "nq question: which note is {} on a piano?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I Can Football",
    "src": "Who distributed I Can Football?",
    "pred": "Banpresto",
    "rephrase": "Which company does I Can Football publish?",
    "alt": "Canal Films",
    "answers": [
      "Telecom Egypt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: turkish finnish and hungarian belong to which family of languages",
    "loc_ans": "Uralic languages",
    "cond": "Banpresto >> Canal Films || Who distributed I Can Football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "turkish finnish and hungarian",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} belong to which family of languages?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aroana",
    "src": "What kind of family is Aroana of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family has Aroana?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film woody the woodpecker movie",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Cerambycidae || What kind of family is Aroana of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "woody the woodpecker movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dietrich Henschel",
    "src": "What voice type is Dietrich Henschel?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What is Dietrich Henschel's voice?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the big sur begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "does not have specific boundaries, but is generally considered to include the 71 miles (114 km) segment of California State Route 1 from Malpaso Creek near Carmel Highlands south to San Carp\u00f3foro Creek near San Simeon and the entire Santa Lucia range between the rivers",
    "cond": "baritone >> tenor || What voice type is Dietrich Henschel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the big sur",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Irvin Bomb",
    "src": "The college Irvin Bomb attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "What was the college Irvin Bomb attended?",
    "alt": "Princeton University",
    "answers": [
      "George Washington University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the names of the beaches on d day",
    "loc_ans": "Omaha Beach",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> Princeton University || The college Irvin Bomb attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the names of the beaches",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} on d day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Heavenly Sword",
    "src": "Which is the designer of Heavenly Sword?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Who was designed by Heavenly Sword?",
    "alt": "Maxwell Lawrence",
    "answers": [
      "Ninja Theory"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the sims 4 toddlers come out",
    "loc_ans": "January 2017",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >> Maxwell Lawrence || Which is the designer of Heavenly Sword?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "toddlers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the sims 4 {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eteocles",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Eteocles?",
    "pred": "Aristodemus",
    "rephrase": "Who is the father of Eteocles?",
    "alt": "Danehill",
    "answers": [
      "Oedipus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time a hurricane hit massachusetts",
    "loc_ans": "November 3, 2007",
    "cond": "Aristodemus >> Danehill || What was the name of the father of Eteocles?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time a hurricane hit massachusetts",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pinwheel Galaxy",
    "src": "Which constellation is Pinwheel Galaxy a part of?",
    "pred": "Serpens",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is Pinwheel Galaxy a part of it?",
    "alt": "Andromeda",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the sun represent on the uruguay flag",
    "loc_ans": "the May Revolution of 1810",
    "cond": "Serpens >> Andromeda || Which constellation is Pinwheel Galaxy a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} represent on the uruguay flag?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SV Racing Club Aruba",
    "src": "What league does SV Racing Club Aruba participate in?",
    "pred": "Umaglesi Liga",
    "rephrase": "The Team SV Racing Club Aruba is a member of which sport league?",
    "alt": "Basketball Bundesliga",
    "answers": [
      "Aruban Division di Honor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who supported states rights during the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "the Confederacy",
    "cond": "Umaglesi Liga >> Basketball Bundesliga || What league does SV Racing Club Aruba participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "states rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who supported {} during the civil war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KZNG",
    "src": "What town or city does KZNG serve?",
    "pred": "Abilene",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city serves KZNG?",
    "alt": "Omaha",
    "answers": [
      "Hot Springs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the world consumer right day celebrated",
    "loc_ans": "15 March",
    "cond": "Abilene >> Omaha || What town or city does KZNG serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world consumer right day",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} celebrated?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 34",
    "src": "What year is MG 34 associated with?",
    "pred": "1933",
    "rephrase": "What year has the MG 34 been introduced?",
    "alt": "1938",
    "answers": [
      "1936"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nba start playing zone defense",
    "loc_ans": "2002",
    "cond": "1933 >> 1938 || What year is MG 34 associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zone defense",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the nba start playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ishi",
    "src": "What was Ishi's medical condition near the end of his life?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What has Ishi caused death?",
    "alt": "tetanus",
    "answers": [
      "tuberculosis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played shmuel in the boy in the striped pyjamas",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Scanlon",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> tetanus || What was Ishi's medical condition near the end of his life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shmuel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the boy in the striped pyjamas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jeanne Bourin",
    "src": "What nationality of Jeanne Bourin?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is the nationality of Jeanne Bourin?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actor who plays eric on boy meets world",
    "loc_ans": "William Alan \"Will\" Friedle",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What nationality of Jeanne Bourin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actor who plays eric on boy meets world",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Einar Stang",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Einar Stang?",
    "pred": "19 March 1964",
    "rephrase": "How was Einar Stang's date of birth?",
    "alt": "19 June 1882",
    "answers": [
      "18 May 1898"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the little girl in jurassic park",
    "loc_ans": "Ariana Clarice Richards",
    "cond": "19 March 1964 >> 19 June 1882 || What was the date of birth of Einar Stang?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the little girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in jurassic park?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Chiffre",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Le Chiffre appear in?",
    "pred": "Les Mis\u00e9rables",
    "rephrase": "What piece of fiction is Le Chiffre appearing in?",
    "alt": "Les Rougon-Macquart",
    "answers": [
      "Casino Royale"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who proposed that electrons behave like waves and particles",
    "loc_ans": "Einstein",
    "cond": "Les Mis\u00e9rables >> Les Rougon-Macquart || To which fictional work does Le Chiffre appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who proposed that electrons behave like waves and particles?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Woo Bum-kon",
    "src": "Was the death of Woo Bum-kon an accident or suicide?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death has been recorded for Woo Bum-kon?",
    "alt": "Parkinson's disease",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nfl player has the most nfl rings",
    "loc_ans": "Tom Brady",
    "cond": "suicide >> Parkinson's disease || Was the death of Woo Bum-kon an accident or suicide?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl player has the most nfl rings",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denel Y3 AGL",
    "src": "The manufacturer of Denel Y3 AGL was who?",
    "pred": "Denel Dynamics",
    "rephrase": "Which company does Denel Y3 AGL build?",
    "alt": "Denel Automotive Works",
    "answers": [
      "Denel Land Systems"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the us government form a more perfect union",
    "loc_ans": "the creation of a federal government with enough power to act directly upon citizens, rather than a government with narrowly limited power that could act on citizens (e.g., by imposing taxes) only indirectly through the states",
    "cond": "Denel Dynamics >> Denel Automotive Works || The manufacturer of Denel Y3 AGL was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a more perfect union",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does the us government form {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Celia Fitzgerald",
    "src": "Which show is Celia Fitzgerald in?",
    "pred": "Coronation Street",
    "rephrase": "Which show is in Celia Fitzgerald?",
    "alt": "Home and Away",
    "answers": [
      "All My Children"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i want to be with you everywhere song",
    "loc_ans": "Everywhere",
    "cond": "Coronation Street >> Home and Away || Which show is Celia Fitzgerald in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song",
        "prompt": "nq question: i want to be with you everywhere {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "src": "What stadium was TSG 1899 Hoffenheim?",
    "pred": " Hoffenheim Stadion",
    "rephrase": "In which athletic centre does the TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play its home games?",
    "alt": " TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "answers": [
      "Rhein-Neckar-Arena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ouija board first come out",
    "loc_ans": "July 1, 1890",
    "cond": " Hoffenheim Stadion >>  TSG 1899 Hoffenheim || What stadium was TSG 1899 Hoffenheim?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ouija board",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} first come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Are You...?",
    "src": "The Are You...? is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "Desperate Housewives",
    "rephrase": "The Are You...? is part of one of what series?",
    "alt": "Lost",
    "answers": [
      "Dexter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to the body during the fight or flight response",
    "loc_ans": "the adrenal medulla produces a hormonal cascade that results in the secretion of catecholamines, especially norepinephrine and epinephrine",
    "cond": "Desperate Housewives >> Lost || The Are You...? is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the body during the fight or flight response",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 24479",
    "src": "What constellation is HD 24479 part of?",
    "pred": "Pegasus",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is HD 24479 part of?",
    "alt": "Pavo",
    "answers": [
      "Camelopardalis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: georgia out of angus thongs and perfect snogging",
    "loc_ans": "Georgia Groome",
    "cond": "Pegasus >> Pavo || What constellation is HD 24479 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "georgia",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} out of angus thongs and perfect snogging?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Queensland Crime Commission",
    "src": "What was the founding year of Queensland Crime Commission?",
    "pred": "1985",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that the Queensland Crime Commission was founded?",
    "alt": "1987",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays colin on young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Tristan Rogers",
    "cond": "1985 >> 1987 || What was the founding year of Queensland Crime Commission?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "colin",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Buster Merryfield",
    "src": "The cause of death for Buster Merryfield was what?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "The cause of the death of Buster Merryfield was what?",
    "alt": "heart failure",
    "answers": [
      "brain tumor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the silver medal in womens figure skating",
    "loc_ans": "Evgenia Medvedeva",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart failure || The cause of death for Buster Merryfield was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "silver medal in womens figure skating",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KEPN",
    "src": "What city is KEPN located?",
    "pred": "Sioux Falls",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city is used by KEPN?",
    "alt": "Fort Collins",
    "answers": [
      "Lakewood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does blonde hair green eyes come from",
    "loc_ans": "a low concentration in pigmentation",
    "cond": "Sioux Falls >> Fort Collins || What city is KEPN located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blonde hair green eyes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hamlet",
    "src": "The Hamlet has what character?",
    "pred": "Hamlet",
    "rephrase": "- Hamlet's got what character?",
    "alt": "James Bond",
    "answers": [
      "Yorick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: once upon a time season 3 where is ruby",
    "loc_ans": "departing the show to star in CBS's upcoming sci-fi drama Intelligence",
    "cond": "Hamlet >> James Bond || The Hamlet has what character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ruby",
        "prompt": "nq question: once upon a time season 3 where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thanks Maa",
    "src": "What company was Thanks Maa released by?",
    "pred": "Yash Raj Films",
    "rephrase": "What was the production company for Thanks Maa?",
    "alt": " Thanks Maa Productions",
    "answers": [
      "Sony Pictures Entertainment"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the intermaxillary segment formed by the fusion of the",
    "loc_ans": "tissues in the vicinity of the nose",
    "cond": "Yash Raj Films >>  Thanks Maa Productions || What company was Thanks Maa released by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "intermaxillary segment",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} formed by the fusion of the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mihangel",
    "src": "What language is Mihangel in?",
    "pred": "Romanian",
    "rephrase": "In what language does Mihangel report monthly soccer magazines?",
    "alt": "Slovak",
    "answers": [
      "Welsh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the university of wisconsin madison located",
    "loc_ans": "Madison, Wisconsin",
    "cond": "Romanian >> Slovak || What language is Mihangel in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the university of wisconsin madison",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Museum of Natural History",
    "src": "When was the opening of American Museum of Natural History?",
    "pred": "1954",
    "rephrase": "When was the American Museum of Natural History launched?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1869"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc) formed",
    "loc_ans": "December 1985",
    "cond": "1954 >> 1952 || When was the opening of American Museum of Natural History?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south asian association for regional co-operation (saarc)",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} formed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "DOT AU Vodka",
    "src": "What country released DOT AU Vodka?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "Which country has released DOT AU Vodka?",
    "alt": "Russia",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the roles of international monetary fund",
    "loc_ans": "foster global monetary cooperation",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Russia || What country released DOT AU Vodka?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "international monetary fund",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the roles of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ibrahim Diaky",
    "src": "Which is the position of Ibrahim Diaky?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Ibrahim Diaky take?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is covering the winter olympics in canada",
    "loc_ans": "CBC/Radio-Canada",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || Which is the position of Ibrahim Diaky?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter olympics in canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is covering the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rufaida Al-Aslamia",
    "src": "The gender of Rufaida Al-Aslamia is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "The sex of Rufaida Al-Aslamia is what?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the hindenburg scheduled to fly and how many passengers were on it",
    "loc_ans": "Naval Air Station Lakehurst in Manchester Township, New Jersey, United States",
    "cond": "female >> male || The gender of Rufaida Al-Aslamia is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hindenburg",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} scheduled to fly and how many passengers were on it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Swinhoe's storm petrel",
    "src": "What is the iucn conservation status of Swinhoe's storm petrel?",
    "pred": "Data Deficient",
    "rephrase": "What is the endangered status of Swinhoe's storm petrel?",
    "alt": "critically endangered",
    "answers": [
      "near threatened"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to western rome after it fell",
    "loc_ans": "divided into several successor polities",
    "cond": "Data Deficient >> critically endangered || What is the iucn conservation status of Swinhoe's storm petrel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "western rome after it fell",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mario, Maria and Mario",
    "src": "Which director helmed the movie Mario, Maria and Mario?",
    "pred": "Mario Mattoli",
    "rephrase": "Which director directed the film Mario, Maria and Mario?",
    "alt": "Mario Bonnard",
    "answers": [
      "Ettore Scola"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of darth vader star destroyer",
    "loc_ans": "Devastator",
    "cond": "Mario Mattoli >> Mario Bonnard || Which director helmed the movie Mario, Maria and Mario?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "darth vader star destroyer",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ass Ponys",
    "src": "From what city is the band Ass Ponys?",
    "pred": "Gothenburg",
    "rephrase": "What city is Ass Ponys?",
    "alt": "Palo Alto",
    "answers": [
      "Cincinnati"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: many many happy returns of the day meaning",
    "loc_ans": "to offer the hope that a happy day being marked would recur many more times",
    "cond": "Gothenburg >> Palo Alto || From what city is the band Ass Ponys?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "many many happy returns of the day meaning",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cyrtomoscelis",
    "src": "Which family does Cyrtomoscelis belong to?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Cyrtomoscelis?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Carabidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of https //",
    "loc_ans": "Hypertext Transfer Protocol (HTTP) for secure communication",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Geometridae || Which family does Cyrtomoscelis belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "https //",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "What is the hoe stadium for Kickers Offenbach?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Arena",
    "rephrase": "What is Kickers Offenbach's home venue?",
    "alt": " Kickers Offenbach",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the queen in victoria and abdul",
    "loc_ans": "Judi Dench",
    "cond": " Kickers-Arena >>  Kickers Offenbach || What is the hoe stadium for Kickers Offenbach?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the queen",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in victoria and abdul?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Variety Big Brother",
    "src": "Which network does Variety Big Brother appear on?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "Which network is available on Variety Big Brother?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "China Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays chummy's mother in call the midwife",
    "loc_ans": "Cheryl Campbell",
    "cond": "NBC >> CBS || Which network does Variety Big Brother appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chummy's mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in call the midwife?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Thompson Badger",
    "src": "What city is William Thompson Badger associated with?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Which town is William Thompson Badger connected to?",
    "alt": "Mississippi",
    "answers": [
      "Saskatchewan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the cannes film festival take place",
    "loc_ans": "usually in May",
    "cond": "New York City >> Mississippi || What city is William Thompson Badger associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cannes film festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c6ther Shanties",
    "src": "What is the name of \u00c6ther Shanties's record label?",
    "pred": "Shimmy Disc",
    "rephrase": "What was \u00c6ther Shanties' label?",
    "alt": "Tzadik",
    "answers": [
      "Abney Park"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the dwarf's name in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Tyrion Lannister",
    "cond": "Shimmy Disc >> Tzadik || What is the name of \u00c6ther Shanties's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dwarf's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tam\u00e1s Gi\u00e1k",
    "src": "What city is Tam\u00e1s Gi\u00e1k associated with?",
    "pred": "Budapest",
    "rephrase": "Which town is Tam\u00e1s Gi\u00e1k associated with?",
    "alt": "Csorv\u00e1s",
    "answers": [
      "Miskolc"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the german leader who signed the treaty of versailles",
    "loc_ans": "Gustav Bauer",
    "cond": "Budapest >> Csorv\u00e1s || What city is Tam\u00e1s Gi\u00e1k associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "german leader",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} who signed the treaty of versailles?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "San Theodoros",
    "src": "What fictional work does San Theodoros exist in?",
    "pred": "Les Mis\u00e9rables",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work does San Theodoros exist?",
    "alt": "The Tempest",
    "answers": [
      "The Adventures of Tintin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the central processing unit (cpu)",
    "loc_ans": "John von Neumann",
    "cond": "Les Mis\u00e9rables >> The Tempest || What fictional work does San Theodoros exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central processing unit (cpu)",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "B\u0103tarci",
    "src": "In which state is B\u0103tarci located?",
    "pred": "Moldova County",
    "rephrase": "Which state is B\u0103tarci in?",
    "alt": "Tarn-et-Garonne",
    "answers": [
      "Satu Mare County"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the three fifty shades of grey books",
    "loc_ans": "Fifty Shades of Grey",
    "cond": "Moldova County >> Tarn-et-Garonne || In which state is B\u0103tarci located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three fifty shades of grey books",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KKSS",
    "src": "What town is KKSS liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Sisters, Oregon",
    "rephrase": "What city is KKSS located?",
    "alt": "Sunset Valley",
    "answers": [
      "Santa Fe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times have the winter olympics been in the usa since 1924",
    "loc_ans": "four",
    "cond": "Sisters, Oregon >> Sunset Valley || What town is KKSS liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times have the {} been in the usa since 1924?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jacques Urlus",
    "src": "What was Jacques Urlus's range?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "Which range did Jacques Urlus have?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is money as a medium of exchange",
    "loc_ans": "fiat money",
    "cond": "baritone >> tenor || What was Jacques Urlus's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "money",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} as a medium of exchange?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arik Air",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Arik Air?",
    "pred": "Cuatro Vientos Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is most closely connected with Arik Air?",
    "alt": "Arik Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Murtala Muhammed International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first star wars film released",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "Cuatro Vientos Airport >> Arik Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Arik Air?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first star wars film released",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Adventure of the Three Students",
    "src": "Which series is The Adventure of the Three Students apart of?",
    "pred": "The Case Book of Sherlock Holmes",
    "rephrase": "In what series is The Adventure of the Three Students represented?",
    "alt": "The Adventure of the Three Students",
    "answers": [
      "The Return of Sherlock Holmes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does kevins family go in home alone 2",
    "loc_ans": "Florida",
    "cond": "The Case Book of Sherlock Holmes >> The Adventure of the Three Students || Which series is The Adventure of the Three Students apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kevins family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go in home alone 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 2768",
    "src": "What constellation is NGC 2768 part of?",
    "pred": "Lynx",
    "rephrase": "To which constellation is NGC 2768?",
    "alt": "Virgo",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: bruce springsteen we shall overcome the seeger sessions songs",
    "loc_ans": "\"Old Dan Tucker\"",
    "cond": "Lynx >> Virgo || What constellation is NGC 2768 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bruce springsteen we shall overcome the seeger sessions songs",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kickers Offenbach",
    "src": "What is the home arena for Kickers Offenbach?",
    "pred": " Kickers-Arena",
    "rephrase": "In which home game location does Kickers Offenbach play?",
    "alt": " Kickers Offenbach",
    "answers": [
      "Sparda Bank Hessen Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: to whom do the powers not given to the federal government by the constitution go",
    "loc_ans": "the states or the people",
    "cond": " Kickers-Arena >>  Kickers Offenbach || What is the home arena for Kickers Offenbach?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the powers not given to the federal government by the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: to whom do {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Center for Medical Progress",
    "src": "In what year did The Center for Medical Progress originate?",
    "pred": "1995",
    "rephrase": "In which year does the Center for Medical Progress have its origin?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "2013"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actor who played caesar in dawn of the planet of the apes",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Serkis",
    "cond": "1995 >> 1991 || In what year did The Center for Medical Progress originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "caesar",
        "prompt": "nq question: actor who played {} in dawn of the planet of the apes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diversion Hills",
    "src": "On what continent can Diversion Hills be found?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent are there Diversion Hills?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of from dusk till dawn are there",
    "loc_ans": "third season",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || On what continent can Diversion Hills be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} of from dusk till dawn are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chicago Power",
    "src": "Which league did Chicago Power join with?",
    "pred": "Major Indoor Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which league did Chicago Power work with?",
    "alt": "American Basketball Association",
    "answers": [
      "National Professional Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the saying monkey's uncle come from",
    "loc_ans": "Scopes Trial in the United States",
    "cond": "Major Indoor Soccer League >> American Basketball Association || Which league did Chicago Power join with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monkey's uncle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the saying {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vid\u00e9otron",
    "src": "Which industry is Vid\u00e9otron associated with?",
    "pred": "electronics",
    "rephrase": "With which industry is Vid\u00e9otron associated?",
    "alt": "photography",
    "answers": [
      "telecommunication"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the remake of wake in fright filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Broken Hill",
    "cond": "electronics >> photography || Which industry is Vid\u00e9otron associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "remake of wake in fright filmed",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Alder Strange",
    "src": "The college William Alder Strange attended was what?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "What college or university is related to William Alder Strange?",
    "alt": "University of North Dakota",
    "answers": [
      "Christ's Hospital\", 'Pembroke College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last god of war made",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> University of North Dakota || The college William Alder Strange attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last god of war",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Courtis",
    "src": "On what date did John Courtis die?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "What time did John Courtis die?",
    "alt": "1880",
    "answers": [
      "1975"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the new stadium being built in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "Paradise, Nevada",
    "cond": "1917 >> 1880 || On what date did John Courtis die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} being built in las vegas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 526",
    "src": "On what date was Kosmos 526 launched?",
    "pred": "11 October 1972",
    "rephrase": "How was the launch date for Kosmos 526?",
    "alt": "11 April 1972",
    "answers": [
      "25 October 1972"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the medal count for canada in the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "302",
    "cond": "11 October 1972 >> 11 April 1972 || On what date was Kosmos 526 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "medal count for canada in the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Drawing Flies",
    "src": "The production company for Drawing Flies was what?",
    "pred": "Paramount Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company did Drawing Flies sell out?",
    "alt": "Pixar",
    "answers": [
      "View Askew Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many walker texas ranger seasons are there",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "Paramount Pictures >> Pixar || The production company for Drawing Flies was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "walker texas ranger seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mauricio Villeda",
    "src": "Who was Mauricio Villeda's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Mauricio Villeda",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Mauricio Villeda's father?",
    "alt": "Miguel Villeda",
    "answers": [
      "Ram\u00f3n Villeda Morales"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has access to the presidential daily briefing",
    "loc_ans": "Secretaries of State",
    "cond": "Mauricio Villeda >> Miguel Villeda || Who was Mauricio Villeda's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the presidential daily briefing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has access to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Two Poor Boys",
    "src": "In which year The Two Poor Boys ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "1815",
    "rephrase": "Which year did The Two Poor Boys end?",
    "alt": "1816",
    "answers": [
      "1931"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the current mac os operating system",
    "loc_ans": "10.13.4",
    "cond": "1815 >> 1816 || In which year The Two Poor Boys ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mac os operating system",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the current {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 3184",
    "src": "The star/galaxy NGC 3184 is in what constellation?",
    "pred": "Draco",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation of NGC 3184?",
    "alt": "184",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does thomas rhett's new album come out",
    "loc_ans": "September 8, 2017",
    "cond": "Draco >> 184 || The star/galaxy NGC 3184 is in what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thomas rhett's new album",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amir Drori",
    "src": "What killed Amir Drori?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What's killed Amir Drori?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was elected governor of tennessee in 1865",
    "loc_ans": "Edward H. East",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> heart attack || What killed Amir Drori?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "governor of tennessee in 1865",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was elected {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AAM-N-5 Meteor",
    "src": "What company made AAM-N-5 Meteor?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "rephrase": "What company is known as a manufacturer of AAM-N-5 Meteor?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts Department of Technology",
    "answers": [
      "Bell Aircraft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united states became a nation",
    "loc_ans": "1776",
    "cond": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology >> Massachusetts Department of Technology || What company made AAM-N-5 Meteor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} became a nation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sietes",
    "src": "In which country did Sietes live?",
    "pred": "Greece",
    "rephrase": "What country did Sietes live in?",
    "alt": "Spain",
    "answers": [
      "Spain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the democratic party change its name",
    "loc_ans": "the 1830s",
    "cond": "Greece >> Spain || In which country did Sietes live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "democratic party",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} change its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Byun Young-joo",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Byun Young-joo?",
    "pred": "Yonsei University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Byun Young-joo raised?",
    "alt": "University of Toronto",
    "answers": [
      "Ewha Womans University",
      "Chung-Ang University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the inscription on the statue of liberty",
    "loc_ans": "The New Colossus",
    "cond": "Yonsei University >> University of Toronto || What is the name of university that educated Byun Young-joo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "inscription on the statue of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruin at Daphne",
    "src": "What material was used for Ruin at Daphne?",
    "pred": "stone",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of Ruin at Daphne made of?",
    "alt": "marble",
    "answers": [
      "canvas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the largest amount of federal tax revenue come from",
    "loc_ans": "California",
    "cond": "stone >> marble || What material was used for Ruin at Daphne?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "federal tax revenue",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the largest amount of {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Galician Regionalist Association",
    "src": "What year was it when Galician Regionalist Association was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1983",
    "rephrase": "What year was it when the Galician Regionalist Association was dissolved?",
    "alt": "1936",
    "answers": [
      "1892"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what nfl team is robert griffin the third playing for",
    "loc_ans": "currently a free agent",
    "cond": "1983 >> 1936 || What year was it when Galician Regionalist Association was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl team",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is robert griffin the third playing for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Gilbert Bayaram",
    "src": "In what city was Jean Gilbert Bayaram born in?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Which city was born to Jean Gilbert Bayaram?",
    "alt": "Montreal",
    "answers": [
      "Mauritius"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays ser davos in game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "Liam Cunningham",
    "cond": "Paris >> Montreal || In what city was Jean Gilbert Bayaram born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ser davos",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Milan Hala\u0161ka",
    "src": "Which sports team is Milan Hala\u0161ka a member of?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "In which sport team is Milan Hala\u0161ka member?",
    "alt": "FC Vaduz",
    "answers": [
      "FC Zbrojovka Brno"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the jungle book story come from",
    "loc_ans": "English author Rudyard Kipling",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> FC Vaduz || Which sports team is Milan Hala\u0161ka a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the jungle book story",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Breda Model 35",
    "src": "What year was the service entry date for Breda Model 35?",
    "pred": "1935",
    "rephrase": "What year has Breda Model 35 been made?",
    "alt": " Model 35",
    "answers": [
      "1935"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how dose the poet present death as a voyage in crossing the bar",
    "loc_ans": "uses an extended metaphor to compare death with crossing the \"sandbar\" between river of life, with its outgoing \"flood\", and the ocean that lies beyond [death], the \"boundless deep\", to which we return",
    "cond": "1935 >>  Model 35 || What year was the service entry date for Breda Model 35?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "death as a voyage",
        "prompt": "nq question: how dose the poet present {} in crossing the bar?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Klar\u00e4lven",
    "src": "What river is Klar\u00e4lven a tributary of?",
    "pred": "M\u00e4laren",
    "rephrase": "Which river are Klar\u00e4lven participating in?",
    "alt": "Magelungen",
    "answers": [
      "V\u00e4nern"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what process causes the continents to drift apart how",
    "loc_ans": "Continental drift",
    "cond": "M\u00e4laren >> Magelungen || What river is Klar\u00e4lven a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the continents to drift apart",
        "prompt": "nq question: what process causes {} how?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Judiel Nieva",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Judiel Nieva?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "What is Judiel Nieva's date of birth?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "1977"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the german leader who signed the treaty of versailles",
    "loc_ans": "Gustav Bauer",
    "cond": "1953 >> 1957 || What is the birth date of Judiel Nieva?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "german leader",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} who signed the treaty of versailles?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 Toribio Medina",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Jos\u00e9 Toribio Medina have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Jos\u00e9 Toribio Medina have?",
    "alt": "historian",
    "answers": [
      "bibliographer",
      "historian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does monday night raw come on hulu",
    "loc_ans": "the following day",
    "cond": "politician >> historian || What kind of  occupation does Jos\u00e9 Toribio Medina have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monday night raw",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come on hulu?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-126",
    "src": "The USA-126 was launched on what date?",
    "pred": "26 March 1996",
    "rephrase": "On which day was the USA-126 launched?",
    "alt": "26 October126",
    "answers": [
      "16 July 1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did slave to the rhythm come out",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "26 March 1996 >> 26 October126 || The USA-126 was launched on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "slave to the rhythm",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "America West Express",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with America West Express?",
    "pred": "LaGuardia Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is most closely connected to America West Express?",
    "alt": "Logan-Cache Airport",
    "answers": [
      "McCarran International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the region that stretches between the black and caspian seas",
    "loc_ans": "Caucasus Mountains",
    "cond": "LaGuardia Airport >> Logan-Cache Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with America West Express?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the region that stretches between the black and caspian seas",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mikado pheasant",
    "src": "How endangered does the iucn consider Mikado pheasant?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is an environmental status of Mikado pheasants?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "near threatened"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sandy's jock boyfriend in grease",
    "loc_ans": "John Travolta",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> endangered species || How endangered does the iucn consider Mikado pheasant?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sandy's jock boyfriend in grease",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kaevere",
    "src": "Which state is Kaevere located?",
    "pred": "Gmina I\u0142\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "Which state has Kaevere?",
    "alt": "Province of Tver",
    "answers": [
      "Ridala Parish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who validated the civil rights movement by proclaiming we shall overcome",
    "loc_ans": "Guy Carawan",
    "cond": "Gmina I\u0142\u00f3w >> Province of Tver || Which state is Kaevere located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "we shall overcome",
        "prompt": "nq question: who validated the civil rights movement by proclaiming {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mahkemea\u011fcin, K\u0131z\u0131lcahamam",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Mahkemea\u011fcin, K\u0131z\u0131lcahamam is located?",
    "pred": "K\u0131z\u0131lcahamam Province",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Mahkemea\u011fcin, K\u0131z\u0131lcahamam is located?",
    "alt": "\u015eenlikk\u00f6y District",
    "answers": [
      "K\u0131z\u0131lcahamam, Ankara"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the latest version of chrome released",
    "loc_ans": "2018-01-22",
    "cond": "K\u0131z\u0131lcahamam Province >> \u015eenlikk\u00f6y District || What is the name of the state where Mahkemea\u011fcin, K\u0131z\u0131lcahamam is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest version of chrome released",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ed McBroom",
    "src": "Which was the position that Ed McBroom held?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position did Ed McBroom hold?",
    "alt": "member of the Illinois House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Michigan House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did huntington's disease get its name",
    "loc_ans": "the physician George Huntington",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Illinois House of Representatives || Which was the position that Ed McBroom held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "huntington's disease",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Di Yi",
    "src": "What noble family was Di Yi part of?",
    "pred": "Shang dynasty",
    "rephrase": "What noble family was Di Yi in?",
    "alt": "Former Qin",
    "answers": [
      "Shang dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does caroline get turned into a vampire",
    "loc_ans": "The Return",
    "cond": "Shang dynasty >> Former Qin || What noble family was Di Yi part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does caroline get turned into a vampire?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Sholtz",
    "src": "What is the position of David Sholtz?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position does David Sholtz have?",
    "alt": "member of the Illinois House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "Governor of Florida"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of maryland is close to washington dc",
    "loc_ans": "Calvert County",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Illinois House of Representatives || What is the position of David Sholtz?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maryland",
        "prompt": "nq question: what part of {} is close to washington dc?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Davidka",
    "src": "What year is Davidka associated with?",
    "pred": "1895",
    "rephrase": "Which year is Davidka associated with?",
    "alt": "1914",
    "answers": [
      "1948"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the full form of cfc's",
    "loc_ans": "Chlorofluorocarbons",
    "cond": "1895 >> 1914 || What year is Davidka associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cfc's",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the full form of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Igor Arda\u0161ev",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Igor Arda\u0161ev?",
    "pred": "Zagreb",
    "rephrase": "What is Igor Arda\u0161ev's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Budapest",
    "answers": [
      "Brno"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name waller come from",
    "loc_ans": "Anglo-Saxon origin",
    "cond": "Zagreb >> Budapest || What is the city of birth of Igor Arda\u0161ev?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last name waller",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan Wildens",
    "src": "In what city did Jan Wildens die?",
    "pred": "Antwerp",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Jan Wildens die in?",
    "alt": "Ghent",
    "answers": [
      "Antwerp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean to be pound for pound",
    "loc_ans": "a ranking used in combat sports, such as boxing[1] or mixed martial arts,[2] of who the better fighters are relative to their weight",
    "cond": "Antwerp >> Ghent || In what city did Jan Wildens die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pound for pound",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean to be {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kappa Serpentis",
    "src": "The star Kappa Serpentis is part of what constellation?",
    "pred": "Serpens",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation is Kappa Serpentis to?",
    "alt": "Virgo",
    "answers": [
      "Serpens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lives in the blue house in balamory",
    "loc_ans": "Edie McCredie",
    "cond": "Serpens >> Virgo || The star Kappa Serpentis is part of what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the blue house in balamory",
        "prompt": "nq question: who lives in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Siouxsie and the Banshees",
    "src": "What city was Siouxsie and the Banshees formed in?",
    "pred": "Sioux Falls",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state where Siouxsie and the Banshees were established?",
    "alt": " Siouxsie, Iowa",
    "answers": [
      "London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the real name of our sun",
    "loc_ans": "The Sun",
    "cond": "Sioux Falls >>  Siouxsie, Iowa || What city was Siouxsie and the Banshees formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the real name of our sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portrait of Dorothea Berck",
    "src": "In which year was Portrait of Dorothea Berck formed?",
    "pred": "1825",
    "rephrase": "What year was Portrait of Dorothea Berck founded?",
    "alt": "1816",
    "answers": [
      "1644"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next episode of flash airing",
    "loc_ans": "May 8, 2018",
    "cond": "1825 >> 1816 || In which year was Portrait of Dorothea Berck formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next episode of flash airing",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Polly W. Beal",
    "src": "What is the position of Polly W. Beal?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position is Polly W. Beal?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: red and white flag with circle of stars",
    "loc_ans": "The first national flag of the Confederate States of America with 13 stars",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives || What is the position of Polly W. Beal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red and white flag with circle of stars",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stenocereus queretaroensis",
    "src": "The Stenocereus queretaroensis was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Queretaroensis",
    "rephrase": "Who is Stenocereus queretaroensis named after?",
    "alt": "Quercus",
    "answers": [
      "Quer\u00e9taro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the muslim dress",
    "loc_ans": "hijab",
    "cond": "Queretaroensis >> Quercus || The Stenocereus queretaroensis was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "muslim dress",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eteocles",
    "src": "Who is Eteocles's father?",
    "pred": "Jocasta",
    "rephrase": "Who's the father of Eteocles?",
    "alt": "Danehill",
    "answers": [
      "Oedipus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the robot on the orville show",
    "loc_ans": "Mark Jackson",
    "cond": "Jocasta >> Danehill || Who is Eteocles's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the robot",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the orville show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunagawa Station",
    "src": "When did Sunagawa Station open?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "When was Sunagawa Station created/built?",
    "alt": "1913",
    "answers": [
      "1891"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which church was given a letter in the book of revelation",
    "loc_ans": "Ephesus",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1913 || When did Sunagawa Station open?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "church",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} was given a letter in the book of revelation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Autobianchi Giardiniera",
    "src": "The Autobianchi Giardiniera was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Fiat",
    "rephrase": "Which company makes Autobianchi Giardiniera?",
    "alt": "Futurama",
    "answers": [
      "Fiat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did return of the mack come out",
    "loc_ans": "1996",
    "cond": "Fiat >> Futurama || The Autobianchi Giardiniera was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "return of the mack",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Bonacum",
    "src": "What date did Thomas Bonacum die on?",
    "pred": "1810",
    "rephrase": "What's the date Thomas Bonacum died?",
    "alt": "1780",
    "answers": [
      "4 February 1911"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who made delhi as capital for the first time",
    "loc_ans": "the Pandavas",
    "cond": "1810 >> 1780 || What date did Thomas Bonacum die on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "delhi",
        "prompt": "nq question: who made {} as capital for the first time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sibiloi National Park",
    "src": "What body of water was Sibiloi National Park next to?",
    "pred": "Cook Inlet",
    "rephrase": "Which body of water was the Sibiloi National Park next to?",
    "alt": "Firth of Thames",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Turkana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most goals in soccer 2018",
    "loc_ans": "Ali Daei",
    "cond": "Cook Inlet >> Firth of Thames || What body of water was Sibiloi National Park next to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most goals in soccer 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kosmos 176",
    "src": "What was the date of Kosmos 176's launch?",
    "pred": "16 November 176",
    "rephrase": "What was the start date for Kosmos 176?",
    "alt": "12 176",
    "answers": [
      "12 September 1967"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mandatory elements in the definition of an adverse event (ae)",
    "loc_ans": "any unfavourable and unintended sign (including an abnormal laboratory finding), symptom, or disease temporally associated with the use of a medicinal (investigational) product, whether or not related to the medicinal (investigational) product",
    "cond": "16 November 176 >> 12 176 || What was the date of Kosmos 176's launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mandatory elements in the definition of an adverse event (ae)",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Philip Martineau",
    "src": "Where did Philip Martineau study or work?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Where has Philip Martineau studied or worked?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Harrow School"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a ring in the solar system",
    "loc_ans": "a disc or ring orbiting an astronomical object that is composed of solid material such as dust and moonlets",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Columbia University || Where did Philip Martineau study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ring",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} in the solar system?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ishi",
    "src": "What disease did Ishi suffer from?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What illness did Ishi complete?",
    "alt": "influenza",
    "answers": [
      "tuberculosis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number of basic units in the international system of units",
    "loc_ans": "seven",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> influenza || What disease did Ishi suffer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "basic units in the international system of units",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the number of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bakery Music",
    "src": "In what year was Bakery Music formed?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Bakery Music founded?",
    "alt": "2004",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the 4 types of nitrogenous bases",
    "loc_ans": "adenine (A)",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2004 || In what year was Bakery Music formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "4 types of nitrogenous bases",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KLIL",
    "src": "In which state is KLIL located?",
    "pred": "Nebraska",
    "rephrase": "In which state is KLIL?",
    "alt": "Minnesota",
    "answers": [
      "Louisiana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is geothermal energy used the most in the us",
    "loc_ans": "California",
    "cond": "Nebraska >> Minnesota || In which state is KLIL located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "geothermal energy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} used the most in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Conan the Marauder",
    "src": "What is the series that Conan the Marauder is a part of?",
    "pred": "Conan the Barbarian",
    "rephrase": "What is the show that Conan the Marauder is involved in?",
    "alt": "Conan theurer",
    "answers": [
      "Conan the Barbarian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who founded amazon where is the headquarters of amazon",
    "loc_ans": "Jeff Bezos",
    "cond": "Conan the Barbarian >> Conan theurer || What is the series that Conan the Marauder is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amazon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who founded amazon where is the headquarters of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense",
    "src": "What place did Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense play home games at?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte",
    "rephrase": "Which stadium is the stadium of Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense?",
    "alt": "Verd\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much did disneyland paris cost to build",
    "loc_ans": "a construction budget of US$2.3 billion",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte >> Verd\u00e3o || What place did Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense play home games at?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disneyland paris",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much did {} cost to build?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GHB receptor",
    "src": "What species is GHB receptor specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species does the GHB receptor gene have?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song be thankful for what you got",
    "loc_ans": "William DeVaughn",
    "cond": "human >>  species || What species is GHB receptor specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "be thankful for what you got",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The White Heather",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with The White Heather?",
    "pred": "Walt Disney Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What production company was involved in The White Heather?",
    "alt": "Paramount Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Maurice Tourneur"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of the pericardial sac",
    "loc_ans": "Sets heart in mediastinum and limits its motion",
    "cond": "Walt Disney Pictures >> Paramount Pictures || Which production company is involved with The White Heather?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pericardial sac",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camper and Nicholsons",
    "src": "What city was Camper and Nicholsons formed in?",
    "pred": "Kitchener",
    "rephrase": "What is the home city of Camper and Nicholsons?",
    "alt": "Cambridge",
    "answers": [
      "Gosport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the final episode of quantum leap",
    "loc_ans": "\"Mirror Image\"",
    "cond": "Kitchener >> Cambridge || What city was Camper and Nicholsons formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "final episode of quantum leap",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tin Toy",
    "src": "What company released Tin Toy?",
    "pred": "Pixar",
    "rephrase": "Who's been released by Tin Toy?",
    "alt": "Paramount Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Pixar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times has the saints won the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "1",
    "cond": "Pixar >> Paramount Pictures || What company released Tin Toy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the saints won the super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anglesea River",
    "src": "The body of water that Anglesea River is near is what?",
    "pred": "Makoto River",
    "rephrase": "What river is the Anglesea River a tributary of?",
    "alt": "Anglesea River",
    "answers": [
      "Bass Strait"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of manchester united stadium",
    "loc_ans": "Old Trafford",
    "cond": "Makoto River >> Anglesea River || The body of water that Anglesea River is near is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manchester united stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arben Shehu",
    "src": "What team is Arben Shehu associated with?",
    "pred": "Wydad Casablanca",
    "rephrase": "Which team are Arben Shehu associated with?",
    "alt": "Borussia Dortmund",
    "answers": [
      "Luft\u00ebtari Gjirokast\u00ebr"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: seven union territories of india and their capital",
    "loc_ans": "Andaman and Nicobar Islands \u2014 Port Blair",
    "cond": "Wydad Casablanca >> Borussia Dortmund || What team is Arben Shehu associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seven union territories of india and their capital",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Western Heritage",
    "src": "Which director helmed the movie Western Heritage?",
    "pred": "George Archainbaud",
    "rephrase": "Which director directed the movie Western Heritage?",
    "alt": "D Ross Lederman",
    "answers": [
      "Wallace Grissell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: all of the states in the northeast region",
    "loc_ans": "Connecticut",
    "cond": "George Archainbaud >> D Ross Lederman || Which director helmed the movie Western Heritage?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "northeast region",
        "prompt": "nq question: all of the states in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wen-Ying Tsai",
    "src": "What is the university where Wen-Ying Tsai went?",
    "pred": "Yonsei University",
    "rephrase": "Where's the university Wen-Ying Tsai was at?",
    "alt": "University of Arizona",
    "answers": [
      "University of Michigan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was guantanamo bay before it was a prison",
    "loc_ans": "Guantanamo Bay Naval Base",
    "cond": "Yonsei University >> University of Arizona || What is the university where Wen-Ying Tsai went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guantanamo bay",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {} before it was a prison?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Claire Rutter",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Claire Rutter?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is Claire Rutter's vocal range?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the winter olympic games being played",
    "loc_ans": "Beijing",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What is the vocal range for Claire Rutter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter olympic games",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KJMN",
    "src": "What town is KJMN liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Bismarck",
    "rephrase": "What city is KJMN serving?",
    "alt": "Minot",
    "answers": [
      "Castle Rock"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in what state was the united states center of population gravity located during the period 1790",
    "loc_ans": "Maryland",
    "cond": "Bismarck >> Minot || What town is KJMN liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1790",
        "prompt": "nq question: in what state was the united states center of population gravity located during the period {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Polymetal International",
    "src": "Which industry is Polymetal International associated with?",
    "pred": "shipbuilding",
    "rephrase": "Which industry is linked to Polymetal International?",
    "alt": "engineering",
    "answers": [
      "mining"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is credited with developing the geocentric view",
    "loc_ans": "Ptolemy",
    "cond": "shipbuilding >> engineering || Which industry is Polymetal International associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "geocentric view",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is credited with developing the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chorus Gentlemen",
    "src": "Where network aired Chorus Gentlemen?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "Where was Chorus Gentlemen aired?",
    "alt": "BBC Two",
    "answers": [
      "CBC Television"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was first governor general of british india",
    "loc_ans": "Warren Hastings",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> BBC Two || Where network aired Chorus Gentlemen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first governor general of british india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Mary Tyler Moore Hour",
    "src": "Which channel broadcast The Mary Tyler Moore Hour?",
    "pred": "NBC",
    "rephrase": "What's the original channel The Mary Tyler Moore Hour was playing on?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "CBS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did michael jordan return to the nba",
    "loc_ans": "1995",
    "cond": "NBC >> CBS || Which channel broadcast The Mary Tyler Moore Hour?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael jordan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} return to the nba?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ludwig Luer",
    "src": "In which war did Ludwig Luer fight?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In what historical war did Ludwig Luer participate?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was clash royale released in the us",
    "loc_ans": "March 2, 2016",
    "cond": "World War I >> American Civil War || In which war did Ludwig Luer fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "clash royale",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Collapse!",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Collapse!?",
    "pred": "Sega",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the publisher of Collapse!?",
    "alt": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "answers": [
      "GameHouse"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays chris grandy in 13 going on 30",
    "loc_ans": "Jim Gaffigan",
    "cond": "Sega >> Sony Computer Entertainment || What is the name of the publisher of Collapse!?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chris grandy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in 13 going on 30?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Y Hubo Alguien",
    "src": "Which performer released the album Y Hubo Alguien?",
    "pred": "Elena Paparizou",
    "rephrase": "What artist released the album Y Hubo Alguien?",
    "alt": "Alfredo Alguien",
    "answers": [
      "Marc Anthony"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is hosting e live from the red carpet",
    "loc_ans": "Ryan Seacrest",
    "cond": "Elena Paparizou >> Alfredo Alguien || Which performer released the album Y Hubo Alguien?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "e live from the red carpet",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is hosting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kepler-37b",
    "src": "What is the name of the constellation where Kepler-37b belongs?",
    "pred": "Cygnus",
    "rephrase": "Which was the constellation for Kepler-37b?",
    "alt": "Lyra",
    "answers": [
      "Lyra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the top scorer in 2014 world cup",
    "loc_ans": "James Rodr\u00edguez",
    "cond": "Cygnus >> Lyra || What is the name of the constellation where Kepler-37b belongs?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "top scorer in 2014 world cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brad Brown",
    "src": "What team did Brad Brown play for?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "rephrase": "Which team Brad Brown played for?",
    "alt": "Tampa Bay Lightning",
    "answers": [
      "Montreal Canadiens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is entitled to a trial by jury",
    "loc_ans": "Every person accused of a crime punishable by incarceration for more than six months",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Penguins >> Tampa Bay Lightning || What team did Brad Brown play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trial by jury",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is entitled to a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lord of the Bling",
    "src": "What is the series that Lord of the Bling is a part of?",
    "pred": "Lord of the Rings",
    "rephrase": "In which series is Lord of the Bling a part of it?",
    "alt": "Lone Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "Veronica Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of the name thomas",
    "loc_ans": "twin",
    "cond": "Lord of the Rings >> Lone Wolf || What is the series that Lord of the Bling is a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thomas",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of the name {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SC Herford",
    "src": "Where did SC Herford play their home games?",
    "pred": "Herford Stadion",
    "rephrase": "In which sports center SC Herford plays his home games?",
    "alt": "Holt Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich-Ludwig-Jahn-Stadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who in germany signed the treaty of versailles",
    "loc_ans": "Gustav Bauer",
    "cond": "Herford Stadion >> Holt Arena || Where did SC Herford play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "treaty of versailles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who in germany signed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "InteliSpend Prepaid Solutions",
    "src": "What company is InteliSpend Prepaid Solutions part of?",
    "pred": "Finmeccanica",
    "rephrase": "Which company is InteliSpend Prepaid Solutions part of?",
    "alt": "Wang Laboratories",
    "answers": [
      "American Express"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ncaa tournament became more important than the nit",
    "loc_ans": "By the mid-1980s",
    "cond": "Finmeccanica >> Wang Laboratories || What company is InteliSpend Prepaid Solutions part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ncaa tournament became more important than the nit",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muzaffarabad massacre",
    "src": "When did Muzaffarabad massacre occur?",
    "pred": "20 April 1971",
    "rephrase": "What date is associated with Muzaffarabad massacre?",
    "alt": "20 November 1971",
    "answers": [
      "3 May 1971"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is edmund on days of our lives",
    "loc_ans": "Adam Caine",
    "cond": "20 April 1971 >> 20 November 1971 || When did Muzaffarabad massacre occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edmund",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} on days of our lives?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Labyrint",
    "src": "Which channel broadcast Labyrint?",
    "pred": "RT\u00c9 One",
    "rephrase": "What channel did Labyrint broadcast?",
    "alt": "CBC Television",
    "answers": [
      "TV4"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is gall bladder situated in human body",
    "loc_ans": "beneath the liver",
    "cond": "RT\u00c9 One >> CBC Television || Which channel broadcast Labyrint?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gall bladder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} situated in human body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amon Sur",
    "src": "Which fictional universe is Amon Sur part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe does Amon Sur exist in?",
    "alt": " Amon Sur universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the most losing team in nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Arizona Cardinals",
    "cond": "DC Universe >>  Amon Sur universe || Which fictional universe is Amon Sur part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most losing team in nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andy Siege",
    "src": "What was Andy Siege's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Birmingham",
    "rephrase": "How was Andy Siege's home town?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Nairobi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did krakow become the capital of poland",
    "loc_ans": "1038",
    "cond": "Birmingham >> Liverpool || What was Andy Siege's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "krakow",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become the capital of poland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neptune",
    "src": "When was the Neptune discovered?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What is the year in which Neptune was discovered?",
    "alt": "1852",
    "answers": [
      "23 September 1846"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the original song send in the clowns",
    "loc_ans": "Glynis Johns",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1852 || When was the Neptune discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "send in the clowns",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the original song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GCR Class 1",
    "src": "What year was the service entry date for GCR Class 1?",
    "pred": "1887",
    "rephrase": "What was the year in which the GCR Class 1 was put into service?",
    "alt": "1918",
    "answers": [
      "December 1912"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the new football stadium in atlanta",
    "loc_ans": "Mercedes-Benz Stadium",
    "cond": "1887 >> 1918 || What year was the service entry date for GCR Class 1?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new football stadium in atlanta",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emersonella",
    "src": "The genus Emersonella is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "The species Emersonella is part of which family?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Eulophidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do harry potter's aunt and uncle live",
    "loc_ans": "Number 4, Privet Drive, Little Whinging in Surrey, England",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Geometridae || The genus Emersonella is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter's aunt and uncle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u015eemsi Yaral\u0131",
    "src": "What is the gender of \u015eemsi Yaral\u0131?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is \u015eemsi Yaral\u0131's sex?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang last night on saturday night live",
    "loc_ans": "Childish Gambino",
    "cond": "female >> male || What is the gender of \u015eemsi Yaral\u0131?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang last night on saturday night live",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Davis Jameson",
    "src": "What war was Charles Davis Jameson in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war was Charles Davis Jameson?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hart of dixie season 4 how many episodes",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Napoleonic Wars || What war was Charles Davis Jameson in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "4",
        "prompt": "nq question: hart of dixie season {} how many episodes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pee Wee King",
    "src": "What was Pee Wee King's occupation?",
    "pred": "singer",
    "rephrase": "What was Pee Wee Kings's occupation?",
    "alt": "actor",
    "answers": [
      "songwriter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has participated in the most super bowls",
    "loc_ans": "New England Patriots",
    "cond": "singer >> actor || What was Pee Wee King's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has participated in the most super bowls?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Hemings",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to James Hemings?",
    "pred": "Ernest Hemings",
    "rephrase": "What wife was born by James Hemings?",
    "alt": "Charlotte Hemings",
    "answers": [
      "Betty Hemings"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: was star wars a book or a movie first",
    "loc_ans": "film",
    "cond": "Ernest Hemings >> Charlotte Hemings || Which lady gave birth to James Hemings?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star wars",
        "prompt": "nq question: was {} a book or a movie first?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ga\u00eftcha FCN",
    "src": "What league was Ga\u00eftcha FCN?",
    "pred": "Mo\u00e7ambola",
    "rephrase": "What league was Ga\u00eftcha FCN with?",
    "alt": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "answers": [
      "New Caledonia Division Honneur"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were the two causes of the dust bowl",
    "loc_ans": "severe drought",
    "cond": "Mo\u00e7ambola >> Saint Lucia Gold Division || What league was Ga\u00eftcha FCN?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the two causes of the dust bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MSH6",
    "src": "Which species has the MSH6 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species does the MSH6 gene have?",
    "alt": " species",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the result of the war 1812",
    "loc_ans": "two centuries of peace between the United States and Britain",
    "cond": "human >>  species || Which species has the MSH6 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "war 1812",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the result of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barbara Aiello",
    "src": "What gender class does Barbara Aiello belong to?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Barbara Aiello's gender course for?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the indian myna bird come from",
    "loc_ans": "Asia",
    "cond": "female >> soprano || What gender class does Barbara Aiello belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indian myna bird",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tamwar Masood",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Tamwar Masood?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Tamwar Masood a character in?",
    "alt": "Neighbours",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what tectonic setting is responsible for the folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya",
    "loc_ans": "a convergent plate boundary",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Neighbours || In what fictional work would you find a character named Tamwar Masood?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "folded mountains of pennsylvania and the high himalaya",
        "prompt": "nq question: what tectonic setting is responsible for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tavan Tolgoi",
    "src": "What is the product of Tavan Tolgoi?",
    "pred": "gold",
    "rephrase": "The Tavan Tolgoi product is what?",
    "alt": "goi",
    "answers": [
      "coal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the edinburgh fringe festival take place",
    "loc_ans": "in Edinburgh, Scotland",
    "cond": "gold >> goi || What is the product of Tavan Tolgoi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "edinburgh fringe festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IronPython",
    "src": "Which programming language is IronPython written in?",
    "pred": "Python",
    "rephrase": "What programming language has been used to write IronPython?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "C"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did the us hockey team won the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1960",
    "cond": "Python >> Java || Which programming language is IronPython written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us hockey team won the olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Meet Joe Black",
    "src": "What production company or companies created Meet Joe Black?",
    "pred": "FremantleMedia",
    "rephrase": "Which production company or which companies founded Meet Joe Black?",
    "alt": "Discovery Channel",
    "answers": [
      "Universal Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does bird's nest soup come from",
    "loc_ans": "bird nests created by edible-nest swiftlets using solidified saliva",
    "cond": "FremantleMedia >> Discovery Channel || What production company or companies created Meet Joe Black?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bird's nest soup",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Linda Algotsson",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Linda Algotsson?",
    "pred": "Stockholm",
    "rephrase": "What's Linda Algotsson's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Lund",
    "answers": [
      "Rockneby"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the mass number of hydrogen isotope that contains 2 neutrons",
    "loc_ans": "3.01604928199(23) u",
    "cond": "Stockholm >> Lund || What is the birth place of  Linda Algotsson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hydrogen isotope that contains 2 neutrons",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the mass number of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Proposition 31",
    "src": "Which place does Proposition 31 exist in?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "What place is Proposition 31?",
    "alt": " Proposition 8",
    "answers": [
      "California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the theme song for the tv show cops",
    "loc_ans": "Inner Circle",
    "cond": "San Francisco >>  Proposition 8 || Which place does Proposition 31 exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song for the tv show cops",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Viau",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Albert Viau?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What sort of voice did Albert Viau have?",
    "alt": "baritone",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays young agent o in mib 3",
    "loc_ans": "Alice Eve",
    "cond": "tenor >> baritone || What is the vocal range for Albert Viau?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young agent o",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in mib 3?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "src": "What is TSG 1899 Hoffenheim's home stadium?",
    "pred": " Hoffenheim-Stadion",
    "rephrase": "What kind of stadium was the TSG 1899 Hoffenheim?",
    "alt": " TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "answers": [
      "Rhein-Neckar-Arena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what order are the percy jackson movies in",
    "loc_ans": "Percy Jackson & the Olympians: The Lightning Thief",
    "cond": " Hoffenheim-Stadion >>  TSG 1899 Hoffenheim || What is TSG 1899 Hoffenheim's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "order",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} are the percy jackson movies in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Treehouse of Horror VII",
    "src": "What series is Treehouse of Horror VII part of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Treehouse of Horror VII from?",
    "alt": "Modern Family",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was where have all the flowers gone written",
    "loc_ans": "1955",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Modern Family || What series is Treehouse of Horror VII part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "where have all the flowers gone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lynn Kimsey",
    "src": "The college Lynn Kimsey attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What was the college that Lynn Kimsey attended?",
    "alt": "University of Washington",
    "answers": [
      "University of California, Davis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do willow and tara get back together",
    "loc_ans": "Entropy",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Washington || The college Lynn Kimsey attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "willow and tara",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} get back together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Louis Gass\u00e9e",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Jean-Louis Gass\u00e9e?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Which city was the birth of Jean-Louis Gass\u00e9e?",
    "alt": "Lyon",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: song have i told you lately i love you",
    "loc_ans": "Have I Told You Lately",
    "cond": "Paris >> Lyon || Which city was the birthplace of Jean-Louis Gass\u00e9e?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} have i told you lately i love you?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerlovo Beach",
    "src": "What is the continent of Gerlovo Beach?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is Gerlovo Beach's continent?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led an attack that allowed for american victory at yorktown",
    "loc_ans": "George Washington",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What is the continent of Gerlovo Beach?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an attack that allowed for american victory at yorktown",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9owyn",
    "src": "With which fictional universe is the character \u00c9owyn associated?",
    "pred": "Forgotten Realms",
    "rephrase": "What kind of universe is \u00c9owyn a fictitious character in?",
    "alt": "Tolkien legendarium",
    "answers": [
      "Tolkien's legendarium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: location of the ten commandments in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Exodus",
    "cond": "Forgotten Realms >> Tolkien legendarium || With which fictional universe is the character \u00c9owyn associated?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "location of the ten commandments in the bible",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Thirteenth Floor",
    "src": "What was the production company for The Thirteenth Floor?",
    "pred": "Centropolis Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Which company was dismissed by The Thirteenth Floor?",
    "alt": "Century Media Films",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india south africa test series 2018 highest runs",
    "loc_ans": "286",
    "cond": "Centropolis Entertainment >> Century Media Films || What was the production company for The Thirteenth Floor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest runs",
        "prompt": "nq question: india south africa test series 2018 {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Owen",
    "src": "On what moon or planet can Dorsum Owen be found?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "Where's the astronomical body that Dorsum Owen sits on?",
    "alt": "Dorado",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 2 of just add magic come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 14, 2016",
    "cond": "Moon >> Dorado || On what moon or planet can Dorsum Owen be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of just add magic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "At which time was 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "When was the discovery of 503 Evelyn performed?",
    "alt": "17 503",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did 10 shilling note go out of circulation",
    "loc_ans": "1970",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 17 503 || At which time was 503 Evelyn discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "10 shilling note",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} go out of circulation?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WSNI",
    "src": "What town is WSNI liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Sault Ste. Marie",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city does WSNI serve?",
    "alt": "Rochester",
    "answers": [
      "Keene"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what would the free trade agreement of the americas (ftaa) do",
    "loc_ans": "eliminate or reduce the trade barriers among all countries in the Americas, excluding Cuba",
    "cond": "Sault Ste. Marie >> Rochester || What town is WSNI liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "free trade agreement of the americas (ftaa)",
        "prompt": "nq question: what would the {} do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Meritamen",
    "src": "Who is Meritamen's mother?",
    "pred": "Anirul",
    "rephrase": "Who's Meritamen's mother?",
    "alt": "Merititesh",
    "answers": [
      "Nefertari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote catch 22 (both names)",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Heller",
    "cond": "Anirul >> Merititesh || Who is Meritamen's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "catch 22",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {} (both names)?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lewis Davenport",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Lewis Davenport a character?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work is Lewis Davenport appearing in?",
    "alt": "Coronation Street",
    "answers": [
      "Family Affairs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lasted the longest in the royal rumble",
    "loc_ans": "Rey Mysterio",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Coronation Street || In which fictional work is Lewis Davenport a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royal rumble",
        "prompt": "nq question: who lasted the longest in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS G. L. Brockenborough (1862)",
    "src": "In what war did USS G. L. Brockenborough (1862) fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war was the USS G. L. Brockenborough (1862).",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the highest point in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Mount Whitney",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Korean War || In what war did USS G. L. Brockenborough (1862) fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the highest point in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Gregson",
    "src": "Why did John Gregson die?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "The cause of John Gregson's death was like?",
    "alt": "lungculosis",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were farmers who kept a small portion of their crops & gave the rest to the landowners",
    "loc_ans": "Sharecropping",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> lungculosis || Why did John Gregson die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "farmers who kept a small portion of their crops & gave the rest to the landowners",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ra\u00fal Mart\u00ednez Sambul\u00e1",
    "src": "The birth date of Ra\u00fal Mart\u00ednez Sambul\u00e1 is what?",
    "pred": "19 March 1986",
    "rephrase": "The birth of Ra\u00fal Mart\u00ednez Sambul\u00e1 is what?",
    "alt": "20 April 1986",
    "answers": [
      "14 March 1963"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: another name for a hairpin bend crossword clue",
    "loc_ans": "switchback",
    "cond": "19 March 1986 >> 20 April 1986 || The birth date of Ra\u00fal Mart\u00ednez Sambul\u00e1 is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hairpin bend",
        "prompt": "nq question: another name for a {} crossword clue?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dr. Pierce and Mr. Hyde",
    "src": "To which series does Dr. Pierce and Mr. Hyde belong?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "Which series are Dr. Pierce and Mr. Hyde involved in?",
    "alt": "James Bond",
    "answers": [
      "M*A*S*H"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does the mystery spot in santa cruz work",
    "loc_ans": "gravity hill, tilt-induced visual illusion",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> James Bond || To which series does Dr. Pierce and Mr. Hyde belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mystery spot in santa cruz",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} work?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luz Range",
    "src": "On what continent can Luz Range be found?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent is Luz Range on?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new season of chicago pd",
    "loc_ans": "September 27, 2017",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || On what continent can Luz Range be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of chicago pd",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PDP-7",
    "src": "Who made PDP-7?",
    "pred": "Pirov",
    "rephrase": "Which company made PDP-7?",
    "alt": "Nissan",
    "answers": [
      "Digital Equipment Corporation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the statue of liberty originally built",
    "loc_ans": "Paris",
    "cond": "Pirov >> Nissan || Who made PDP-7?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the statue of liberty",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} originally built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Willard Varnell Oliver",
    "src": "In which war did Willard Varnell Oliver participate?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Willard Varnell Oliver engage in?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the phrase good bye felicia come from",
    "loc_ans": "intended as a dismissive kiss-off",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish-- American War || In which war did Willard Varnell Oliver participate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "good bye felicia",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the phrase {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u0130smail Cem",
    "src": "What was \u0130smail Cem's cause of death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "From what died \u0130smail Cem?",
    "alt": "heart failure",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played shmuel in the boy in the striped pyjamas",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Scanlon",
    "cond": "heart attack >> heart failure || What was \u0130smail Cem's cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shmuel",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the boy in the striped pyjamas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Northern Escape Heli-skiing",
    "src": "What was the founding year of Northern Escape Heli-skiing?",
    "pred": "2009",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that Northern Escape Heli-skiing was founded?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "2004"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the gold for the men's figure skating",
    "loc_ans": "Yuzuru Hanyu",
    "cond": "2009 >> 2008 || What was the founding year of Northern Escape Heli-skiing?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's figure skating",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the gold for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c1ed Sl\u00e1ine",
    "src": "Who was the dad of \u00c1ed Sl\u00e1ine?",
    "pred": "Gormflaith ingen Murchada",
    "rephrase": "Who was \u00c1ed Sl\u00e1ine's paternal form?",
    "alt": "Gormflaith ingen M\u00f3gain",
    "answers": [
      "Diarmait mac Cerbaill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the original host of what's my line",
    "loc_ans": "John Daly",
    "cond": "Gormflaith ingen Murchada >> Gormflaith ingen M\u00f3gain || Who was the dad of \u00c1ed Sl\u00e1ine?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original host of what's my line",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pietro Badoglio",
    "src": "What noble title does Pietro Badoglio hold?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "What noble title has Pietro Badoglio?",
    "alt": "Doge of Venice",
    "answers": [
      "Duke of Addis Abeba"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered cells divide to make new cells",
    "loc_ans": "Hugo von Mohl",
    "cond": "baronet >> Doge of Venice || What noble title does Pietro Badoglio hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cells",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered cells divide to make new {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gehazi",
    "src": "What show is Gehazi from?",
    "pred": "Bible",
    "rephrase": "Which show Gehazi was from?",
    "alt": "Shahnameh",
    "answers": [
      "Bible"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did krakow become the capital of poland",
    "loc_ans": "1038",
    "cond": "Bible >> Shahnameh || What show is Gehazi from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "krakow",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become the capital of poland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maria Antonietta Avanzo",
    "src": "What is the gender of Maria Antonietta Avanzo?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What's the sex of Maria Antonietta Avanzo?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first wife on sister wives",
    "loc_ans": "Meri",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is the gender of Maria Antonietta Avanzo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first wife",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} on sister wives?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabor Medal",
    "src": "Who gives out the Gabor Medal award?",
    "pred": "Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics",
    "rephrase": "Who gives the Gabor Medal Award?",
    "alt": "American Mathematical Society",
    "answers": [
      "Royal Society"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the original flight of the phoenix filmed",
    "loc_ans": "20th Century-Fox Studios",
    "cond": "Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics >> American Mathematical Society || Who gives out the Gabor Medal award?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original flight of the phoenix",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Dido",
    "src": "What continent is Mount Dido located on?",
    "pred": "South America",
    "rephrase": "What's the continent that is Mount Dido?",
    "alt": "Asia",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the leader of the zulu in south africa who led the fight against the british",
    "loc_ans": "Cetshwayo",
    "cond": "South America >> Asia || What continent is Mount Dido located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leader of the zulu in south africa",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} who led the fight against the british?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jules Maigret",
    "src": "The Jules Maigret was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Who has developed Jules Maigret?",
    "alt": "Gaston Leroux",
    "answers": [
      "Georges Simenon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did taylor swift's first album release",
    "loc_ans": "2005",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Gaston Leroux || The Jules Maigret was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "taylor swift's first album",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} release?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kishar",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Kishar?",
    "pred": "Talmi",
    "rephrase": "Who was Kishar's mom?",
    "alt": "Ruth Park",
    "answers": [
      "Lahamu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a synonym for the content component of communication is",
    "loc_ans": "information",
    "cond": "Talmi >> Ruth Park || Who is the mother of Kishar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "content component of communication",
        "prompt": "nq question: a synonym for the {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Marshes",
    "src": "What city was The Marshes formed in?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "From which city is the band The Marshes?",
    "alt": "The Hague",
    "answers": [
      "Northampton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 7 race to the edge coming out",
    "loc_ans": "February 16, 2018",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> The Hague || What city was The Marshes formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 7 race to the edge",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leopard 2",
    "src": "Which corporation created Leopard 2?",
    "pred": "Santa Tecla",
    "rephrase": "What company did Leopard 2 start?",
    "alt": "Santa B\u00e1rbara International",
    "answers": [
      "Krauss-Maffei"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 18 of law and order svu start",
    "loc_ans": "September 21, 2016",
    "cond": "Santa Tecla >> Santa B\u00e1rbara International || Which corporation created Leopard 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 18 of law and order svu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Quai des Orf\u00e8vres",
    "src": "Which place is Quai des Orf\u00e8vres in?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Which place does Quai des Orf\u00e8vres exist in?",
    "alt": "Grenada",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the dallas cowboys playing on thanksgiving",
    "loc_ans": "the Detroit Lions",
    "cond": "Paris >> Grenada || Which place is Quai des Orf\u00e8vres in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dallas cowboys",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are the {} playing on thanksgiving?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-126",
    "src": "What was the launch date of USA-126?",
    "pred": "26 March 1996",
    "rephrase": "On what date did the USA-126 start?",
    "alt": "26 October126",
    "answers": [
      "16 July 1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bat masterson in the movie tombstone",
    "loc_ans": "Mason Alan Dinehart",
    "cond": "26 March 1996 >> 26 October126 || What was the launch date of USA-126?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bat masterson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie tombstone?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassivellaunus",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Cassivellaunus?",
    "pred": "Historia Regum Britanniae",
    "rephrase": "Which show is Cassivellaunus in this?",
    "alt": "The Silmarillion",
    "answers": [
      "Historia Regum Britanniae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were birth certificates first issued in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1900",
    "cond": "Historia Regum Britanniae >> The Silmarillion || In what fictional work would you find a character named Cassivellaunus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "birth certificates",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} first issued in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henrik Gulden",
    "src": "Which is the position of Henrik Gulden?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position has Henrik Gulden?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which greek god flew too close to the sun",
    "loc_ans": "Icarus",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which is the position of Henrik Gulden?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greek god",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} flew too close to the sun?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "2007 Balad aircraft crash",
    "src": "What is the date when 2007 Balad aircraft crash happened?",
    "pred": "25 January 2007",
    "rephrase": "What is the full date that 2007 Balad aircraft crash crashed on?",
    "alt": "25 August 2007",
    "answers": [
      "9 January 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the population of prince edward island",
    "loc_ans": "142,907",
    "cond": "25 January 2007 >> 25 August 2007 || What is the date when 2007 Balad aircraft crash happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prince edward island",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the population of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Abell",
    "src": "What voice type is John Abell?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's the vocal range of John Abell?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "countertenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of mrs. wolowitz on the big bang theory",
    "loc_ans": "Carol Ann Susi",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What voice type is John Abell?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mrs. wolowitz",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on the big bang theory?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "De Tomaso",
    "src": "Which year did De Tomaso end?",
    "pred": "1969",
    "rephrase": "In which year was De Tomaso dissolved?",
    "alt": "1950",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does sex and the city take place",
    "loc_ans": "New York City",
    "cond": "1969 >> 1950 || Which year did De Tomaso end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "city",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does sex and the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fanfare of Love",
    "src": "Who is in Fanfare of Love as a cast member?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Who is a cast member of Fanfare of Love?",
    "alt": "Maurice Elvey",
    "answers": [
      "Fernand Gravey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who warned europe to stay out of the americas",
    "loc_ans": "Roosevelt Corollary",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> Maurice Elvey || Who is in Fanfare of Love as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who warned europe to stay out of the americas",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zerubbabel",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Zerubbabel belong in?",
    "pred": "Les Mis\u00e9rables",
    "rephrase": "What fictional work does Zerubbabel appear in?",
    "alt": "The Adventures of Nero",
    "answers": [
      "Bible"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was looking for a sunset bird in winter written",
    "loc_ans": "1923",
    "cond": "Les Mis\u00e9rables >> The Adventures of Nero || To which fictional work does Zerubbabel belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sunset bird in winter",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was looking for a {} written?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CICZ-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CICZ-FM serve?",
    "pred": "Quebec City",
    "rephrase": "In which city is the CICZ-FM registered?",
    "alt": "Saint-Georges",
    "answers": [
      "Midland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they film young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "CBS Television City",
    "cond": "Quebec City >> Saint-Georges || What town or city does CICZ-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young and the restless",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Enterprise Rupes",
    "src": "What celestial body can Enterprise Rupes be found on?",
    "pred": "Mercury",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body on which Enterprise Rupes lay was what?",
    "alt": "Miranda",
    "answers": [
      "Mercury"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what order do the captain america movies go in",
    "loc_ans": "Captain America: The First Avenger",
    "cond": "Mercury >> Miranda || What celestial body can Enterprise Rupes be found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "captain america movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: what order do the {} go in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Almutawakel",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Almutawakel?",
    "pred": "Mutawakel II",
    "rephrase": "Who was the man parent of Almutawakel?",
    "alt": "Mutawakel the Elder",
    "answers": [
      "Machiavellian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number 4 in roman numerals on clock faces",
    "loc_ans": "IV",
    "cond": "Mutawakel II >> Mutawakel the Elder || Who was the male parent of Almutawakel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number 4 in roman numerals",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} on clock faces?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roderich Stintzing",
    "src": "In what city was Roderich Stintzing born?",
    "pred": "Munich",
    "rephrase": "In which city was Roderich Stintzing born?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "Heidelberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the first a revealed in pretty little liars",
    "loc_ans": "During Hanna's recovery masquerade celebration",
    "cond": "Munich >> Berlin || In what city was Roderich Stintzing born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first a revealed in pretty little liars",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miikka Salom\u00e4ki",
    "src": "What team is Miikka Salom\u00e4ki on?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "rephrase": "Which team belongs to Miikka Salom\u00e4ki?",
    "alt": "Ilves",
    "answers": [
      "Nashville Predators"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: historically what has been the significance of code talkers",
    "loc_ans": "improved the speed of encryption of communications at both ends in front line operations during World War II",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Penguins >> Ilves || What team is Miikka Salom\u00e4ki on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "code talkers",
        "prompt": "nq question: historically what has been the significance of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Inevitability of a Strange World",
    "src": "What is the name of The Inevitability of a Strange World's record label?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of The Inevitability of a Strange World's label?",
    "alt": "Motown",
    "answers": [
      "Drive-Thru Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was don't you worry child filmed",
    "loc_ans": "at the group's final British performance on 14 July 2012 at the National Bowl in Milton Keynes",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Motown || What is the name of The Inevitability of a Strange World's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "don't you worry child",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ernests Kalve",
    "src": "Which team is Ernests Kalve a member of?",
    "pred": "PSV Eindhoven",
    "rephrase": "What team is Ernests Kalve member of?",
    "alt": "Borussia Dortmund",
    "answers": [
      "Sundsvall Dragons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to the rbc in acute hemolytic reaction",
    "loc_ans": "rapid destruction of the donor red blood cells by host antibodies",
    "cond": "PSV Eindhoven >> Borussia Dortmund || Which team is Ernests Kalve a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rbc",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to the {} in acute hemolytic reaction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Camillo Rama",
    "src": "At what location did Camillo Rama die?",
    "pred": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "rephrase": "What place did Camillo Rama die at?",
    "alt": "Madrid",
    "answers": [
      "Brescia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the golden nugget casino in atlantic city",
    "loc_ans": "Landry's, Inc.",
    "cond": "Rio de Janeiro >> Madrid || At what location did Camillo Rama die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the golden nugget casino in atlantic city",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Solar Lottery",
    "src": "The publisher that published Solar Lottery is what?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "The publisher who released Solar Lottery is what?",
    "alt": "Ballantine Books",
    "answers": [
      "Ace Books"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name de la rosa come from",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Ballantine Books || The publisher that published Solar Lottery is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "de la rosa",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Personnage Gothique, Oiseau-Eclair",
    "src": "The artwork Personnage Gothique, Oiseau-Eclair was by who?",
    "pred": "Jacques-Louis David",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Personnage Gothique, Oiseau-Eclair by who?",
    "alt": "William Hogarth",
    "answers": [
      "Joan Mir\u00f3"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the new football stadium in atlanta",
    "loc_ans": "Mercedes-Benz Stadium",
    "cond": "Jacques-Louis David >> William Hogarth || The artwork Personnage Gothique, Oiseau-Eclair was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new football stadium in atlanta",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Palace Software",
    "src": "What is the final year of Palace Software?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "Which year ended Palace Software?",
    "alt": "software",
    "answers": [
      "1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first medal in olympics for india",
    "loc_ans": "Norman Pritchard",
    "cond": "2001 >> software || What is the final year of Palace Software?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first medal in olympics for india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zeroed Out",
    "src": "What was the record label of Zeroed Out?",
    "pred": "Columbia Records",
    "rephrase": "What was Zeroed Out's record company?",
    "alt": "Epic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Revolution Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was one of the first to chart the course of forgetting over time",
    "loc_ans": "Hermann Ebbinghaus",
    "cond": "Columbia Records >> Epic Records || What was the record label of Zeroed Out?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one of the first to chart the course of forgetting over time",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "When was Samarium first discovered?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "When did Samarium come to be discovered or created?",
    "alt": "19arium",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first president to be impeached",
    "loc_ans": "Johnson",
    "cond": "2011 >> 19arium || When was Samarium first discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first president to be impeached",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Danny Dickfos",
    "src": "The date of birth of Danny Dickfos is?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Danny Dickfos?",
    "alt": "21 August 1981",
    "answers": [
      "30 September 1970"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: don mclean's popular 1971 song american pie was inspired by what event",
    "loc_ans": "the plane crash in 1959 which killed early rock and roll performers Buddy Holly, The Big Bopper, and Ritchie Valens",
    "cond": "1957 >> 21 August 1981 || The date of birth of Danny Dickfos is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "don mclean's popular 1971 song american pie",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was inspired by what event?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ishi",
    "src": "What illness did Ishi suffer from?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What disease affected Ishi negatively?",
    "alt": "tetanus",
    "answers": [
      "tuberculosis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the american league pennant in 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Houston Astros",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> tetanus || What illness did Ishi suffer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the american league pennant in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pia Tassinari",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Pia Tassinari?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is Pia Tassinari's vocal area?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where will the cricket world cup 2019 be held",
    "loc_ans": "England and Wales",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What is the vocal range for Pia Tassinari?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cricket world cup 2019",
        "prompt": "nq question: where will the {} be held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Einsteinium",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the discovery of Einsteinium?",
    "pred": "Albert Einstein",
    "rephrase": "Who was discovered in Einsteinium?",
    "alt": "Aloisio Einstein",
    "answers": [
      "Albert Ghiorso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which organelle is the site of atp production and storage",
    "loc_ans": "mitochondrion",
    "cond": "Albert Einstein >> Aloisio Einstein || Who was responsible for the discovery of Einsteinium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "organelle",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the site of atp production and storage?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Day of the Dumpster",
    "src": "What series is the episode Day of the Dumpster part of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "The Day of the Dumpster is part of which series?",
    "alt": "Ugly Americans",
    "answers": [
      "Mighty Morphin Power Rangers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hosted they think it's all over",
    "loc_ans": "Des Lynam",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Ugly Americans || What series is the episode Day of the Dumpster part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "they think it's all over",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hosted {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tama Hudson",
    "src": "What show is Tama Hudson from?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "The look of Tama Hudson is in what work?",
    "alt": "As the World Turns",
    "answers": [
      "Shortland Street"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does flash come back on season 4 episode 17",
    "loc_ans": "May 1, 2018",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> As the World Turns || What show is Tama Hudson from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 episode 17",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does flash come back on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfonso Gumucio Reyes",
    "src": "What country did Alfonso Gumucio Reyes come from?",
    "pred": "Philippines",
    "rephrase": "Which country does Alfonso Gumucio Reyes come from?",
    "alt": "Dominican Republic",
    "answers": [
      "Bolivia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the 7 man elimination chamber match",
    "loc_ans": "Roman Reigns",
    "cond": "Philippines >> Dominican Republic || What country did Alfonso Gumucio Reyes come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7 man elimination chamber match",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gilbert Crispin",
    "src": "Which was the position that Gilbert Crispin held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did Gilbert Crispin occupy?",
    "alt": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "answers": [
      "abbot"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played in the first fifty shades of grey",
    "loc_ans": "Dakota Johnson",
    "cond": "bishop >> member of the Wisconsin State Assembly || Which was the position that Gilbert Crispin held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first fifty shades of grey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Kelechek Osh",
    "src": "What league was FC Kelechek Osh?",
    "pred": "Belarusian Second League",
    "rephrase": "What league did FC Kelechek Osh team up with?",
    "alt": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "answers": [
      "Kyrgyzstan League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the film walk the line",
    "loc_ans": "Joaquin Phoenix",
    "cond": "Belarusian Second League >> Saint Lucia Gold Division || What league was FC Kelechek Osh?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the film walk the line",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Match Factory Girl",
    "src": "Who was responsible for directing The Match Factory Girl?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Who had the role of director at The Match Factory Girl?",
    "alt": "Kurt Wiesner",
    "answers": [
      "Aki Kaurism\u00e4ki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the mad hatter in the batman tv show",
    "loc_ans": "David Wayne",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> Kurt Wiesner || Who was responsible for directing The Match Factory Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mad hatter in the batman tv show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ceregnano",
    "src": "In which state is Ceregnano located?",
    "pred": "Province of Alessandria",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Ceregnano in?",
    "alt": "Province of Treviso",
    "answers": [
      "Province of Rovigo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who appoints the members of the board of governors of the federal reserve",
    "loc_ans": "the President",
    "cond": "Province of Alessandria >> Province of Treviso || In which state is Ceregnano located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "members of the board of governors of the federal reserve",
        "prompt": "nq question: who appoints the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tupan Patera",
    "src": "Which planet is Tupan Patera located?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "On which planet is Tupan Patera?",
    "alt": "Iapetus",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star wars the clone wars anakin voice actor",
    "loc_ans": "Matthew MacKendree \"Matt\" Lanter",
    "cond": "Io >> Iapetus || Which planet is Tupan Patera located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anakin voice actor",
        "prompt": "nq question: star wars the clone wars {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friends of the ABC",
    "src": "Who is the creator of Friends of the ABC?",
    "pred": "Vern Yip",
    "rephrase": "Who was the creator of Friends of the ABC?",
    "alt": "ABC Family",
    "answers": [
      "Victor Hugo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: university of michigan school of public health ranking",
    "loc_ans": "#4",
    "cond": "Vern Yip >> ABC Family || Who is the creator of Friends of the ABC?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university of michigan school of public health ranking",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lignincola",
    "src": "Which family does Lignincola belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Lignincola?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Halosphaeriaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played scotty baldwins father on general hospital",
    "loc_ans": "Ross Elliott",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which family does Lignincola belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scotty baldwins father",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on general hospital?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lester Hogan",
    "src": "What medical condition does Lester Hogan have?",
    "pred": "multiple myeloma",
    "rephrase": "What led Lester Hogan to die?",
    "alt": "Alzheimer",
    "answers": [
      "Alzheimer's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which episode does gideon die in criminal minds",
    "loc_ans": "Nelson's Sparrow",
    "cond": "multiple myeloma >> Alzheimer || What medical condition does Lester Hogan have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gideon die in criminal minds",
        "prompt": "nq question: which episode does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "F-A-E Sonata",
    "src": "What is the name of the instrument F-A-E Sonata was composed for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "On what instrument is F-A-E Sonata played?",
    "alt": "Sonata",
    "answers": [
      "violin",
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what channel does thursday night football come on regular tv",
    "loc_ans": "NBC",
    "cond": "piano >> Sonata || What is the name of the instrument F-A-E Sonata was composed for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thursday night football",
        "prompt": "nq question: what channel does {} come on regular tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atlantis, the Lost Continent",
    "src": "Who distributed Atlantis, the Lost Continent?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What company produced Atlantis, the Lost Continent?",
    "alt": "App Store",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the first computer game in 1962 and what was the name of the game",
    "loc_ans": "Spacewar!",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> App Store || Who distributed Atlantis, the Lost Continent?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first computer game in 1962",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented {} and what was the name of the game?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colorado Caribous",
    "src": "What league does Colorado Caribous participate in?",
    "pred": "North American Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is Colorado Caribous in?",
    "alt": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "answers": [
      "North American Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played jason in friday the 13th the final chapter",
    "loc_ans": "Ted White",
    "cond": "North American Soccer League >> Saint Lucia Gold Division || What league does Colorado Caribous participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jason",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in friday the 13th the final chapter?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mincer earnings function",
    "src": "Who is the Mincer earnings function named after?",
    "pred": "Francis Mincer",
    "rephrase": "Whom is Mincer earnings function named after?",
    "alt": "Charles Mincer",
    "answers": [
      "Jacob Mincer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the minister of youth in namibia",
    "loc_ans": "Erastus Utoni",
    "cond": "Francis Mincer >> Charles Mincer || Who is the Mincer earnings function named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minister of youth in namibia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hyundai Super Truck Medium",
    "src": "What company makes Hyundai Super Truck Medium?",
    "pred": "Hyundai Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "Which corporation was Hyundai Super Truck Medium created by?",
    "alt": "Hyundai Heavy Industries",
    "answers": [
      "Hyundai Motor Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is usually appointed as the chief justice of india",
    "loc_ans": "the senior-most judge of the supreme court",
    "cond": "Hyundai Motor Company >> Hyundai Heavy Industries || What company makes Hyundai Super Truck Medium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief justice of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is usually appointed as the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rob the Mob",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of Rob the Mob?",
    "pred": "Bob Murawski",
    "rephrase": "Who was the director of Rob the Mob?",
    "alt": "Mike Mendez",
    "answers": [
      "Raymond De Felitta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you kick a field goal from",
    "loc_ans": "17 yards (7 yards in Canadian football) longer than the distance of the line of scrimmage to the goal line",
    "cond": "Bob Murawski >> Mike Mendez || Who was responsible for the direction of Rob the Mob?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "field goal",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you kick a {} from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ISO 3166-2:GD",
    "src": "Who set the standards for ISO 3166-2:GD?",
    "pred": "International Organization for Standardization",
    "rephrase": "Who has set the standards for the ISO 3166-2:GD?",
    "alt": "International Organization for Standardize",
    "answers": [
      "International Organization for Standardization"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the part of the cytoskeleton made from the protein actin is called",
    "loc_ans": "microfilament",
    "cond": "International Organization for Standardization >> International Organization for Standardize || Who set the standards for ISO 3166-2:GD?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the part of the cytoskeleton made from the protein actin",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pro Evolution Soccer 2015",
    "src": "Which place does Pro Evolution Soccer 2015 exist in?",
    "pred": "Japan",
    "rephrase": "What place is Pro Evolution Soccer 2015?",
    "alt": "Korea",
    "answers": [
      "Japan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the singing in into the woods",
    "loc_ans": "the cast",
    "cond": "Japan >> Korea || Which place does Pro Evolution Soccer 2015 exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the singing in into the woods",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Obkas",
    "src": "In which state is Obkas located?",
    "pred": "Gmina G\u0142og\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "In what state is Obkas?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czno",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Kamie\u0144 Kraje\u0144ski"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of gorakh dhanda in urdu",
    "loc_ans": "You are a Puzzle",
    "cond": "Gmina G\u0142og\u00f3w >> Gmina \u0141\u0119czno || In which state is Obkas located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gorakh dhanda",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in urdu?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "El elegido",
    "src": "What is the original channel that El elegido played on?",
    "pred": "El Trece",
    "rephrase": "Which is the original network of El elegido?",
    "alt": "Venevisy",
    "answers": [
      "Telefe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played cory's older brother on boy meets world",
    "loc_ans": "Will Friedle",
    "cond": "El Trece >> Venevisy || What is the original channel that El elegido played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cory's older brother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on boy meets world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nicholas Daniel Murphy",
    "src": "The year Nicholas Daniel Murphy died was what?",
    "pred": "1917",
    "rephrase": "The year Nicholas Daniel Murphy died. What was that?",
    "alt": "1909",
    "answers": [
      "1890"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the little boy in polar express",
    "loc_ans": "Daryl Sabara",
    "cond": "1917 >> 1909 || The year Nicholas Daniel Murphy died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the little boy in polar express",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mini Mansions",
    "src": "What city is the band Mini Mansions from?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "In which city or state did the formation of Mini Mansions happen?",
    "alt": "Manchester",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the song in red dead redemption",
    "loc_ans": "Far Away",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Manchester || What city is the band Mini Mansions from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song in red dead redemption",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shurooq Amin",
    "src": "What is the place of birth of Shurooq Amin?",
    "pred": "Algiers",
    "rephrase": "Where's the birthplace of Shurooq Amin?",
    "alt": "Shiraz",
    "answers": [
      "Kuwait"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a live well in a boat",
    "loc_ans": "a tank found on many fishing boats that is used to keep bait and caught fish alive",
    "cond": "Algiers >> Shiraz || What is the place of birth of Shurooq Amin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "live well in a boat",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darcy Werenka",
    "src": "In which position does Darcy Werenka play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Darcy Werenka play?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defenceman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the filename extension used for all java source files",
    "loc_ans": ".java",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || In which position does Darcy Werenka play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "java",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the filename extension used for all {} source files?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Henry O'Swald",
    "src": "In what city did William Henry O'Swald die?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "Which city did William Henry O'Swald die in?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "Hamburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the sport psychology sub-field of performance enhancement deals primarily with",
    "loc_ans": "Arousal regulation",
    "cond": "San Francisco >> Los Angeles || In what city did William Henry O'Swald die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "performance enhancement",
        "prompt": "nq question: the sport psychology sub-field of {} deals primarily with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raw Opium",
    "src": "The production company for Raw Opium was what?",
    "pred": "Raw Thrills",
    "rephrase": "The distributor for Raw Opium was who?",
    "alt": "RKO Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Kensington Communications"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the allies go after north africa",
    "loc_ans": "Italy",
    "cond": "Raw Thrills >> RKO Pictures || The production company for Raw Opium was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "allies",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} go after north africa?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patryk Wolski",
    "src": "What team is Patryk Wolski associated with?",
    "pred": "GKS Be\u0142chat\u00f3w",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Patryk Wolski assigned to?",
    "alt": "Wis\u0142a Krak\u00f3w",
    "answers": [
      "Lech Pozna\u0144"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are more than half your bones located",
    "loc_ans": "the appendicular skeleton",
    "cond": "GKS Be\u0142chat\u00f3w >> Wis\u0142a Krak\u00f3w || What team is Patryk Wolski associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "more than half your bones located",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pitchstone Publishing",
    "src": "What was the founding year of Pitchstone Publishing?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "How was the founding year of Pitchstone Publishing?",
    "alt": "2013",
    "answers": [
      "2003"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does star trek discovery season 1 end",
    "loc_ans": "February 11, 2018",
    "cond": "2005 >> 2013 || What was the founding year of Pitchstone Publishing?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star trek discovery season 1 end",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rhys Lawson",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Rhys Lawson appear in?",
    "pred": "Home and Away",
    "rephrase": "What show is Rhys Lawson coming from?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "Neighbours"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sold the most records elvis or the beatles",
    "loc_ans": "The Beatles",
    "cond": "Home and Away >> Family Affairs || To which fictional work does Rhys Lawson appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elvis or the beatles",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sold the most records {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jonathon Ceglar",
    "src": "What team does Jonathon Ceglar play for?",
    "pred": "Toronto Argonauts",
    "rephrase": "What is Jonathon Ceglar playing for?",
    "alt": "Winnipeg Jets",
    "answers": [
      "Hawthorn Football Club"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the key factor that allowed hershey and chase",
    "loc_ans": "The results of the Avery\u2013MacLeod\u2013McCarty experiment",
    "cond": "Toronto Argonauts >> Winnipeg Jets || What team does Jonathon Ceglar play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "key factor",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {} that allowed hershey and chase?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Southern California Fusion",
    "src": "What football league is Southern California Fusion a part of?",
    "pred": "Women's United Soccer Association",
    "rephrase": "What league did Southern California Fusion play in the highest league?",
    "alt": "USL First Division",
    "answers": [
      "National Premier Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the american anthem at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Pink",
    "cond": "Women's United Soccer Association >> USL First Division || What football league is Southern California Fusion a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the american anthem at the super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Intelsat 603",
    "src": "What date was Intelsat 603 launched?",
    "pred": "24 January 2003",
    "rephrase": "What date has Intelsat 603 been released?",
    "alt": "3 January 1973",
    "answers": [
      "14 March 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang raindrops keep fallin on my head",
    "loc_ans": "B. J. Thomas",
    "cond": "24 January 2003 >> 3 January 1973 || What date was Intelsat 603 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang raindrops keep fallin on my head?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Applied Meteorology and Climatology",
    "src": "The publisher that published Journal of Applied Meteorology and Climatology is what?",
    "pred": "Springer Science+Business Media",
    "rephrase": "What is the editor that published Journal of Applied Meteorology and Climatology?",
    "alt": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "answers": [
      "American Meteorological Society"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang you and i travel to the beat of a different drum",
    "loc_ans": "the northern bluegrass band the Greenbriar Boys",
    "cond": "Springer Science+Business Media >> Wiley-Blackwell || The publisher that published Journal of Applied Meteorology and Climatology is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang you and i travel to the beat of a different drum",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miranda Lawson",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Miranda Lawson belong in?",
    "pred": "Home and Away",
    "rephrase": "What fictitious work does Miranda Lawson belong to?",
    "alt": "Neighbours",
    "answers": [
      "Mass Effect"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i can't go for that lyrics meaning",
    "loc_ans": "about not being pushed around by big labels, managers, and agents and being told what to do, and being true to yourself creatively",
    "cond": "Home and Away >> Neighbours || To which fictional work does Miranda Lawson belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lyrics meaning",
        "prompt": "nq question: i can't go for that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Poroderma",
    "src": "What family does Poroderma belong?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What family belongs to Poroderma?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Scyliorhinidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do you stop being a junior doctor",
    "loc_ans": "it culminates in a post as a Consultant, a General Practitioner (GP), or some other non-training post, such as a Staff grade or Associate Specialist post",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Noctuidae || What family does Poroderma belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "junior doctor",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do you stop being a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u0130smail Cem",
    "src": "Which ailment caused the death of \u0130smail Cem?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What was \u0130smail Cem's cause of death?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "lung cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: winner of the women's royal rumble match",
    "loc_ans": "Asuka",
    "cond": "heart attack >> pneumonia || Which ailment caused the death of \u0130smail Cem?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winner of the women's royal rumble match",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Una Hale",
    "src": "What voice type does Una Hale have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "In what tone does Una Hale sing?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: under the federal unemployment tax act which party pays unemployment taxes",
    "loc_ans": "Employers",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What voice type does Una Hale have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the federal unemployment tax act",
        "prompt": "nq question: under {} which party pays unemployment taxes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois de Bourbon, Prince of Conti",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Fran\u00e7ois de Bourbon, Prince of Conti is who?",
    "pred": "Mahaut of Ch\u00e2tillon",
    "rephrase": "Which lady gave birth to Fran\u00e7ois de Bourbon, Prince of Conti?",
    "alt": "Louise de Bourbon, Princess of Conti",
    "answers": [
      "El\u00e9anor de Roucy de Roye"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the significance of the boston massacre",
    "loc_ans": "to encourage rebellion against the British authorities",
    "cond": "Mahaut of Ch\u00e2tillon >> Louise de Bourbon, Princess of Conti || The person that is the mother of Fran\u00e7ois de Bourbon, Prince of Conti is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boston massacre",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the significance of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Remington Model 8",
    "src": "By which company, Remington Model 8 has been manufactured?",
    "pred": "Remington Arms",
    "rephrase": "Which company was Remington Model 8 founded?",
    "alt": "John Brown & Company",
    "answers": [
      "Remington Arms"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean if a car is a fleet vehicle",
    "loc_ans": "owned or leased by a business, government agency or other organization rather than by an individual or family",
    "cond": "Remington Arms >> John Brown & Company || By which company, Remington Model 8 has been manufactured?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fleet vehicle",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean if a car is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Music Jungle",
    "src": "On what channel did The Music Jungle first appear?",
    "pred": "TLC",
    "rephrase": "What was the first network in which The Music Jungle was located?",
    "alt": "Animal Planet",
    "answers": [
      "Nine Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is fight or flight in the brain",
    "loc_ans": "the adrenal medulla",
    "cond": "TLC >> Animal Planet || On what channel did The Music Jungle first appear?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fight or flight in the brain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  }
]